<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diagnosis | PlatCOVID</title>
    <link>/syntax_summary/diagnsosis/</link>
      <atom:link href="/syntax_summary/diagnsosis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Diagnosis</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>BioHub - UFPE</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu7e12209333f22d741aca7d462871821f_9877_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Diagnosis</title>
      <link>/syntax_summary/diagnsosis/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diagnsose Sentence Context</title>
      <link>/syntax_summary/diagnsosis/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/syntax_summary/diagnsosis/info/</guid>
      <description> 

&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 1.&lt;/strong&gt; Analysis of context sentence of 340 absracts clustered as diagnosis.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
PMID
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Gene Context Sentence
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
ePubDate
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/31944312&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Recent advances in the detection of respiratory virus infection in humans.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Conventional diagnostic tests, such as the assays for rapid detection of antiviral antibodies or viral antigens, are widely used in many clinical laboratories. […] With the development of modern technologies, new diagnostic strategies, including multiplex nucleic acid amplification and microarray-based assays, are emerging. […] This review summarizes currently available and novel emerging diagnostic methods for the detection of common respiratory viruses, such as influenza virus, human respiratory syncytial virus, coronavirus, human adenovirus, and human rhinovirus. […] It is anticipated that such data will assist researchers and clinicians to develop appropriate diagnostic strategies for timely and effective detection of respiratory virus infections.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31987001&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;31987001&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
These findings provide the basis for starting further studies on the pathogenesis, and optimizing the design of diagnostic, antiviral and vaccination strategies for this emerging infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31992387&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;31992387&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We aimed to develop and deploy robust diagnostic methodology for use in public health laboratory settings without having virus material available. […] Here we present a validated diagnostic workflow for 2019-nCoV, its design relying on close genetic relatedness of 2019-nCoV with SARS coronavirus, making use of synthetic nucleic acid technology.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32004427&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32004427&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We report the first case of 2019-nCoV infection confirmed in the United States and describe the identification, diagnosis, clinical course, and management of the case, including the patient’s initial mild symptoms at presentation with progression to pneumonia on day 9 of illness.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32017984&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Measures for diagnosing and treating infections by a novel coronavirus responsible for a pneumonia outbreak originating in Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here, we focus on advances in research and development of fast diagnosis methods, as well as potential prophylactics and therapeutics to prevent or treat 2019-nCoV infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32020915&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32020915&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Herein, we present on an overview of the currently available information on the pathogenesis, epidemiology, clinical presentation, diagnosis, and treatment of this virus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32023681&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Diagnosis and clinical management of 2019 novel coronavirus infection: an operational recommendation of Peking Union Medical College Hospital (V2.0)].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To standardize the diagnosis and treatment of this new infectious disease, operational guidelines for the diagnosis and management of 2019-nCoV infection is accomplished by Peking Union Medical College Hospital.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32023682&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32023682&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After the outbreak of this disease, Chinese scientists invested a lot of energy to carry out research by developing rapid diagnostic reagents, identifying the characters of the pathogen, screening out clinical drugs that may inhibit the virus, and are rapidly developing vaccines.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32023684&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Efficient management of novel coronavirus pneumonia by efficient prevention and control in scientific manner].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Based on current studies, the author summarized the clinical characteristics and evolution of the novel viral pneumonia, and proposed the key points of diagnosis and treatment, the scientific management of both confirmed and suspected cases, and the scientific management of disease prevention and control.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32023686&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Early detection and disease assessment of patients with novel coronavirus pneumonia].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The novel coronavirus has the characteristics of rapid transmission, atypical clinical symptoms, and easy to affect both lungs, leading to missed diagnosis and misdiagnosis, as well as difficult to detection and assessment at early stage.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32026148&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnosis and treatment recommendations for pediatric respiratory infection caused by the 2019 novel coronavirus.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Following the latest National recommendations for diagnosis and treatment of pneumonia caused by 2019-nCoV (the 4th edition) and current status of clinical practice in Zhejiang Province, recommendations for the diagnosis and treatment of respiratory infection caused by 2019-nCoV for children were drafted by the National Clinical Research Center for Child Health, the National Children’s Regional Medical Center, Children’s Hospital, Zhejiang University School of Medicine to further standardize the protocol for diagnosis and treatment of respiratory infection in children caused by 2019-nCoV.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32026671&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Analysis of clinical features of 29 patients with 2019 novel coronavirus pneumonia].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
According to the relevant diagnostic criteria, the patients were divided into three groups: mild (15 cases), severe (9 cases) and critical (5 cases). […] High resolution CT is of great value in the differential diagnosis of this disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32029004&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A rapid advice guideline for the diagnosis and treatment of 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infected pneumonia (standard version).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This guideline includes the guideline methodology, epidemiological characteristics, disease screening and population prevention, diagnosis, treatment and control (including traditional Chinese Medicine), nosocomial infection prevention and control, and disease nursing of the 2019-nCoV.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32033513&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32033513&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
the National Health Commission of the People’s Republic of China publish the guidelines for the diagnosis and treatment of novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection (trial version 5) .
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32033514&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Expert consensus for bronchoscopy during the epidemic of 2019 Novel Coronavirus infection (Trial version)].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It needs to emphasize that bronchoscopy should not be used as a routine means for the diagnosis of 2019-nCoV infection sampling.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32034659&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnosis, treatment, and prevention of 2019 novel coronavirus infection in children: experts’ consensus statement.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This statement is based on the Novel Coronavirus Infection Pneumonia Diagnosis and Treatment Standards (the fourth edition) (National Health Committee) and other previous diagnosis and treatment strategies for pediatric virus infections. […] The present consensus statement summarizes current strategies on diagnosis, treatment, and prevention of 2019-nCoV infection in children.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32035431&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32035431&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In about 20 days since the diagnosis of the first case of the 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) in Korea on January 20, 2020, 28 cases have been confirmed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32046815&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Laboratory readiness and response for novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) in expert laboratories in 30 EU/EEA countries, January 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Thirty-eight laboratories in 24 EU/EEA countries had diagnostic tests available by 29 January 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-20
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32047895&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Consistent detection of 2019 novel coronavirus in saliva.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Saliva is a promising non-invasive specimen for diagnosis, monitoring, and infection control in patients with 2019-nCoV infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32048163&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical and biochemical indexes from 2019-nCoV infected patients linked to viral loads and lung injury.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Our results suggest a number of potential diagnosis biomarkers and angiotensin receptor blocker (ARB) drugs for potential repurposing treatment of 2019-nCoV infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32051072&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32051072&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
During the epidemic of 2019-nCoV, the emergency response plan for the NICU should be based on the actual situation, including diagnosis, isolation, and treatment, as well as available equipment and staffing, and take into account the psychosocial needs of the families and neonatal care staff.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32051073&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Recommendation for the diagnosis and treatment of novel coronavirus infection in children in Hubei (Trial version 1)].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In order to further standardize and enhance the clinical management of 2019-nCoV infection in children, reduce the incidence, and decrease the number of severe cases, we have formulated this diagnosis and treatment recommendation according to the recent information at home and abroad.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32051074&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32051074&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Under the unified arrangement of the Xiangya Hospital of Central South University, the Department of Pediatrics has formulated an action plan with Xiangya unique model to prevent and control NCP among children according to the current epidemic situation and diagnostic and therapeutic program in China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32053470&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Time Course of Lung Changes On Chest CT During Recovery From 2019 Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19) Pneumonia.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Purpose To determine the change in chest CT findings associated with COVID-19 pneumonia from initial diagnosis until patient recovery.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32057211&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32057211&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Strategies for prevention and control of NCP include improving epidemic surveillance, quarantining the source of infection, speeding up the diagnosis of suspected cases, optimizing the management of close contacts, tightening prevention and control of cluster outbreaks and hospital infection, preventing possible rebound of the epidemic after people return to work from the Chinese Spring Festival holiday, and strengthening community prevention and control.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32062875&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Retracted: Clinical and epidemiological characteristics of 34 children with 2019 novel coronavirus infection in Shenzhen].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Chest CT scanning is heplful for early diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32065057&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Molecular and serological investigation of 2019-nCoV infected patients: implication of multiple shedding routes.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It was believed that 2019-nCoV was transmitted through respiratory tract and then induced pneumonia, thus molecular diagnosis based on oral swabs was used for confirmation of this disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32066206&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32066206&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Rapid diagnosis of concomitant NCP, safe and effective transportation, implementation of the interventional procedure, protection of vascular surgical team and postoperative management and follow-up of such patients have become urgent problems for us.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32074516&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32074516&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnostic systems for 2019-nCoV were developed with urgency.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32074550&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32074550&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The drug is recommended to be included in the next version of the Guidelines for the Prevention, Diagnosis, and Treatment of Pneumonia Caused by COVID-19 issued by the National Health Commission of the People’s Republic of China for treatment of COVID-19 infection in larger populations in the future.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32077115&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical characteristics of 140 patients infected with SARS-CoV-2 in Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Detailed clinical investigation of 140 hospitalized COVID-19 cases suggests eosinopenia together with lymphopenia may be a potential indicator for diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32077440&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32077440&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
For patients with lung occupying lesions, the whole process of diagnosis and treatment can not be carried out as usual due to the epidemic. […] All thoracic surgeons in China should work together to develop the proper procedures for the diagnosis and treatment in this special situation, and continuously update the recommendations based on epidemic changes and further understanding of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32077441&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32077441&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
With the spread of COVID-19, the routine clinical diagnosis and treatment for lung cancer patients has been disturbed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32077660&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Preliminary study of the relationship between novel coronavirus pneumonia and liver function damage: a multicenter study].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Clinical classification (mild, moderate, severe, and critical) was carried out according to the diagnosis and treatment program of novel coronavirus pneumonia (Trial Fifth Edition) issued by the National Health Commission.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-20
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32080994&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32080994&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Complying with overall requirements of the government and regulations on public health emergences, as well as the clinical features of diagnosis and treatment of dental illness, this paper refers to previous guidelines and studies on the infection prevention and control in dental diagnosis and treatment in China and foreign countries.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-21
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32083985&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19): A Perspective from China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Since most COVID-19 infected patients were diagnosed with pneumonia and characteristic CT imaging patterns, radiological examinations have become vital in early diagnosis and assessment of disease course. […] To date, CT findings have been recommended as major evidence for clinical diagnosis of COVID-19 in Hubei, China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-21
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32084676&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32084676&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Referring to the “Diagnosis and Treatment Scheme for NCP (Trial Version 4 and 5)” and combining the actual practice situation in our hospital with the “Summary of New Coronavirus Files of Shanghai Renji Hospital”, we summarize how to carry out the clinical practice of colorectal surgery under the situation of the prevention and control of the NCP epidemiology, meanwhile under such situation aiming the procedure of diagnose and treatment for emergency patients with colorectal tumor, we share the experiences of the diagnosis of colorectal tumor, the management of patients with colorectal cancer who are scheduled to be admitted for surgery, the protection of wards, the perioperative management. […] The main points are as follows: (1) Multidisciplinary team (MDT) must be run through the diagnosis and treatment of colorectal cancer.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32086886&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32086886&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The outbreak of the novel coronavirus has affected the normal diagnosis and treatment services in oral medical institutions across the country.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32086938&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The SARS, MERS and novel coronavirus (COVID-19) epidemics, the newest and biggest global health threats: what lessons have we learned?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Utilizing the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC, USA) website, and a comprehensive review of PubMed literature, we obtained information regarding clinical signs and symptoms, treatment and diagnosis, transmission methods, protection methods and risk factors for Middle East Respiratory Syndrome (MERS), Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS) and COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32087623&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Comparison of the clinical characteristics between RNA positive and negative patients clinically diagnosed with 2019 novel coronavirus pneumonia].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To raise awareness about 2019 novel coronavirus pneumonia (NCP) and reduce missed diagnosis rate and misdiagnosis rate by comparing the clinical characteristics between RNA positive and negative patients clinically diagnosed with NCP. &lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; From January 2020 to February 2020, 54 patients who were newly diagnosed with NCP in Wuhan Fourth Hospital were included in this study. […] Therefore, we should improve the understanding of NCP to prevent missed diagnosis and misdiagnosis; In addition, more rapid and accurate NCP diagnostic approaches should be further developed. &lt;b&gt;目的：&lt;/b&gt; 比较临床诊断新型冠状病毒肺炎（novel coronavirus pneumonia，NCP）核酸检测阳性与阴性患者临床特征的差异，以提高对NCP的认识，降低漏诊及误诊率。
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32088679&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;2019-nCoV (Wuhan virus), a novel Coronavirus: human-to-human transmission, travel-related cases, and vaccine readiness.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnostic PCR protocols can be found at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.who.int/health-topics/coronavirus/laboratory-diagnostics-for-novel-coronavirus&#34; class=&#34;uri&#34;&gt;https://www.who.int/health-topics/coronavirus/laboratory-diagnostics-for-novel-coronavirus&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32088847&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;18&lt;/sup&gt;F-FDG PET/CT findings of COVID-19: a series of four highly suspected cases.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A retrospective review of the patients’ medical history, clinical and laboratory data, as well as imaging findings strongly suggested a diagnosis of COVID-19. […] Although &lt;sup&gt;18&lt;/sup&gt;F-FDG PET/CT cannot be routinely used in an emergency setting and is generally not recommended for infectious diseases, our pilot data shed light on the potential clinical utility of this imaging technique in the differential diagnosis of complex cases.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32091414&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Chest CT Findings in Patients With Coronavirus Disease 2019 and Its Relationship With Clinical Features.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Computed tomography plays an important role in the diagnosis and evaluation of this emerging global health emergency.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32096367&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Management of corona virus disease-19 (COVID-19): the Zhejiang experience].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
However, since COVID-19 was a newly emerging disease, more work was warranted to improve strategies of prevention, diagnosis and treatment for COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32096395&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[The treatment proposal for the patients with breast diseases in the central epidemic area of 2019 coronavirus disease].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In the central epidemic area of COVID-19, Hubei province, especially Wuhan, the clinical specialists of breast diseases should consider all of the following factors comprehensively: the prevention of COVID-19, the diagnosis and treatment of breast diseases and the accessibility of medical resources.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-25
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32096396&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32096396&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After the outbreak of this disease, the overwhelming majority of cities have launched the “first level response” and the regular diagnosis and treatment of cancer patients are greatly affected. […] The epidemic of novel coronavirus pneumonia poses new challenges to diagnosis and treatment of the patients with digestive system malignancies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-25
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32098019&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32098019&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Third, ascertainment bias and risk of death among all those infected would be smaller when estimated using shorter virus detection windows and less sensitive diagnostic laboratory tests.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-20
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32098302&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32098302&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The collaborative efforts of researchers are needed to fill the knowledge gaps about this new virus, to develop the proper diagnostic tools, and effective treatment to combat this infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32098422&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Systematic Comparison of Two Animal-to-Human Transmitted Human Coronaviruses: SARS-CoV-2 and SARS-CoV.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The goal of this work is to systematically review and compare between SARS-CoV and SARS-CoV-2 in the context of their virus incubation, originations, diagnosis and treatment methods, genomic and proteomic sequences, and pathogenic mechanisms.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32098466&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[What are the highlights of Diagnosis and treatment of Disease 2019 novel coronavirus infection suitable for Military support Hubei medical team].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
According to &amp;quot; the Diagnosis and Treatment of New Coronavirus Pneumonia &amp;quot;(6th edition) of the National Health Commission of the People’s Republic of China, a new guideline for the diagnosis and treatment of 2019 novel coronavirus infection suitable for the military (first trial version) was established. […] Some unique opinions and suggestions are put forward in terms of disease name, diagnosis criteria, antiviral treatment, glucocorticoid application, etc. […] This article will make a proper interpretation in order to understand the guideline better and help guide the diagnosis and treatment of diseases.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32099934&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32099934&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Due to significant variations in the control strategies, which have been changing over time, and thanks to the introduction of detection technologies that have been rapidly improved, enabling to shorten the time from infection/symptoms onset to diagnosis, leading to faster confirmation of the new coronavirus cases, our previous estimations on the transmission risk of the 2019-nCoV need to be revised.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32100980&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32100980&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Fever patients during chemotherapy need to receive differential diagnosis and screening according to national standards.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32101510&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Correlation of Chest CT and RT-PCR Testing in Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) in China: A Report of 1014 Cases.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Background Chest CT is used for diagnosis of 2019 novel coronavirus disease (COVID-19), as an important complement to the reverse-transcription polymerase chain reaction (RT-PCR) tests. […] Purpose To investigate the diagnostic value and consistency of chest CT as compared with comparison to RT-PCR assay in COVID-19. […] Conclusion Chest CT has a high sensitivity for diagnosis of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32104917&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Development and clinical application of a rapid IgM-IgG combined antibody test for SARS-CoV-2 infection diagnosis.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Although the virus (severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus [SARS-Cov-2]) nucleic acid real-time polymerase chain reaction (PCR) test has become the standard method for diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 infection, these real-time PCR test kits have many limitations. […] In addition, we evaluated clinical diagnosis results obtained from different types of venous and fingerstick blood samples.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32105637&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Radiological findings from 81 patients with COVID-19 pneumonia in Wuhan, China: a descriptive study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Combining assessment of imaging features with clinical and laboratory findings could facilitate early diagnosis of COVID-19 pneumonia.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32107577&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Imaging and clinical features of patients with 2019 novel coronavirus SARS-CoV-2.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Chest CT examination plays an important role in the initial diagnosis of the novel coronavirus pneumonia.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32108459&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32108459&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In addition to supporting the frontline actively, medical workers in general surgery spare no efforts in making good diagnosis and treatment of specialized diseases by optimizing treatment process, providing medical advice online, mastering indications of delayed operation and emergency operation reasonably, etc.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32108460&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32108460&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
During the epidemic period, the routine diagnosis and treatment of tumor patients was affected with varying degrees. […] In this special period, we performed the superiority of the multi-disciplinary team of diagnosis and treatment, achieved accurate diagnosis and treatment of patients with hepatobiliary malignant tumors, provided support for these patients with limited medical resources, and helped them to survive during the epidemic period.On the basis of fully understanding the new coronavirus pneumonia, the treatment strategy should be changed timely during the epidemic, and more appropriate treatment methods should be adopted to minimize the adverse effect of the epidemic on tumor treatment.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32109443&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical and computed tomographic imaging features of novel coronavirus pneumonia caused by SARS-CoV-2.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
CT scanning provides important bases for early diagnosis and treatment of NCP.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32111114&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32111114&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
According to &lt;i&gt;the guidelines on the diagnosis and treatment of COVID-19 (6(th) trial edition)&lt;/i&gt;, the latest relative literature at home and abroad, the features of the COVID-19, recommendations for the COVID-19 prevention and control issued by the National Health Commission of China, and management experience of diagnosis and treatment in the related disciplines, we put forward recommendations for the medical practices of burn treatment during the outbreak of the COVID-19 in outpatient and emergency treatment, inpatient treatment, operation and ward management, etc.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32111449&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32111449&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The reported cases highlight non-specific clinical presentations of 2019 novel coronavirus disease (COVID-19) as well as the importance of rapid laboratory-based diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32112549&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32112549&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Since the outbreak of novel coronavirus pneumonia in December 2019, the diagnosis and treatment of patients with cancer have been facing great challenges. […] Although oncologists are not fighting on the front line to against the epidemic, during this special period, we should not only protect patients, their families and medical staff from the infection of novel Coronavirus, but also minimize the impact of the epidemic on the diagnosis and the treatment of patients with cancer. […] Combining the guidelines for diagnosis and treatment of tumors with our clinical experience, in this epidemic period, we discuss the strategies for diagnosis, treatment, and follow-up of malignant tumors of the digestive system in this article.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32112886&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Characteristics of COVID-19 infection in Beijing.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The information on demographic, epidemiological, clinical, laboratory test for the COVID-19 virus, diagnostic classification, cluster case and outcome were obtained.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32114193&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Comparison of different samples for 2019 novel coronavirus detection by nucleic acid amplification tests.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It might be better to make a diagnosis combining the computed tomography scans and nucleic acid detection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32116147&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus disinfection in histopathology.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It is feasible that potentially infectious samples may be received in histopathology laboratories for diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32118389&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Clinical analysis of 31 cases of 2019 novel coronavirus infection in children from six provinces (autonomous region) of northern China].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Close contact history of epidemiology, nucleic acid detection and chest imaging are important bases for diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32118394&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32118394&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The diagnosis and treatment of lung cancer patients have been challenged greatly because of extraordinary public health measures since the lung cancer patients are a high-risk population during the COVID-19 outbreak period.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32124995&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Fecal specimen diagnosis 2019 novel coronavirus-infected pneumonia.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
These results may help to understand the clinical diagnosis and the changes in clinical parameters of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-12
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32125126&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Management and clinical thinking of Coronavirus Disease 2019].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
How to make early diagnosis?
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32127123&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32127123&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Since the symptoms are similar to other respiratory infections, differential diagnosis in travellers arriving from countries with wide-spread COVID-19 must include other more common infections such as influenza and other respiratory tract diseases.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32130038&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19): Role of Chest CT in Diagnosis and Management.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;OBJECTIVE.&lt;/b&gt; The objective of our study was to determine the misdiagnosis rate of radiologists for coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) and evaluate the performance of chest CT in the diagnosis and management of COVID-19. […] The CT features of COVID-19 are reported and compared with the CT features of other viruses to familiarize radiologists with possible CT patterns. &lt;b&gt;MATERIALS AND METHODS.&lt;/b&gt; This study included the first 51 patients with a diagnosis of COVID-19 infection confirmed by nucleic acid testing (23 women and 28 men; age range, 26-83 years) and two patients with adenovirus (one woman and one man; ages, 58 and 66 years). […] There are differences as well as similarities in the CT features of COVID-19 compared with those of the severe acute respiratory syndrome. &lt;b&gt;CONCLUSION.&lt;/b&gt; We found that chest CT had a low rate of missed diagnosis of COVID-19 (3.9%, 2/51) and may be useful as a standard method for the rapid diagnosis of COVID-19 to optimize the management of patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32131908&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Escalating infection control response to the rapidly evolving epidemiology of the coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) due to SARS-CoV-2 in Hong Kong.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A bundled approach of active and enhanced laboratory surveillance, early airborne infection isolation, rapid molecular diagnostic testing, and contact tracing for healthcare workers (HCWs) with unprotected exposure in the hospitals was implemented.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32132196&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Improved molecular diagnosis of COVID-19 by the novel, highly sensitive and specific COVID-19-RdRp/Hel real-time reverse transcription-polymerase chain reaction assay validated &lt;i&gt;in vitro&lt;/i&gt; and with clinical specimens.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The highly sensitive and specific COVID-19-RdRp/Hel assay may help to improve the laboratory diagnosis of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32133833&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32133833&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To investigate the principles of differential diagnosis of pulmonary infiltrates in cancer patients during the outbreak of novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) by analyzing one case of lymphoma who presented pulmonary ground-glass opacities (GGO) after courses of chemotherapy. &lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; Baseline demographics and clinicopathological data of eligible patients were retrieved from medical records.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32134116&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Unique epidemiological and clinical features of the emerging 2019 novel coronavirus pneumonia (COVID-19) implicate special control measures.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We summarize latest literatures on genetic, epidemiological, and clinical features of COVID-19 in comparison to SARS and MERS and emphasize special measures on diagnosis and potential interventions.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-31
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32138488&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The 2019 Novel Coronavirus Outbreak - A Global Threat.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis is confirmed with PCR based testing of appropriate respiratory samples. […] Standard infection control and prevention techniques should be followed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32141619&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The transmission and diagnosis of 2019 novel coronavirus infection disease (COVID-19): A Chinese perspective.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The Chinese government has taken emergency measures to control the outbreak and has undertaken initial steps in the diagnosis and treatment of 2019 novel coronavirus infection disease (COVID-19). […] Our research presents selected available cases of COVID-19 in China to better understand the transmission and diagnosis regarding this infectious disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-12
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32145185&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Middle East respiratory syndrome.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This Seminar provides an update on the current knowledge and perspectives on MERS epidemiology, virology, mode of transmission, pathogenesis, diagnosis, clinical features, management, infection control, development of new therapeutics and vaccines, and highlights unanswered questions and priorities for research, improved management, and prevention.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32147731&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnosis and Management of First Case of COVID-19 in Canada: Lessons applied from SARS.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We report diagnosis and management of the first laboratory-confirmed case of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) hospitalized in Toronto, Canada.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32153167&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[The differential diagnosis for novel coronavirus pneumonia and similar lung diseases in general hospitals].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The National Health Commission, PRC has revised the consensus on diagnosis and treatment seven times in a short period of time, indicating the growing understanding of the disease. […] The diagnosis and differential diagnosis of novel coronavirus pneumonia was facing challenges not only because of large number of tourists increasing dramatically after the relieving of epidemic, but also patients with other diseases return from different areas to search for medical care. […] We were trying to find the similarities and differences among them, and to identify clues to the diagnosis of novel coronavirus pneumonia, so as to ensure accurate diagnosis and treatment.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32155789&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32155789&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The data will be used for future reference. &lt;i&gt;Methods:&lt;/i&gt; From 31 January to 2 February 2020, we conducted an online survey using snowball sampling techniques.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32156330&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32156330&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The need for timely establishment of diagnostic assays arose when Germany was confronted with the first travel-associated outbreak of severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) in Europe.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32156607&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Positive rate of RT-PCR detection of SARS-CoV-2 infection in 4880 cases from one hospital in Wuhan, China, from Jan to Feb 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The RT-PCR detection of viral nucleic acid test (NAT) was one of the most quickly established laboratory diagnosis method in a novel viral pandemic, just as in this COVID-19 outbreak. 4880 cases that had respiratory infection symptoms or close contact with COVID-19 patients in hospital in Wuhan, China, were tested for SARS-CoV-2 infection by use of quantitative RT-PCR (qRT-PCR) on samples from the respiratory tract.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32157849&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Construction and evaluation of a novel diagnosis process for 2019-Corona Virus Disease].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To construct and evaluate a diagnosis process for 2019-Corona Virus Disease (COVID-19). &lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; A continuous cohort of adults and adolescent (≥12 years) who screened COVID-19 was included in Xiangya Hospital of Central South University from January 23 to February 3, 2020 in which cases were divided the test library and the verification library. […] The accuracy of CT to make a definite diagnosis was higher than that of epidemiological history, fever, and blood lymph count decline (0.809 vs 0.660, 0.532, 0.596, &lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;=0.001, 0.002, 0.003, respectively). […] The CT-COVID-19 would have reduced the missed diagnosis rate caused by false negative of nucleic acid test (31 vs 64, difference rate 51.6%), the positive rate of nucleic acid test was 64.5% (20/31).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32157862&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CT Manifestations of Novel Coronavirus Pneumonia: A Case Report&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Then, chest computed tomography was performed and showed bilateral multifocal ground glass opacities with consolidation which suggested viral pneumonia as a differential diagnosis, and the subsequent 2019-novel coronavirus pneumonia nucleic acid test was positive.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32160149&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32160149&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A patient in the United States was given a diagnosis of infection with this virus by the state of Washington and the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on January 20, 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32161940&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Dysregulation of immune response in patients with COVID-19 in Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Surveillance of NLR and lymphocyte subsets is helpful in the early screening of critical illness, diagnosis and treatment of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32162699&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A report of clinical diagnosis and treatment of nine cases of coronavirus disease 2019.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
However, there is no unified standard for the diagnosis and treatment of COVID-19. […] In the retrospective analysis, we report nine cases of COVID-19, describe the history of contact, clinical manifestations, the course of diagnosis and clinical treatment before, during and after treatment.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32166607&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A Review of Coronavirus Disease-2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis is by demonstration of the virus in respiratory secretions by special molecular tests.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32166939&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Which sampling method for the upper respiratory tract specimen should be taken to diagnose patient with COVID-19?]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
According to the guidelines drafted by China’s Center for Disease prevention and Control (CDC), the positive nucleic acid test is need to the diagnosis of patient with COVID-19. […] Therefore, which kind of sampling methods should be chosen to help the COVID-19 diagnosis and which way is the most secure for doctors and nurses is our concern.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32167180&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The establishment of reference sequence for SARS-CoV-2 and variation analysis.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Establishment of the reference sequence for SARS-CoV-2 could benefit not only biological study of this virus but also diagnosis, clinical monitoring and intervention of SARS-CoV-2 infection in the future.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-20
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32170559&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Combination of western medicine and Chinese traditional patent medicine in treating a family case of COVID-19 in Wuhan.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This report describes the identification, diagnosis, clinical course, and management of three cases from a family, suggests the expected therapeutic effects of SHL on COVID-19, and warrants further clinical trials.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32170865&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus disease 2019: What we know?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The purpose of this review is primarily to review the pathogen, clinical features, diagnosis, and treatment of COVID-19, but also to comment briefly on the epidemiology and pathology based on the current evidence.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32171740&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;New insights on the antiviral effects of chloroquine against coronavirus: what to expect for COVID-19?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The efforts of international health authorities have since focused on rapid diagnosis and isolation of patients as well as the search for therapies able to counter the most severe effects of the disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32171872&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Arbidol combined with LPV/r versus LPV/r alone against Corona Virus Disease 2019: A retrospective cohort study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The primary endpoint was a negative conversion rate of coronavirus from the date of COVID-19 diagnosis(day7, day14), and assessed whether the pneumonia was progressing or improving by chest CT (day7). […] We analyzed 16 patients who received oral arbidol and LPV/r in the combination group and 17 who oral LPV/r only in the monotherapy group, and both initiated after diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32171948&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32171948&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The detection and diagnosis have been improved as well.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32171952&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The SARS-CoV-2 outbreak: what we know.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This paper aggregates and consolidates the epidemiology, clinical manifestations, diagnosis, treatments and preventions of this new type of coronavirus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32172228&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Potential preanalytical and analytical vulnerabilities in the laboratory diagnosis of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
As the current gold standard for the etiological diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 infection is (real time) reverse transcription polymerase chain reaction (rRT-PCR) on respiratory tract specimens, the diagnostic accuracy of this technique shall be considered a foremost prerequisite. […] Some analytical problems may also contribute to jeopardize the diagnostic accuracy, including testing outside the diagnostic window, active viral recombination, use of inadequately validated assays, insufficient harmonization, instrument malfunctioning, along with other specific technical issues. […] Some practical indications can hence be identified for minimizing the risk of diagnostic errors, encompassing the improvement of diagnostic accuracy by combining clinical evidence with results of chest computed tomography (CT) and RT-PCR, interpretation of RT-PCR results according to epidemiologic, clinical and radiological factors, recollection and testing of upper (or lower) respiratory specimens in patients with negative RT-PCR test results and high suspicion or probability of infection, dissemination of clear instructions for specimen (especially swab) collection, management and storage, together with refinement of molecular target(s) and thorough compliance with analytical procedures, including quality assurance.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32172669&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnosis and clinical management of severe acute respiratory syndrome Coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) infection: an operational recommendation of Peking Union Medical College Hospital (V2.0).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To standardize the diagnosis and treatment of this new infectious disease, an operational recommendation for the diagnosis and management of SARS-CoV-2 infection is developed by Peking Union Medical College Hospital.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32174057&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32174057&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Owing to the complications of COVID-19 pneumonia, the first symptom and imaging features of patients can be very atypical and early diagnosis of COVID-19 infections remains a challenge.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32174096&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32174096&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To explore the management strategies for patients with gynecological malignant tumors during the outbreak and transmission of COVID19. &lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; We retrospectively analyzed the clinical characteristics, treatment, and disease outcomes of three patients with gynecological malignancies associated with COVID19 in Renmin Hospital of Wuhan University in January 2020, and proposed management strategies for patients with gynecological tumors under risk of COVID19. &lt;b&gt;Results:&lt;/b&gt; Three patients were treated COVID19 based on the national diagnosis and treatment protocol as well as research progress. […] While actively preventing and controlling COVID-19, the diagnosis and treatment of gynecological malignant tumors should be carried out in an orderly and safe manner. &lt;b&gt;目的：&lt;/b&gt; 在新型冠状病毒肺炎(COVID-19)暴发和传播期间，探讨妇科恶性肿瘤患者的管理策略。
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32174267&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Era of molecular diagnosis for pathogen identification of unexplained pneumonia, lessons to be learned.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this study, we illustrated the importance of combining molecular diagnostics to rule out common pathogens and performed mNGS to obtain unbiased potential pathogen result for the diagnosis of UP.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32179660&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology of COVID-19 Among Children in China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The epidemic curves were constructed by key dates of disease onset and case diagnosis. […] Onset-to-diagnosis curves were constructed by fitting a log-normal distribution to data on both onset and diagnosis dates.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32179908&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A 55-Day-Old Female Infant infected with COVID 19: presenting with pneumonia, liver injury, and heart damage.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We report a 55-day-old case with COVID-19 confirmed in China and describe the identification, diagnosis, clinical course, and treatment of the patient, including the disease progression from day 7 to day 11 of illness.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32180140&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical features of pediatric patients with COVID-19: a report of two family cluster cases.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We should attach importance to early recognition, early diagnosis, and early treatment of infected children.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32181488&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32181488&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We evaluated the correlation of domestic air traffic to the number of confirmed COVID-19 cases and determined the growth curves of COVID-19 cases within China before and after lockdown as well as after changes in COVID-19 diagnostic criteria. […] A further increase is detected after changing diagnostic and testing methodology to 19.3 (95% CI: 15.1-26.3), respectively.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32181807&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiologic and Clinical Characteristics of 91 Hospitalized Patients with COVID-19 in Zhejiang, China: A retrospective, multi-centre case series.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The median of incubation period was 6 (IQR, 3-8) days and the median time from first visit to a doctor to confirmed diagnosis was 1 (1-2) days.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32181911&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnostic utility of clinical laboratory data determinations for patients with the severe COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The role of clinical laboratory data in the differential diagnosis of the severe forms of COVID-19 has not been definitely established.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32183901&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology, causes, clinical manifestation and diagnosis, prevention and control of coronavirus disease (COVID-19) during the early outbreak period: a scoping review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this scoping review, 65 research articles published before 31 January 2020 were analyzed and discussed to better understand the epidemiology, causes, clinical diagnosis, prevention and control of this virus. […] During this early period, published research primarily explored the epidemiology, causes, clinical manifestation and diagnosis, as well as prevention and control of the novel coronavirus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32185921&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32185921&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
If the diagnosis and treatment of malaria cases as well as the investigation and response of the epidemic foci are not carried out timely, it may endanger patients’lives and cause the possible of secondary transmission, which threatens the achievements of malaria elimination in China. […] Due to the extensive spread and high transmission ability of the COVID-19, there is a possibility of virus infections among malaria cases during the medical care-seeking behaviors and among healthcare professionals during clinical diagnosis and treatment, sample collection and testing and epidemiological surveys.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32187887&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Insight into COVID-2019 for pediatricians.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The World Health Organization confirmed this diagnosis and named the pathogen SARSCoV-2. […] From the perspective of clinical pediatricians as the first line fighting the epidemic, this paper will discuss the clinical characteristics, prevention and control measures, outcomes, diagnosis, and treatment of pediatric cases.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32189015&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32189015&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis relies on PCR using specimens from the respiratory tract.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32189175&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32189175&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Knowledge of CT characteristics of COVID-19 pneumonia might be helpful to the early diagnosis and treatment of patients, and to control the spread of infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32190290&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32190290&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here we highlight nine most important research questions concerning virus transmission, asymptomatic and presymptomatic virus shedding, diagnosis, treatment, vaccine development, origin of virus and viral pathogenesis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32191587&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Temporal Changes of CT Findings in 90 Patients with COVID-19 Pneumonia: A Longitudinal Study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Background CT may play a central role in the diagnosis and management of COVID-19 pneumonia.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32191588&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32191588&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnostic performance was assessed by the area under the receiver operating characteristic curve (AUC), sensitivity and specificity.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32191623&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The critical role of laboratory medicine during coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) and other viral outbreaks.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Despite there being evidence that laboratory tests are vital throughout many clinical pathways, there are at least three major areas where in vitro diagnostics can also provide essential contributions to diagnostic reasoning and managed care of patients with suspected or confirmed SARS-CoV-2 infection. […] These include etiological diagnosis, patient monitoring, as well as epidemiologic surveillance.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32191813&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32191813&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The World Health Organization recommends a combination of measures: rapid diagnosis and immediate isolation of cases, rigorous tracking and precautionary self-isolation of close contacts.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-25
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32192296&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32192296&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Although colorectal surgery is not a front-line subject in the fight against the epidemic, but in this special situation, it is a difficult task to provide the highest quality medical services and ensure the orderly clinical work, on the premise of maximizing the protection for patients and their families, health of medical staff, and the safety of wards and hospitals, We summarize how to carry out the clinical practice of colorectal surgery under the situation of the prevention and control of the COVID-19 epidemiology, including the procedures of diagnose and treatment for emergency patients with colorectal tumor, and share the experiences of the diagnosis of colorectal tumor, the management of patients with colorectal cancer who are scheduled to be admitted for surgery, the protection of wards, the perioperative management. […] The main points are as follows: (1) Multidisciplinary team (MDT) must be run through the diagnosis and treatment of colorectal cancer.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32192297&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Chemotherapy strategy for colorectal cancer under the outbreak of corona virus disease 2019].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Fever patients during chemotherapy need to receive differential diagnosis and screening according to national standards.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32193037&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CT manifestations of coronavirus disease-2019: A retrospective analysis of 73 cases by disease severity.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We analyzed the initial and follow-up CT features of patients with disease severity, according to the Guidelines for the Diagnosis and Treatment of New Coronavirus Pneumonia.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32193638&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32193638&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In diagnosis, chest computed tomography (CT) manifestations can supplement parts of limitations of real-time reverse transcription polymerase chain reaction (RT-PCR) assay. […] Based on a comprehensive literature review and the experience in the frontline, we aim to review the typical and relatively atypical CT manifestations with representative COVID-19 cases at our hospital, and hope to strengthen the recognition of these features with radiologists and help them make a quick and accurate diagnosis.Key Points • Ground glass opacities, consolidation, reticular pattern, and crazy paving pattern are typical CT manifestations of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32195698&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Infection: Implications for Perioperative and Critical Care Physicians.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here, the authors review COVID-19 pathogenesis, presentation, diagnosis, and potential therapeutics, with a focus on management of COVID-19-associated respiratory failure.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32196032&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32196032&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Identifying antibodies (Abs) that neutralize infectious agents is the first step for developing therapeutics, vaccines, and diagnostic tools for these infectious agents.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-20
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32196430&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Laboratory diagnosis of emerging human coronavirus infections - the state of the art.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The three unprecedented outbreaks of emerging human coronavirus (HCoV) infections at the beginning of the twenty-first century have highlighted the necessity for readily available, accurate and fast diagnostic testing methods. […] The laboratory diagnostic methods for human coronavirus infections have evolved substantially, with the development of novel assays as well as the availability of updated tests for emerging ones. […] Several integrated, random-access, point-of-care molecular devices are currently under development for fast and accurate diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 infections.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32196678&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Eleven faces of coronavirus disease 2019.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Laboratory detection of the viral nucleic acid can yield false-negative results, and serological testing of virus-specific IgG and IgM antibodies should be used as an alternative for diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32198191&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32198191&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It includes a description of hazard group 3 organisms, the category to which SARS-CoV-2 has been assigned, a brief description of what is currently known about the pathological and autopsy findings in COVID-19, a summary of the recommendations for conducting autopsies in suspected COVID-19 cases and the techniques for making the diagnosis at autopsy.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32198501&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Profiling Early Humoral Response to Diagnose Novel Coronavirus Disease (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The diagnostic value of IgM was evaluated in this cohort. […] Humoral response to SARS-CoV-2 can aid to the diagnosis of COVID-19, including subclinical cases.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-21
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32198915&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[When COVID-19 encounters interstitial lung disease: challenges and management].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Clinicians need to comprehensively analyze the epidemic history, disease onset characteristics, clinical manifestations, image characteristics, serological andpathogenic microorganism test results to confirm diagnosis. […] Because of this, the article will discuss the issues related to the differential diagnosis and management of COVID-19 and ILD, and try to provide reasonable suggestions.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-21
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32198986&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Review and Prospect of Pathological Features of Corona Virus Disease.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
But so far, the pathological diagnosis of COVID-19 has been relatively deficient： it is still confined to the pathological findings of punctured organs, and the majority of medical workers have poor awareness of its pathological characteristics.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32201353&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A review of the 2019 Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19) based on current evidence.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Based on the current published evidence, we systematically summarizes the epidemiology, clinical characteristics, diagnosis, treatment and prevention of knowledge surrounding COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32202343&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Systematic review of COVID-19 in children shows milder cases and a better prognosis than adults.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnostic findings have been similar to adults, with fever and respiratory symptoms being prevalent, but fewer children seem to have developed severe pneumonia.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32202646&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32202646&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Frontline health care workers engaged in direct diagnosis, treatment, and care of patients with COVID-19 were associated with a higher risk of symptoms of depression (OR, 1.52; 95% CI, 1.11-2.09; P = .01), anxiety (OR, 1.57; 95% CI, 1.22-2.02; P &amp;lt; .001), insomnia (OR, 2.97; 95% CI, 1.92-4.60; P &amp;lt; .001), and distress (OR, 1.60; 95% CI, 1.25-2.04; P &amp;lt; .001). […] In this survey of heath care workers in hospitals equipped with fever clinics or wards for patients with COVID-19 in Wuhan and other regions in China, participants reported experiencing psychological burden, especially nurses, women, those in Wuhan, and frontline health care workers directly engaged in the diagnosis, treatment, and care for patients with COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32202911&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32202911&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Gastrointestinal (GI) endoscopy is a high-risk diagnostic-therapeutic procedure in the case of upper GI examinations, and a moderate to low-risk intervention when involving lower GI explorations.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32204750&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32204750&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
With the spread of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) and growing knowledge of its diagnosis and treatment, it has been clear that children are also susceptible to severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32204756&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Clinical features and chest CT findings of coronavirus disease 2019 in infants and young children].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Infants and young children with COVID-19 tend to have mild clinical symptoms and imaging findings not as typical as those of adults, and therefore, the diagnosis of COVID-19 should be made based on imaging findings along with epidemiological history and nucleic acid detection. […] Chest CT has guiding significance for the early diagnosis of asymptomatic children.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32204757&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Twin girls infected with SARS-CoV-2].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This article reports the diagnosis and treatment of twin girls who were diagnosed with severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) infection in Hunan Province, China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32205090&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32205090&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This ward houses patients exhibiting atypical manifestations or awaiting definitive diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32205269&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Rapid viral diagnosis and ambulatory management of suspected COVID-19 cases presenting at the infectious diseases referral hospital in Marseille, France, - January 31st to March 1st, 2020: A respiratory virus snapshot.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Rapid virological diagnosis is needed to limit the length of isolation for suspected COVID-19 cases. […] We managed the first 280 patients suspected to have COVID-19 through a rapid care circuit and virological diagnosis in our infectious disease reference hospital in Marseille, France.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32207068&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32207068&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There is still an urgent need to accelerate protocols that lead to the implementation of rapid point-of-care diagnostic testing and effective antiviral therapies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32207542&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32207542&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Mobilize research platforms for patient needs: Leverage our relationships with participants and rapidly deploy novel clinical engagement techniques such as digital tools to intervene remotely and reduce the negative effects of social isolation on our participants.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32207591&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[CT imaging features of patients with different clinical types of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19)].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A total of 67 patients diagnosed as COVID-19 by nucleic acid testing were included and divided into 4 groups according to the clinical staging based on &lt;i&gt;Diagnosis and treatment of novel coronavirus pneumonia (Trial version 6)&lt;/i&gt;.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32211920&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32211920&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis relies on PCR using specimens from the respiratory tract.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32211963&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus disease 2019: initial chest CT findings.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
If these typical alterations are found, then the differential diagnosis of coronavirus disease 2019 must be considered.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32213269&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Analysis on cluster cases of COVID-19 in Tianjin].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The interval from onset to diagnosis for the first case was longer than those of other cases in the familial clusters (Z=-2.406, &lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;= 0.016). […] The intervals from onset to diagnosis were significant different among the family, working place and public place clusters (&lt;i&gt;H&lt;/i&gt;=8.843, , &lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;=0.012) , and there were also significant differences in onset time among the secondary cases (&lt;i&gt;H&lt;/i&gt;=16.607, &lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;=0.000) . &lt;b&gt;Conclusions:&lt;/b&gt; In the surveillance of COVID-19 epidemic, special attention should be paid to the cases from same family, same work place, or other places where clustering are prone to occur, and the epidemiological investigation should be carried out timely to confirm the cluster.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32213270&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Epidemiological analysis on 1 052 cases of COVID-19 in epidemic clusters].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The median of onset- diagnosis interval of the initial cases was 6 (3-9) days, and the median of onset-diagnosis interval of the secondary cases was 5 (3-8) days. &lt;b&gt;Conclusions:&lt;/b&gt; Epidemic clusters of COVID-19 were common in many cities outside Wuhan and Hubei. […] After 4 February, the epidemic clusters were mainly caused by the first generation or second generation cases in local areas, and the time for diagnosis became shorter. &lt;b&gt;目的：&lt;/b&gt; 了解新型冠状病毒肺炎聚集性病例的流行病学特征，探讨家庭因素以及集体活动等对本病传播的影响。
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32213337&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Temporal profiles of viral load in posterior oropharyngeal saliva samples and serum antibody responses during infection by SARS-CoV-2: an observational cohort study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Serological assay can complement RT-qPCR for diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32215691&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CT image visual quantitative evaluation and clinical classification of coronavirus disease (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
ROC was used to test the diagnosis ability of TSS for severe-critical type.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32216961&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Imaging manifestations and diagnostic value of chest CT of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) in the Xiaogan area.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Spiral CT is a sensitive examination method, which can be applied to make an early diagnosis and for evaluation of progression, with a diagnostic sensitivity and accuracy better than that of nucleic acid detection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32217113&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32217113&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here we present a review of COVID-19 in pregnancy, bringing together the various factors integral to the understanding of pathophysiology and susceptibility, diagnostic challenges with real-time reverse transcriptase polymerase chain reaction (RT-PCR) assays, therapeutic controversies, intrauterine transmission and maternal-fetal complications.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32217506&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32217506&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
However, some countries remain ill-equipped, have poor diagnostic capacity, and are in need of further capacity development in response to public health threats.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32217556&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32217556&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Among a cohort of 799 patients, 113 who died and 161 who recovered with a diagnosis of covid-19 were analysed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32219006&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32219006&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The confirmation rate of Wuhan estimated by our model is 0.0643, substantially lower than that of Hubei excluding Wuhan (0.1914), and that of China excluding Hubei (0.2189), but it jumps to 0.3229 after February 12 when clinical evidence was adopted in new diagnosis guidelines.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-31
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32219626&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32219626&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Based on the New Diagnosis and Treatment Scheme for Novel Coronavirus Infected Pneumonia (Trial Edition 5), combined with our current clinical treatment experience, we recently proposed a revision of the first edition of “Guidance for maternal and fetal management during pneumonia epidemics of novel coronavirus infection in the Wuhan Tongji Hospital”. […] This article focused on the issues of greatest concern of pregnant women including severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) infection diagnostic criteria, inspection precautions, drug treatment options, indications and methods of termination of pregnancy, postpartum fever, breastfeeding considerations, mode of mother-to-child transmission, neonatal isolation and advice on neonatal nursing, to provide valuable experience for better management of SARS-CoV-2 infection in pregnant women and newborns.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32219814&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32219814&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In view of the seriousness of the COVID-19 epidemic, a series of prevention and control measures adopted by the government have restricted the follow-up, diagnosis and treatment of patients by the hospitals, which has a great impact on their mental and physical health.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32219885&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Stability issues of RT-PCR testing of SARS-CoV-2 for hospitalized patients clinically diagnosed with COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We also found that the RT-PCR results from several tests at different points were variable from the same patients during the course of diagnosis and treatment of these patients. […] Our results indicate that in addition to the emphasis on RT-PCR testing, clinical indicators such as computed tomography images should also be used not only for diagnosis and treatment but also for isolation, recovery/discharge, and transferring for hospitalized patients clinically diagnosed with COVID-19 during the current epidemic. […] These results suggested the urgent needs for the standard of procedures of sampling from different anatomic sites, sample transportation, optimization of RT-PCR, serology diagnosis/screening for SARS-CoV-2 infection, and distinct diagnosis from other respiratory diseases such as fluenza infections as well.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32220177&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Epidemiology, Treatment, and Epidemic Prevention and Control of the Coronavirus Disease 2019: a Review].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Meanwhile, rapid detection kit for serological monitoring of the virus in general population is expected so as to achieve early detection, early diagnosis, early isolation and early treatment.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32220181&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Clinical Study and CT Findings of a Familial Cluster of Pneumonia with Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19)].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The epidemiological and clinical features could provide quicker diagnosis and better management for the COVID-19 infected patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32221117&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32221117&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 can complicate the perioperative course with diagnostic challenge and a high potential fatality rate.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32221519&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Antibody responses to SARS-CoV-2 in patients of novel coronavirus disease 2019.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Combining RNA and antibody detections significantly improved the sensitivity of pathogenic diagnosis for COVID-19 (p&amp;lt;0.001), even in early phase of 1-week since onset (p=0.007). […] The findings provide strong empirical support for the routine application of serological testing in the diagnosis and management of COVID-19 patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32221523&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Quantitative Detection and Viral Load Analysis of SARS-CoV-2 in Infected Patients.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The widely used reverse transcription PCR (RT-PCR) method has limitations for clinical diagnosis and treatment.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32222119&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical analysis of pregnant women with 2019 novel coronavirus pneumonia.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Therefore, the protective measures are necessary on admission; the instant CT scan and real-time reverse-transcriptase polymerase-chain-reaction assay should be helpful in early diagnosis and avoid cross-infection on the occasion that patients have fever and other respiratory signs.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32222720&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32222720&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Practical work experience in our spinal outpatient and emergency department during the COVID-19 pandemic is summarized in this article, with combined evidence-based medical evidence to explore a standardized process of diagnosis and treatment for spinal diseases.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32222812&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32222812&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The topics were: (1) infection control, (2) laboratory diagnosis and specimens, (3) hemodynamic support, (4) ventilatory support, and (5) COVID-19 therapy.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32222988&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Review article: gastrointestinal features in COVID-19 and the possibility of faecal transmission.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diarrhoea was the most common gastrointestinal symptom in children and adults, with a mean duration of 4.1 ± 2.5 days, and was observed before and after diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32222992&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Detectable SARS-CoV-2 viral RNA in feces of three children during recovery period of COVID-19 pneumonia.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
All of these three cases experienced mild illness and recovered soon after the treatment, with the nucleic acid of throat swab turning negative within 14, 11, and 7 days after diagnosis, respectively.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32223004&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32223004&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Dermatoscope is a convenient diagnostic tool used by dermatologists in the diagnosis of skin, hair and nail disorders.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32223179&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnosing COVID-19: The Disease and Tools for Detection.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The aim of this review article is to inform the audience of diagnostic and surveillance technologies for SARS-CoV-2 and their performance characteristics.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32223665&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Timely Diagnosis and Treatment Shortens the Time to Resolution of Coronavirus Disease (COVID-19) Pneumonia and Lowers the Highest and Last CT Scores From Sequential Chest CT.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;OBJECTIVE.&lt;/b&gt; This study aims to assess correlations of the time from symptom onset to diagnosis and treatment with the time to disease resolution and CT scores as based on findings from sequential chest CT examinations. &lt;b&gt;MATERIALS AND METHODS.&lt;/b&gt; Thirty patients with coronavirus disease (COVID-19) confirmed by reverse transcription-polymerase chain reaction analysis underwent chest CT examinations. […] The time from symptom onset to diagnosis and treatment was recorded for each patient, and on the basis of this information, patients with COVID-19 were divided into group 1 (patients for whom this interval was ≤ 3 days) and group 2 (those for whom this interval was &amp;gt; 3 days). […] The differences in age, sex, and last CT scores determined before discharge between the two groups were analyzed, and correlations of the time from symptom onset to diagnosis and treatment with the time to disease resolution as well as with the highest CT score also underwent statistical analysis. &lt;b&gt;RESULTS.&lt;/b&gt; A total of 25 subjects were enrolled in the study. […] The time from symptom onset to diagnosis and treatment had a positive correlation with the time to disease resolution (&lt;i&gt;r&lt;/i&gt; = 0.93; &lt;i&gt;p&lt;/i&gt; = 0.000) as well as with the highest CT score (&lt;i&gt;r&lt;/i&gt; = 0.83; &lt;i&gt;p&lt;/i&gt; = 0.006). &lt;b&gt;CONCLUSION.&lt;/b&gt; Timely diagnosis and treatment are key to providing a better prognosis for patients with COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-31
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32224769&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Surviving Sepsis Campaign: Guidelines on the Management of Critically Ill Adults with Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The topics were: 1) infection control, 2) laboratory diagnosis and specimens, 3) hemodynamic support, 4) ventilatory support, and 5) COVID-19 therapy.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-31
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32225135&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32225135&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Simplification of the diagnostic and staging pathway has to be prioritized in order to reduce hospital visits and consequently the risk of contagion.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-31
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32226287&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Evaluation of SARS-CoV-2 RNA shedding in clinical specimens and clinical characteristics of 10 patients with COVID-19 in Macau.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Based on our data on SARS-CoV-2 RNA shedding in stool and the possibility of a lag in viral detection in NPS specimens, the assessment of both fecal and respiratory specimen is recommended to enhance diagnostic sensitivity, and also to aid discharge decision before the role of viral RNA shedding in stool is clarified.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32226295&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19: what has been learned and to be learned about the novel coronavirus disease.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We will cover the basics about the epidemiology, etiology, virology, diagnosis, treatment, prognosis, and prevention of the disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32226962&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 in a Patient Presenting with Syncope and a Normal Chest X-ray.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Our unique case underscores the increasing diversity of COVID-19 presentations and potential for initial mis- diagnosis and delay in implementing proper precautions.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32227494&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Caution should be exercised for the detection of SARS-CoV-2, especially in the elderly.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After patient recovery, a chest CT examination, combined with SARS-CoV-2 RNA detection, confirmed diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-31
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32228809&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32228809&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
These findings might also serve as a practical reference for clinical diagnosis and medical treatment.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32229107&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Dynamic change process of target genes by RT-PCR testing of SARS-Cov-2 during the course of a Coronavirus Disease 2019 patient.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We report the dynamic change process of target genes by RT-PCR testing of SARS-Cov-2 during the course of a COVID-19 patient: from successive negative results to successive single positive nucleocapsid gene, to two positive target genes (orf1ab and nucleocapsid) by RT-PCR testing of SARS-Cov-2, and describe the diagnosis, clinical course, and management of the case.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32229322&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnosis of the Coronavirus disease (COVID-19): rRT-PCR or CT?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To evaluate the diagnostic value of computed tomography (CT) and real-time reverse-transcriptase-polymerase chain reaction (rRT-PCR) for COVID-19 pneumonia. […] For patients with a final confirmed diagnosis, clinical and laboratory data, in addition to CT imaging findings were evaluated.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32229605&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Evaluation of Nucleocapsid and Spike Protein-based ELISAs for detecting antibodies against SARS-CoV-2.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Background:&lt;/b&gt; At present, PCR-based nucleic acid detection cannot meet the demands for coronavirus infectious disease (COVID-19) diagnosis.&lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; 214 confirmed COVID-19 patients who were hospitalized in the General Hospital of Central Theater Command of the People’s Liberation Army between January 18 and February 26, 2020, were recruited. […] Two Enzyme-Linked Immunosorbent Assay (ELISA) kits based on recombinant SARS-CoV-2 nucleocapsid protein (rN) and spike protein (rS) were used for detecting IgM and IgG antibodies, and their diagnostic feasibility was evaluated.&lt;b&gt;Results:&lt;/b&gt; Among the 214 patients, 146 (68.2%) and 150 (70.1%) were successfully diagnosed with the rN-based IgM and IgG ELISAs, respectively; 165 (77.1%) and 159 (74.3%) were successfully diagnosed with the rS-based IgM and IgG ELISAs, respectively. […] The positive rate of rN-based and rS-based IgM and IgG ELISAs was less than 60% during the early stage of the illness 0-10 d.p.o., and that of IgM and IgG was obviously increased after 10 d.p.o.&lt;b&gt;Conclusions:&lt;/b&gt; ELISA has a high sensitivity, especially for the detection of serum samples from patients after 10 d.p.o, it can be an important supplementary method for COVID-19 diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32229732&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Disease 19 Infection Does Not Result in Acute Kidney Injury: An Analysis of 116 Hospitalized Patients from Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
All these patients did not meet the diagnostic criteria of AKI.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32232230&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32232230&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
As one of the busiest specialised hospitals in the world, the Department of Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery of Peking University School and Hospital of Stomatology summarised the experience with disease prevention and control and clinical recommendations on the examination, diagnosis and treatment processes, clinical management, healthcare personnel protection and disinfection amid the continued spread of the pandemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32232423&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32232423&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Because of the rapid spread of this disease through respiratory droplets, health care workers who come in close contact with the upper aerodigestive tract during diagnostic and therapeutic procedures, such as otolaryngologists-head and neck surgeons, are particularly at risk.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32232433&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Characteristics of Ocular Findings of Patients With Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) in Hubei Province, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Understanding ocular manifestations of patients with COVID-19 by ophthalmologists and others may facilitate the diagnosis and prevention of transmission of the disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32232648&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnostic performance of chest CT to differentiate COVID-19 pneumonia in non-high-epidemic area in Japan.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To evaluate the diagnostic performance of chest CT to differentiate coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) pneumonia in non-high-epidemic area in Japan. […] Using a Likert scale and its receiver operating characteristic curve analysis, two radiologists (R1/R2) evaluated the diagnostic performance of the five CT criteria: (1) ground glass opacity (GGO)-predominant lesions, (2) GGO- and peripheral-predominant lesions, (3) bilateral GGO-predominant lesions; (4) bilateral GGO- and peripheral-predominant lesions, and (5) bilateral GGO- and peripheral-predominant lesions without nodules, airway abnormalities, pleural effusion, and mediastinal lymphadenopathy. […] The five CT criteria showed moderate to excellent diagnostic performance with area under the curves (AUCs) ranging 0.77-0.88 for R1 and 0.78-0.92 for R2.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32232837&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32232837&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Pre-existing primary headache diagnosis was present in about a third [46/158 (29.1%)] of respondents. […] A pre-existing primary headache diagnosis (OR = 4.20, 95% CI 1.48-15.40; P = .030) and combined PPE usage for &amp;gt;4 hours per day (OR 3.91, 95% CI 1.35-11.31; P = .012) were independently associated with de novo PPE-associated headaches. […] Since COVID-19 outbreak, 42/46 (91.3%) of respondents with pre-existing headache diagnosis either “agreed” or “strongly agreed” that the increased PPE usage had affected the control of their background headaches, which affected their level of work performance.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32233563&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Effect of delay in diagnosis on transmission of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Delay in diagnosis and limited hospital resources lead to a rapid spread of COVID-19. […] In this study, we investigate the effect of delay in diagnosis on the disease transmission with a new formulated dynamic model. […] Sensitivity analyses and numerical simulations reveal that, improving the proportion of timely diagnosis and shortening the waiting time for diagnosis can not eliminate COVID-19 but can effectively decrease the basic reproduction number, significantly reduce the transmission risk, and effectively prevent the endemic of COVID-19, e.g., shorten the peak time and reduce the peak value of new confirmed cases and new infection, decrease the cumulative number of confirmed cases and total infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32233876&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Role of Emergency Radiology in COVID-19: From Preparedness to Diagnosis.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Emergency trauma radiology, although a relatively new subspecialty of radiology, plays a critical role in both the diagnosis/triage of acutely ill patients, but even more important in providing leadership and taking the lead in the preparedness of imaging departments in dealing with novel highly infectious communicable diseases and mass casualties. […] We discuss roles that community radiology clinics, outpatient radiology departments, and emergency radiology departments can play in the diagnosis of this disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32233973&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32233973&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Satisfactory outcome was observed in one mild case and one severe case of COVID-19 pneumonia after the use of the online/offline multidisciplinary quarantine observation form, online monitoring, and classified diagnosis and treatment, as well as strict compliance with quarantine measures. &lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32233980&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32233980&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Furthermore, rapid and effective stroke care remains paramount to achieve maximal functional recovery for those needing admission and to triage care appropriately for those who may be presenting with neurological symptoms but have an alternative diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32234126&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32234126&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The diagnosis of COVID-19 is based on the positive of etiological test.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32234127&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Epidemiological characteristics of COVID-19 in Gansu province].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Also, the incubation period prolonged along with the epidemic stage (&lt;i&gt;F&lt;/i&gt;=51.65, &lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;&amp;lt;0.01), but the intervals between disease onset and hospital visit (&lt;i&gt;F&lt;/i&gt;=5.32, &lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;&amp;lt;0.01), disease onset and diagnosis (&lt;i&gt;F&lt;/i&gt;=5.25, &lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;&amp;lt;0.01) became shorter along with the epidemic stage.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32234465&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Recent progress in understanding 2019 novel coronavirus (SARS-CoV-2) associated with human respiratory disease: detection, mechanisms and treatment.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To effectively implement epidemic prevention, early identification and diagnosis are critical to disease control.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32234468&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The epidemiology, diagnosis and treatment of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Early diagnosis, quarantine, and supportive treatments are essential to cure patients. […] This paper reviews the literature on all available information about the epidemiology, diagnosis, isolation and treatments of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32235517&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32235517&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Whereas diagnostic or infrastructural technology is an expensive investment with long-term payback, leapfrogging digital applications reduce contingent costs. “Digital” savings can be shared by key stakeholders with P4P schemes, incentivizing value co-creation patterns.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32237160&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiological analysis of COVID-19 and practical experience from China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Chinese medical staff have summarized a set of effective strategies and methods in the diagnosis and treatment of this disease that are worthy of reference for their international counterparts.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32237278&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Isolation and rapid sharing of the 2019 novel coronavirus (SARS-CoV-2) from the first patient diagnosed with COVID-19 in Australia.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The ability to rapidly identify, propagate, and internationally share our SARS-CoV-2 isolate is an important step in collaborative scientific efforts to deal effectively with this international public health emergency by developing better diagnostic procedures, vaccine candidates, and antiviral agents.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32237288&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Guidelines for Laboratory Diagnosis of Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) in Korea.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 is a severe acute respiratory syndrome Coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) infection, and real-time reverse transcription-PCR is currently the most reliable diagnostic method for COVID-19 around the world. […] These guidelines are based on other related domestic and international guidelines, as well as expert opinions and include the selection of test subjects, selection of specimens, diagnostic methods, interpretation of test results, and biosafety.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32238024&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A case of imported COVID-19 diagnosed by PCR-positive lower respiratory specimen but with PCR-negative throat swabs.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A lower respiratory tract specimen should be obtained for better diagnosis of corona virus disease 2019, even in the absence of respiratory symptoms for patients with significant travel or exposure history.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32238223&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Case Report: Walking Pneumonia in Novel Coronavirus Disease (COVID-19): Mild Symptoms with Marked Abnormalities on Chest Imaging.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis in this patient was facilitated by chest imaging and repeat viral testing. […] Thus, chest imaging studies might enhance capabilities for early diagnosis of COVID-19 pneumonia.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32238224&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32238224&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The Importance of Diagnostic Testing during a Viral Pandemic: Early Lessons from Novel Coronavirus Disease (COVID-19).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32238260&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32238260&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Thus leading to a delay in the diagnosis of COVID-19 infection and further spread of the virus, since in most cases of Dengue there are no warning signs and treatment is ambulatory.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32238336&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32238336&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The response strategy included early diagnosis, patient isolation, symptomatic monitoring of contacts as well as suspected and confirmed cases, and public health quarantine.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32238612&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Novel Coronavirus 2019 (2019-nCoV) Infection: Part I - Preparedness and Management in the Pediatric Intensive Care Unit in Resource-limited Settings.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis involves a combination of clinical and epidemiological features with laboratory confirmation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32238615&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Perinatal-Neonatal Management of COVID-19 Infection - Guidelines of the Federation of Obstetric and Gynecological Societies of India (FOGSI), National Neonatology Forum of India (NNF), and Indian Academy of Pediatrics (IAP).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Perinatal period poses unique challenges and care of the mother-baby dyads requires special resources for prevention of transmission, diagnosis of infection and providing clinical care during labor, resuscitation and postnatal period. […] To provide recommendations for prevention of transmission, diagnosis of infection and providing clinical care during labor, resuscitation and postnatal period. […] A set of twenty recommendations are provided under the following broad headings: 1) pregnant women with travel history, clinical suspicion or confirmed COVID-19 infection; 2) neonatal care; 3) prevention and infection control; 4) diagnosis; 5) general questions.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32238757&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Current Status of Epidemiology, Diagnosis, Therapeutics, and Vaccines for Novel Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Currently, various diagnostic kits to test for COVID-19 are available and several repurposing therapeutics for COVID-19 have shown to be clinically effective. […] Here, we review the current status of epidemiology, diagnosis, treatment, and vaccine development for COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32239472&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Proposal of a low-dose, long-pitch, dual-source chest CT protocol on third-generation dual-source CT using a tin filter for spectral shaping at 100 kVp for CoronaVirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) patients: a feasibility study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To subjectively and objectively evaluate the feasibility and diagnostic reliability of a low-dose, long-pitch dual-source chest CT protocol on third-generation dual-source CT (DSCT) with spectral shaping at 100Sn kVp for COVID-19 patients. […] Qualitative analysis demonstrated significant reduction in motion artifacts (p = 0.031) with comparable diagnostic reliability between HD-DECT and LDCT. […] Ultra-low-dose, dual-source, fast CT protocol provides highly diagnostic images for COVID-19 with potential for reduction in dose and motion artifacts.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32240285&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;First Mildly Ill, Non-Hospitalized Case of Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) Without Viral Transmission in the United States - Maricopa County, Arizona, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Contacts were persons exposed to the case on or after the day before case diagnostic specimen collection. […] Specimens collected 18 days after diagnosis tested positive. […] This report demonstrates that SARS-CoV-2 infection can cause mild illness and result in positive tests for up to 18 days after diagnosis, without evidence of transmission to close contacts.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32241244&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnostic Value and Key Features of Computed Tomography in Coronavirus Disease 2019.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To date, computed tomography (CT) findings have been recommended as major evidence for the clinical diagnosis of COVID-19 in Hubei, China. […] Since most patients with COVID-19 infection share typical imaging features, radiological examinations have an irreplaceable role in screening, diagnosis and monitoring treatment effects in clinical practice.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32241316&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Case Report on Early Diagnosis of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Early diagnosis is one of the important contents in prevention and control. […] COVID-19 patients with early mild pneumonia often lack typical evidence to make a definitive diagnosis. […] Based on the analysis of the cases of 4 patients, this article finds that early diagnosis requires a combination of epidemiology, clinical manifestations, imaging, and etiology, with particular emphasis on epidemiology history and chest CT manifestations.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32241761&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32241761&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
4 959 790 Chinese students aged 6 to 22 years with a diagnosis of any of 44 notifiable infectious diseases. […] Diagnosis of, and deaths from, 44 notifiable infectious diseases.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32242438&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Primary care management of the coronavirus (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis is made by a RT-PCR test using respiratory secretions, usually nasopharyngeal and oropharyngeal swabs.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32242947&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Imaging and clinical features of patients with 2019 novel coronavirus SARS-CoV-2: A systematic review and meta-analysis.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We aim to explore reliable evidence for the diagnosis and treatment of the COVID-19 by analyzing all the published studies by Chinese scholars on the clinical and imaging features in novel coronavirus pneumonia caused by SARS-CoV-2.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32243238&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Chest CT Features of COVID-19 in Rome, Italy.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Background The standard for diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 virus is reverse transcription polymerase chain reaction (RT-PCR) test, but chest CT may play a complimentary role in the early detection of COVID-19 pneumonia. […] Diagnostic performance of CT was calculated using RT-PCR as reference.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32243288&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32243288&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This has led the United States to declare a national emergency and a ban on all elective diagnostic and therapeutic procedures, as well as elective surgery in inpatient and outpatient settings. […] However, these facilities may be able assist acute care hospitals, as essential (urgent and emergent) surgeries and diagnostic and therapeutic procedures will still need to be performed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32243697&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32243697&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After the diagnosis of COVID-19, immunosuppressive agents were discontinued and methylprednisolone with prophylactic antibiotics were initiated, however, the lung injury progressed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32245150&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Characterization of the Humoral Immune Response to Porcine Epidemic Diarrhea Virus Infection under Experimental and Field Conditions Using an AlphaLISA Platform.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In the absence of effective vaccines, infection prevention and control through diagnostic testing and quarantine are critical. […] Early detection and differential diagnosis of PEDV infections increase the chance of successful control of the disease. […] Particularly, the bridge assay constitutes a rapid diagnostic that substantially improves upon the “time to result” metric of currently available immunoassays.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32245395&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32245395&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this Commentary, we would like to comment on the article titled “A rapid advice guideline for the diagnosis and treatment of 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infected pneumonia (standard version)” as a featured article in Military Medical Research.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32245396&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32245396&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
On 6 February 2020, our team had published a rapid advice guideline for diagnosis and treatment of 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection, and this guideline provided our experience and make well reference for fighting against this pandemic worldwide. […] However, the coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) is a new disease, our awareness and knowledge are gradually increasing based on the ongoing research findings and clinical practice experience; hence, the strategies of diagnosis and treatment are also continually updated. […] In this letter, we answered one comment on our guideline and provided the newest diagnostic criteria of “suspected case” and “confirmed case” according to the latest Diagnosis and Treatment Guidelines for COVID-19 (seventh version) that issued by the National Health Committee of the People’s Republic of China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32245835&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Laboratory Diagnosis of COVID-19 Infection: Current Issues and Challenges.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This commentary covers current issues and challenges for the laboratory diagnosis of infections caused by SARS-CoV-2. […] In the pre-analytical stage, collecting the proper respiratory tract specimen at the right time from the right anatomic site is essential for a prompt and accurate molecular diagnosis of COVID-19. […] In the analytic stage, real-time RT-PCR assays remain the molecular test of choice for the etiologic diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 infection while antibody-based techniques are being introduced as supplemental tools. […] Finally, random access, integrated devices available at the point of care with scalable capacities will facilitate the rapid and accurate diagnosis and monitoring of SARS-CoV-2 infections and greatly assist in the control of this outbreak.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32246819&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Pulmonary High-Resolution Computed Tomography (HRCT) Findings of Patients with Early-Stage Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) in Hangzhou, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Thus, suspected cases need to be closely monitored, and epidemiological history and clinical laboratory examination should also be considered during diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32246822&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Potential false-negative nucleic acid testing results for Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2 from thermal inactivation of samples with low viral loads.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Nucleic acid testing (NAT) has played an important role in patient diagnosis and management of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32246838&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32246838&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We had a dedicated task force that identified a response plan, which included: (1) establishment of dedicated, cohorted intensive care unit(s) (ICU) for COVID-19-positive patients; (2) design of appropriate procedures for pre-triage, diagnosis and isolation of suspected and confirmed cases; and (3) training of all staff to work in the dedicated ICU in personal protective equipment use and patient management.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32249943&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A comparative-descriptive analysis of clinical characteristics in 2019-Coronavirus-infected children and adults.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In summary, knowledge of these differences between children and adults will not only be helpful for the clinical diagnosis of 2019 novel coronavirus disease (COVID-19), but also for a future discussion on age-specific coronavirus infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32249944&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32249944&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The diagnosis was performed by the virology team under direction of Maria R.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32250170&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32250170&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Plant biotechnology offers potential solutions to this pandemic through the development of low-cost vaccines and antibodies useful for therapy, prophylaxis, and diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32250958&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32250958&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Using a third-party statistics tool, we anonymously monitored user activity as well as content utilization patterns since the diagnosis of the first case of SARS-CoV-2 in Switzerland on February 25, 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32251668&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Gastrointestinal Manifestations of SARS-CoV-2 Infection and Virus Load in Fecal Samples from the Hong Kong Cohort and Systematic Review and Meta-analysis.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We collected data from the cohort of patients with COVID-19 in Hong Kong (n=59; diagnosis from February 2 through Feb 29, 2020), and searched PubMed, Embase, Cochrane and three Chinese databases through March 11, 2020 according to the Preferred Reporting Items for Systematic Reviews and Meta-Analyses guidelines.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32251790&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS) and Coronavirus disease-2019 (COVID-19): From Causes to Preventions in Hong Kong.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To prevent further outbreak of COVID-19, this article discusses the current understanding of COVID-19 and compares with the outbreak of SARS-CoV-2 in 2003 of Hong Kong from the causes, transmission, symptoms, diagnosis, treatments and preventions to study for an applicable measurement to control COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32251798&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnostic value and dynamic variance of serum antibody in coronavirus disease 2019.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To investigate the diagnostic value of serological test and dynamitic variance of serum antibody in coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19). […] Viral serological test is an effective diagnostic means for SARS-CoV-2 infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32253371&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32253371&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To provide insights on this issue, a 25-items online Survey was sent to all Italian residents one month after the first case of COVID-19 in Italy, to evaluate their routine involvement in “clinical” (on-call duty, outpatient visits, diagnostic procedures) and “surgical” (endoscopic, open and minimally invasive surgery) training activities before and during the COVID-19 period.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32255413&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Role of Chest Imaging in Patient Management during the COVID-19 Pandemic: A Multinational Consensus Statement from the Fleischner Society.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
For these regions, healthcare delivery has been disrupted and compromised by critical resource constraints in diagnostic testing, hospital beds, ventilators, and healthcare workers who have fallen ill to the virus exacerbated by shortages of personal protective equipment. […] Thoracic imaging with chest radiography (CXR) and computed tomography (CT) are key tools for pulmonary disease diagnosis and management, but their role in the management of COVID-19 has not been considered within the multivariable context of the severity of respiratory disease, pre-test probability, risk factors for disease progression, and critical resource constraints.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32257173&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;An evidence-based framework for priority clinical research questions for COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
From the research objectives for SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV, ten themes in the literature were identified: Clinical characterisation, prognosis, diagnosis, clinical management, viral pathogenesis, epidemiological characterisation, infection prevention and control/transmission, susceptibility, psychosocial, and aetiology. […] For COVID19, some information on clinical presentation, diagnostic testing, and aetiology is available but many clinical research gaps have yet to be filled.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32259123&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32259123&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Where needed, clients are referred to 16-hour treatment clinics, which are specifically set up for the diagnosis and treatment of the disease, to the hospitals, or will be treated at home.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32259130&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiological and Clinical Aspects of COVID-19; a Narrative Review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Accordingly, our narrative review appraised epidemiological and clinical aspects of the disease including genetic diversity of coronavirus genus, mode of transmission, incubation period, infectivity, pathogenicity, virulence, immunogenicity, diagnosis, surveillance, clinical case management and also successful measures for preventing its spread in some communities.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32259132&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Laboratory Parameters in Detection of COVID-19 Patients with Positive RT-PCR; a Diagnostic Accuracy Study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This diagnostic accuracy study was conducted on suspected COVID-19 patients, who presented to Behpooyan Clinic Medical center in Tehran (Iran) from 22 February to 14 March, 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32259403&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Novel coronavirus infection in children outside of Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Children who have a familial clustering or have a family member with a definite diagnosis should be reported to ensure a timely diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32259546&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Risk of nosocomial transmission of coronavirus disease 2019: an experience in a general ward setting in Hong Kong.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To describe an outbreak investigation of a patient with COVID-19 who was nursed in an open cubicle of a general ward before the diagnosis was made.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32259829&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Outbreak: An Overview.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Highly sensitive and specific diagnostic assays are key to case identification, contact tracing, identification of the animal source, and implementation of control measures.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32259853&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Nuclear medicine in SARS-CoV-2 pandemia: 18F-FDG-PET/CT to visualize COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis relies on clinical presentation, exposure history, PCR using specimens from the respiratory tract together with computed tomography (CT) imaging.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32260436&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32260436&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
ECG-derived respiration techniques were used in conjunction with a novel, phonocardiogram-derived respiration approach to extract respiratory parameters.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32260471&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;In Vitro Diagnostic Assays for COVID-19: Recent Advances and Emerging Trends.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There have been tremendous advances in in vitro diagnostic (IVD) assays for coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) caused by severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2). […] A wide range of serology immunoassays (IAs) have also been developed that complement the molecular assays for the diagnosis of COVID-19. […] However, the performance of IVD assays needs to be critically evaluated before they are employed for the clinical diagnosis of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32265088&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32265088&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A proof of concept (PoC) and prototype are presented, demonstrating a reusable custom-made three-dimensionally (3D) printed face mask based on materials and techniques (3D imaging and 3D printing) with global availability.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32265202&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Ocular manifestations of a hospitalised patient with confirmed 2019 novel coronavirus disease.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
However, conjunctival sampling might not be useful for early diagnosis because the virus may not appear initially in the conjunctiva.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32265220&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Prediction models for diagnosis and prognosis of covid-19 infection: systematic review and critical appraisal.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Three models were identified for predicting hospital admission from pneumonia and other events (as proxy outcomes for covid-19 pneumonia) in the general population; 18 diagnostic models for detecting covid-19 infection (13 were machine learning based on computed tomography scans); and 10 prognostic models for predicting mortality risk, progression to severe disease, or length of hospital stay. […] C index estimates ranged from 0.73 to 0.81 in prediction models for the general population (reported for all three models), from 0.81 to more than 0.99 in diagnostic models (reported for 13 of the 18 models), and from 0.85 to 0.98 in prognostic models (reported for six of the 10 models). […] Finally, studies should adhere to the TRIPOD (transparent reporting of a multivariable prediction model for individual prognosis or diagnosis) reporting guideline.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32266184&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Infants Born to Mothers With a New Coronavirus (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
One had rashes at birth but was discharged without parental consent for a diagnostic test.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32266524&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A case report of COVID-19 with false negative RT-PCR test: necessity of chest CT.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The definite diagnosis of corona virus disease 2019 (COVID-19) is based on the viral isolation or positive result of polymerase chain reaction (PCR) from sputum, or nasal swab, or throat swab.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32267109&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Coronavirus and COVID-19 : focus on a galopping pandemic].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The diagnosis is most often based on the detection of the viral genome in the nasopharynx by molecular biology methods. […] Le diagnostic repose, le plus souvent, sur la détection du génome viral au niveau du nasopharynx par des méthodes de biologie moléculaire.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32267209&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32267209&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Radiology departments play a critical role in policy and guideline development both for the department and for the institutions, specifically in planning diagnostic screening, triage, and management of patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32267220&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2-Specific Antibody Responses in Coronavirus Disease 2019 Patients.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Although molecular diagnostic tests were rapidly developed, serologic assays are still lacking, yet urgently needed. […] Overall, the validated assays described can be instrumental for detection of SARS-CoV-2-specific antibodies for diagnostic, seroepidemiologic, and vaccine evaluation studies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32268019&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Clinical experience of high-flow nasal cannula oxygen therapy in severe corona virus disease 2019 (COVID-19) patients].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
High-flow nasal cannula (HFNC) has been utilized widely due to its superiority over other non-invasive respiratory support techniques.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32268454&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32268454&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After admission, 6 patients were given routine treatment, the medical staffs paid attention to the protection and screened COVID-19 according to the diagnosis and treatment plan of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32269893&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A Comprehensive Literature Review on the Clinical Presentation, and Management of the Pandemic Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Furthermore, the limitations and statistical strength of the diagnostic tools currently in clinical practice are evaluated.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32270477&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32270477&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In the context of the COVID-19 pandemic, patients need to be evaluated within 2-4 weeks in the following cases: cytology result of “squamous cell carcinoma,” “atypical glandular cells, favor neoplastic,” “endocervical adenocarcinoma in situ,” or “adenocarcinoma”; histopathological diagnosis of suspected invasion from cervical/vaginal biopsy, or invasive disease after a cervical excision procedure, vaginal excision, or vulvar biopsy/excision; sudden onset of strongly suggestive symptoms for malignancy.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32270581&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32270581&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
For any care or intervention in the upper aerodigestive tract region, irrespective of the setting and a confirmed diagnosis (eg, rhinoscopy or flexible laryngoscopy in the outpatient setting and tracheostomy or rigid endoscopy under anesthesia), it is strongly recommended that all health care personnel wear personal protective equipment such as N95, gown, cap, eye protection, and gloves.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32270938&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Covid-19 diagnosis : clinical recommendations and performance of nasopharyngeal swab-PCR].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The Covid-19 pandemic imposes new diagnostic strategies in order to optimize the medical care of our patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32271208&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Survey of COVID-19 Disease Among Orthopaedic Surgeons in Wuhan, People’s Republic of China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnostic Level IV.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32271596&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Co-infection of Coronavirus Disease 2019 and Influenza A: A Report from Iran.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
They were referred to the intended centers for COVID-19 diagnosis and management of Shiraz University of Medical Sciences in southern Iran.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32271599&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32271599&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Therefore, cancer patients require higher level measures for preventing and treating infectious diseases. furthermore, cancer patients may bear additional risk due to the restriction of access to the routine diagnostic and therapeutic services during such epidemic. […] This article provides the recommendations and possible actions that should be considered by patients, their caregivers and families, physician, nurses, managers and staff of medical centers involved in cancer diagnosis and treatment. […] We pursued two major goals in our recommendations: first, limiting the exposure of cancer patients to medical environments and second, modifying the treatment modalities in a manner that reduces the probability of myelosuppression such as delaying elective diagnostic and therapeutic services, shortening the treatment course, or prolonging the interval between treatment courses.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32271601&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology and Clinical Characteristics of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Recently, accurate RNA detection has been decisive for the diagnosis of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32271602&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Improved Early Recognition of Coronavirus Disease-2019 (COVID-19): Single-Center Data from a Shanghai Screening Hospital.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The number of infected people is rapidly increasing, while the diagnostic method of COVID-19 is only by nucleic acid testing. […] To explain the epidemiological characteristics, clinical features, imaging manifestations and to judge diagnostic value of COVID-19 by analyzing the clinical data of COVID-19 suspected and confirmed patients in a non-outbreak, Shanghai, China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32271724&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32271724&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
At the time the investigation began, testing guidance recommended focusing on persons with clinical findings of lower respiratory illness and travel to an affected area or an epidemiologic link to a laboratory-confirmed COVID-19 case, or on persons hospitalized for severe respiratory disease and no alternative diagnosis (1).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32272080&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Intensive care management of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19): challenges and recommendations.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Streamlining of workflows for rapid diagnosis and isolation, clinical management, and infection prevention will matter not only to patients with COVID-19, but also to health-care workers and other patients who are at risk from nosocomial transmission.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32272262&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;High-resolution Chest CT Features and Clinical Characteristics of Patients Infected with COVID-19 in Jiangsu, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Clinical performances of patients with COVID-19, mostly with epidemiologic history and typical symptoms, were critical valuable in the diagnosis of the COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32272857&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Role of Tissue Engineering in COVID-19 and Future Viral Outbreaks.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In light of the current novel coronavirus (COVID-19) pandemic, as well as other viral outbreaks in the 21st century, there is a dire need for new diagnostic and therapeutic strategies to combat infectious diseases worldwide.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32273490&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Disease (COVID-19) in Children - What We Know So Far and What We Do Not?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis is by Reverse transcriptase-Polymerase chain reaction (RT-PCR) testing of upper or lower respiratory tract secretions.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32275128&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Roles of multidisciplinary team (MDT) in diagnosis and treatment of suspected cases of corona virus disease 2019 (COVID-19)].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To analyze the roles of multidisciplinary team (MDT) in the diagnosis and treatment of suspected cases of corona virus disease 2019 (COVID-19). […] The efficiency of diagnosis and treatment for suspected COVID-19 patients can be improved under MDT mode, particularly for complicated and refractory cases.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32275257&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical manifestation, diagnosis, prevention and control of SARS-CoV-2 (COVID-19) during the outbreak period.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This review summarizes current strategies on the diagnosis. […] The SARS-CoV-2 causes changes in blood cells and factors and makes lung abnormalities in patients, which can be detected by serological, molecular, and radiological techniques by detecting these changes and injuries.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32275288&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Neurologic Manifestations of Hospitalized Patients With Coronavirus Disease 2019 in Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The study included 214 consecutive hospitalized patients with laboratory-confirmed diagnosis of severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 infection. […] During the epidemic period of COVID-19, when seeing patients with neurologic manifestations, clinicians should suspect severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 infection as a differential diagnosis to avoid delayed diagnosis or misdiagnosis and lose the chance to treat and prevent further transmission.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32275452&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 with Different Severity: A Multi-center Study of Clinical Features.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Patients were divided into four groups according to age and into three groups (moderate, severe, and critical group) according to the fifth version of the guidelines issued by the National Health Commission of China on Diagnosis and Treatment of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32275742&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32275742&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The diagnosis of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) was confirmed by real-time reverse transcriptase polymerase chain reaction testing on postmortem swabs.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32275766&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Point-of-care lung ultrasound in patients with COVID-19 - a narrative review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Compared to other monitoring modalities, such as auscultation or radiographic imaging, we argue lung ultrasound has high diagnostic accuracy, is ergonomically favourable and has fewer infection control implications.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32275784&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32275784&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Telemedicine, defined as the delivery of health care services at a distance using electronic means for diagnosis and treatment, holds tremendous promise to increase access to broadly specialty care.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32275978&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Role of Chest Imaging in Patient Management during the COVID-19 Pandemic: A Multinational Consensus Statement from the Fleischner Society.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
For these regions, healthcare delivery has been disrupted and compromised by critical resource constraints in diagnostic testing, hospital beds, ventilators, and healthcare workers who have fallen ill to the virus exacerbated by shortages of personal protective equipment. […] Thoracic imaging with chest radiography (CXR) and computed tomography (CT) are key tools for pulmonary disease diagnosis and management, but their role in the management of COVID-19 has not been considered within the multivariable context of the severity of respiratory disease, pre-test probability, risk factors for disease progression, and critical resource constraints.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32276051&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Development of Reverse Transcription Loop-mediated Isothermal Amplification (RT-LAMP) Assays Targeting SARS-CoV-2.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis of COVID-19 is currently performed by RT-qPCR methods, but the capacity of RT-qPCR methods is limited by its requirement of high-level facilities and instruments.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32276116&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Rapid and visual detection of 2019 novel coronavirus (SARS-CoV-2) by a reverse transcription loop-mediated isothermal amplification assay.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To describe the availability of this method in clinical diagnosis, we collected 130 specimens from patients with clinically suspected SARS-CoV-2 infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32276755&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32276755&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Chest radiography and chest CT are frequently used to support the diagnosis of COVID-19 infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32276930&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32276930&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Amid concerns over the spread of COVID-19, oncology practices have “gone virtual,” with video appointments scheduled for any service that does not require diagnostic testing or treatment.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32277022&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical evaluation of the cobas SARS-CoV-2 test and a diagnostic platform switch during 48 hours in the midst of the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Laboratories are currently witnessing extraordinary demand globally for sampling devices, reagents, consumables, and diagnostic instruments needed for timely diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 infection. […] To meet diagnostic needs as the pandemic grows, the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) recently granted several commercial SARS-CoV-2 tests Emergency Use Authorization (EUA), but manufacturer-independent evaluation data are scarce. […] Immediate prospective head-to-head comparative evaluation followed on 502 samples, and the diagnostic approaches showed overall percent agreement of 99.6% and a kappa value of 0.98. […] Under the extraordinary circumstances that laboratories are facing worldwide, a safe diagnostic platform switch is feasible in only 48 hours and in the midst of the COVID-19 pandemic if carefully planned and executed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32277387&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32277387&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It is urgent to set up guidelines for the prevention, diagnosis, and treatment of COVID-19 in liver transplant recipients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32277408&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;First case of COVID-19 complicated with fulminant myocarditis: a case report and insights.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The patient conformed to the diagnostic criteria of the Chinese expert consensus statement for fulminant myocarditis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32277490&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32277490&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
For patients, concerns about Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome-Corona Virus 2 (SARS-CoV2) will add to the anxiety caused by the diagnosis of a serious fetal anomaly, and for fetal medicine teams the situation gets more complex.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32277763&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32277763&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The COVID-19 pandemic has necessitated cancelation of elective or non-urgent contact with the healthcare system, including non-urgent nerve conduction studies and electromyography (electrodiagnostic [EDX] studies).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32277845&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32277845&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There are limitations associated with sensitivity and specificity of diagnostic tests used and classification of patients based on test results has also been questioned.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32277967&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32277967&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Monitoring dynamic changes of SAA, combined with CT imaging could be valuable in diagnosis and treatment of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32278065&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diarrhea during COVID-19 infection: pathogenesis, epidemiology, prevention and management.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We searched on PubMed, EMBASE, and Web of Science up to March 2020 to identify studies documenting diarrhea and mechansism of intestinal inflammation in patients with confirmed diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 infection. […] Increasing evidence indicates possible fecal oral transmission, indicating the need for a rapid and effective modification of the screening and diagnostic algorithms.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32278764&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 and diabetes: Knowledge in progress.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We searched for articles in PubMed and Google Scholar databases till 02 April 2020, with the following keywords: “SARS-CoV-2”, “COVID-19”, “infection”, “pathogenesis”, “incubation period”, “transmission”, “clinical features”, “diagnosis”, “treatment”, “diabetes”, with interposition of the Boolean operator “AND”.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32279934&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32279934&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The latter leads to an acceptable choice of materials and techniques for personal protection and prevention of cross-contamination to other patients and staff. […] The authors have presented a protocolized approach that uses diagnostic criteria to clearly define benchmarks from the medical history along with clinical symptoms and laboratory tests. […] Patients can then be rapidly assigned into 1 of 3 risk categories that direct the choice of protective materials and/or techniques.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32280076&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical and computed tomographic (CT) images characteristics in the patients with COVID-19 infection: What should radiologists need to know?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There were some typical CT features for diagnosis of COVID-19 pneumonia.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281327&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Rapid establishment of traditional Chinese medicine prevention and treatment of 2019-nCoV based on clinical experience and molecular docking].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Taking full advantage of the clinical experience of traditional Chinese medicine(TCM) in preventing and controlling major epidemics such as SARS, it is an important mission for TCM to propose effective formula with immediate response and solid evidence by using modern biomedical knowledge and techniques(molecular docking assisted TCM formulation for short).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281328&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Study on screening potential traditional Chinese medicines against 2019-nCoV based on Mpro and PLP].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
By combining the diagnosis and treatment scheme of Hunan province’s and angiotensin converting enzyme 2(ACE2) inhibitors screening from literature, present study also discussed the rational application of candidate herbs to this epidemic situation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281329&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Study on treatment of cytokine storm by anti-2019-nCoV prescriptions based on arachidonic acid metabolic pathway].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In the end, we obtained the potential active prescriptions on &amp;amp;quot;cytokine storm&amp;amp;quot; according to the potential herbs in the &amp;amp;quot;National novel coronavirus pneumonia diagnosis and treatment plan(trial version sixth)&amp;amp;quot;.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281331&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Analysis on pattern of prescriptions and syndromes of traditional Chinese medicine for prevention and treatment of COVID-19].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To investigate the regularity of prescription and clinical syndromes by analyzing the diagnosis and treatment protocols of traditional Chinese medicine(TCM) for coronavirus disease 2019(COVID-19), so as to provide references for syndrome differentiation and relevant researches. […] The diagnosis and treatment protocols of COVID-19 published by national and regional health authorities were searched, and information was extracted in regard to disease stages, type of syndromes, and prescriptions, etc. […] A total of 26 diagnosis and treatment protocols of TCM for COVID-19 were retrieved after screening(including 1 national scheme and 25 regional ones), among which 16 contained aspects of both prevention and treatment, 7 only involved treatment contents and 3 were prevention schemes. […] There were many diagnosis and treatment protocols for COVID-19 have been published, which generally followed the national edition, through with certain personalities in different regional protocols. […] Along with the deepening recognition of COVID-19, the diagnosis and treatment protocols are still need further concretization and standardization.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281333&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Analysis of property and efficacy of traditional Chinese medicine in staging revention and treatment of coronavirus disease 2019].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This study collected prevention and treatment approaches of traditional Chinese medicine for COVID-19 released from the National Health Committee of China, 7 provinces and municipal health committees, the Chinese Medicine Administration and Handbook of Traditional Chinese Medicine Diagnosis and Treatment of COVID-19 between January 1 and February 18, 2020, and prescriptions prepared by 3 masters of Chinese medicine and 4 well-known Chinese medicine experts.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32281335&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32281335&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Chinese patent medicines and prescriptions in medical observation and clinical treatment were recommended in the &amp;amp;quot;pneumonia diagnosis and treatment plan for new coronavirus infection&amp;amp;quot;(trial version fifth) of the National Health Commission of the People’s Republic of China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32281391&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32281391&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We recommend to set up an isolation zone for handling patients who do not meet the diagnostic criteria of COVID-19 but are not completely cleared of the possibility of infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281667&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus disease 2019: new things to know!&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&amp;quot; 1 which report the clinical features, diagnosis and treatment of the novel Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281668&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;C-reactive protein correlates with CT findings and predicts severe COVID-19 early.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The present study aimed to analyze the characteristics of severe COVID-19 and identify biomarkers for differential diagnosis and prognosis prediction.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281757&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Covid-19 in patients on dialysis: infection prevention and control strategies].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
However, as Covid-19 is an emerging disease, more work is needed to improve prevention, diagnosis and treatment strategies. […] It is essential to avoid nosocomial spread; in order to control and reduce the rate of infections it is necessary to strengthen the management of medical and nursing personnel through the early diagnosis, isolation and treatment of patients undergoing dialysis treatment.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281785&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Dual-Functional Plasmonic Photothermal Biosensors for Highly Accurate Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2 Detection.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Reliable laboratory diagnosis of the disease has been one of the foremost priorities for promoting public health interventions. […] The routinely used reverse transcription polymerase chain reaction (RT-PCR) is currently the reference method for COVID-19 diagnosis. […] In this work, a dual-functional plasmonic biosensor combining the plasmonic photothermal (PPT) effect and localized surface plasmon resonance (LSPR) sensing transduction provides an alternative and promising solution for the clinical COVID-19 diagnosis. […] This study gains insight into the thermoplasmonic enhancement and its applicability in the nucleic acid tests and viral disease diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32282372&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32282372&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here he considers the implications of exemplary innovations-virtual care, hospital at home, advances in diagnosis and therapy, virtual learning, and virtual clinical learning-for regulators, academic medical centers, faculty, and students.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32282404&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Incidental CT Findings Suspicious for Covid-19 Associated Pneumonia on Nuclear Medicine Exams: Recognition and Management Plan.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It is critical for Nuclear Medicine physicians to develop diagnostic skills for timely recognition of typical findings of C-19AP on a localizing CT.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32282863&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32282863&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this minireview, we provide a brief introduction of the general features of SARS-CoV-2 and discuss current knowledge of molecular immune pathogenesis, diagnosis and treatment of COVID-19 on the base of the present understanding of SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV infections, which may be helpful in offering novel insights and potential therapeutic targets for combating the SARS-CoV-2 infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32282894&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnostic Testing for Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome-Related Coronavirus-2: A Narrative Review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnostic testing to identify persons infected with severe acute respiratory syndrome-related coronavirus-2 (SARS-CoV-2) infection is central to control the global pandemic of COVID-19 that began in late 2019. […] In a few countries, the use of diagnostic testing on a massive scale has been a cornerstone of successful containment strategies. […] Although excellent tools exist for the diagnosis of symptomatic patients in well-equipped laboratories, important gaps remain in screening asymptomatic persons in the incubation phase, as well as in the accurate determination of live viral shedding during convalescence to inform decisions to end isolation. […] Here, the authors review the current array of tests for SARS-CoV-2, highlight gaps in current diagnostic capacity, and propose potential solutions.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32283006&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SARS-CoV-2: Olfaction, Brain Infection, and the Urgent Need for Clinical Samples Allowing Earlier Virus Detection.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Attempts at slowing the pandemic at this stage depend on the number and quality of diagnostic tests performed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32283141&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Serological immunochromatographic approach in diagnosis with SARS-CoV-2 infected COVID-19 patients.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The standard diagnostic approach that widely adopted in the clinic is nucleic acid detection by real-time RT-PCR.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32283185&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32283185&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The two cohorts (cryopreserved versus fresh) were similar in patient age, KPS, diagnosis, DRI, HCT-comorbidity index, donor/graft source, and conditioning intensity.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32283268&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32283268&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
With the high transmissibility of the virus, there has been an increasing concern for the development of techniques to perform surgical intervention while mitigating the risk for infecting hospital staff.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32283498&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19: From bench to bed side.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Ample data is available to suggest the differences in etiology, transmission cycle, diagnosis, genetics, hosts, reproductive rates, clinical features, laboratory diagnosis and radiological features between SARS-CoV-1, MERS-CoV and SARS-CoV-2.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32285293&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Searching therapeutic strategy of new coronavirus pneumonia from angiotensin-converting enzyme 2: the target of COVID-19 and SARS-CoV.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This article will summarize the role of ACE2 in multiple organ damage caused by COVID-19 and SARS-CoV, targeted blocking drugs against ACE2, and drugs that inhibit inflammation in order to provide the basis for subsequent related research, diagnosis and treatment, and drug development.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32285338&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32285338&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Among surgeons worldwide, a concern with the use of minimally invasive techniques has been raised due to a proposed risk of viral transmission of the coronavirus disease of 2019 (COVID-19) with the creation of pneumoperitoneum.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32285862&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32285862&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The publication of full-genomes of the newly identified coronavirus (initially called 2019-nCoV, now called SARS-CoV2) in public and private databases, of standardized diagnostic protocols and of the clinical-epidemiological information generated will allow addressing the Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC), declared on January 30 by the WHO.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32285949&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Computed Tomography Imaging of an HIV-infected Patient with Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This report provides reference for the diagnosis and treatment of HIV-infected patients with COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32286155&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Significance of Serology Testing to Assist Timely Diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 infections: Implication from a Family Cluster.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Confirmative diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 infections has been challenged due to unsatisfactory positive rate of molecular assays. […] Our results emphasized the significance of serology testing to assist timely diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 infections, especially for COVID-19 close contacts screening.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32286216&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Diagnostic imaging findings in COVID-19].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This is a review of diagnostic imaging findings in coronavirus disease-2019 (COVID-19). […] Initially the CT can be normal, and the diagnostic performance for COVID-19 is not optimal.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32286242&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The value of urine biochemical parameters in the prediction of the severity of coronavirus disease 2019.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A viral nucleic acid test is used for the diagnosis of COVID-19, and some hematological indicators have been used in the auxiliary diagnosis and identification of the severity of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32286916&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32286916&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Until preoperative diagnostic testing becomes standardized and readily available, elective cases should be deferred and emergent/urgent cases should be treated as high risk for COVID-19 exposure.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32287040&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32287040&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The HHS was designed for the collection, integration, standardization, and analysis of COVID-19-related data from multiple sources, which includes a case reporting system, diagnostic labs, electronic medical records, and social media on mobile devices.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32289466&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32289466&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This is a cross-sectional study of patients who received a COVID-19 diagnosis between December 30, 2019 and February 7, 2020 at Tongji Hospital. […] A total of 102 patients (48 Male [47%] and 54 Female [53%]) with clinical symptoms, Rt, and chest Computed Tomography (CT) abnormalities were identified with a clinical diagnosis of COVID-19. […] Of a total of 102 patients identified, 72 patients (36 men [50%] and 36 women [50%]; mean [SD] age, 58.68 [14.81] years) were confirmed to have COVID-19 by laboratory diagnosis with a SARS-CoV-2 RT-PCR assay. […] To lower the SARS-CoV-2 nosocomial infection, all health care professionals should wear protective goggles.The inefficient diagnostic method and the sampling time lag may contribute to the lower positive rate of conjunctival swab samples of SARS-CoV-2.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32290643&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32290643&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To summarize the administration model of a COVID-19 designated hospital transformed from a community hospital to improve the emergency capacity of community hospitals and the efficiency of diagnosis and treatment of medical staff in the COVID-19 pandemic. […] Its diagnosis and treatment model has completed the treatment of COVID- 19 patients successfully.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32291080&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32291080&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
As this is a respiratory infection, chest radiography and computed tomography (CT) are important imaging techniques in the work-up of this disease. […] We describe the response of radiology departments in Singapore to this pandemic, in terms of diagnosis, re-configuration of the department, re-organisation and segregation of staff, infection control, managerial, and leadership issues.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32291197&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 pneumonia: A review of typical CT findings and differential diagnosis.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Computed tomography (CT) can be used as an important complement for the diagnosis of COVID-19 pneumonia in the current epidemic context. […] In this review, we present the typical CT features of COVID-19 pneumonia and discuss the main differential diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32291207&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32291207&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We enrolled patients with confirmed diagnosis of COVID-19 retrospectively and collected heart-related clinical data, mainly including cardiac imaging findings, laboratory results and clinical outcomes.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32291374&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Importance of Chest CT Scan in COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
One of the challenges in managing COVID-19 is the identification of a swift, accessible, and reliable diagnostic modality that could serve as an alternative to a reverse-transcriptase polymerase chain reaction (RT-PCR). […] As of the writing of this paper, RT-PCR is still the recommended tool in diagnosing COVID-19, but the notion of a more prompt and accurate diagnostic tool is a possibility worth looking into. […] The objective of this case study is to investigate the importance and utility of chest computed tomography (CT) in the diagnosis of COVID-19, as increasing pieces of evidence suggest that chest CT could prove useful in the clinical pathway in diagnosing COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32291501&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CT features of novel coronavirus pneumonia (COVID-19) in children.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
As the majority of patients infected with COVID-19 had chest CT abnormality, chest CT has become an important tool for early diagnosis of COVID-19 and monitoring disease progression. […] This review is mainly about the differences in clinical symptom spectrum, diagnosis of COVID-19, and CT imaging findings between adults and children, while highlighting the value of radiology in prevention and control of COVID-19 in pediatric patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32291542&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The epidemiology and clinical information about COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we summarized the epidemiological characteristics, clinical features, diagnosis, treatment, and prognosis of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32292205&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Distributions of time, place, and population of novel coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) from January 20 to February 10, 2020, in China].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The COVID-19 epidemic should be considered a global threat and the steps for control include early diagnosis and treatment, as well as isolation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32292213&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Coronavirus: from common cold to severe pulmonary failure].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Molecular diagnostic methods have been established in a very short time and a number of clinical studies on the effectiveness of different antiviral drugs are ongoing.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32292529&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32292529&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
As the epicentre of the initial outbreak, China has been updating the National COVID-19 Diagnostic and Treatment Guideline with up-to-date information about the disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32292623&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Recent advances and perspectives of nucleic acid detection for coronavirus.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It is important to establish a quick standard diagnostic test for the detection of the infectious disease (COVID-19) to prevent subsequent secondary spread. […] Polymerase chain reaction (PCR) is regarded as a gold standard test for the molecular diagnosis of viral and bacterial infections with high sensitivity and specificity. […] It is anticipated that this will assist researchers and clinicians in developing better techniques for timely and effective detection of coronavirus infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32292637&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32292637&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Based on refined management theory, we professionally developed the standards for prevention and control of COVID-19 in non-isolated areas, systematically implemented various prevention and control measures, performed gridding audit, effectively communicated among teams and between doctors and patients assisted by information techniques, and reported results for quality improvement.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32292697&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32292697&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
All patients received oral HGF therapy for six months when they were confirmed the diagnosis of steroid-associated ONFH.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32292802&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Emergence of deadly severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus-2 during 2019-2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We have also provided information about the classification, genome, proteins, clinical presentation of COVID-19, type of clinical specimens to be collected and diagnostic methods adopted to identify the respiratory illness.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32292826&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32292826&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Since the coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) outbreak was identified in December 2019 in Wuhan, China, a strong response from the research community has been observed with the proliferation of independent clinical trials assessing diagnostic methods, therapeutic and prophylactic strategies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32292880&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Progress and prospect on imaging diagnosis of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The appearance of pneumonia is one of the major clues for the diagnosis, progress and therapeutic evaluation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32292902&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Outcome of Coronavirus spectrum infections (SARS, MERS, COVID 1 -19) during pregnancy: a systematic review and meta-analysis.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
An overt diagnosis of pneumonia was made in 91.8% and the most common symptoms were fever (82.6%), cough (57.1%) and dyspnea (27.0%).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32292904&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32292904&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The diagnosis, infection control, and treatment of COVID-19 in hemodialysis patients are discussed in this report, and we conclude with recommendations for how a dialysis facility can respond to COVID-19 based on our experiences.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32293168&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Rapid Detection of COVID-19 Causative Virus (SARS-CoV-2) in Human Nasopharyngeal Swab Specimens Using Field-Effect Transistor-Based Biosensor.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Because no specific drugs or vaccines for COVID-19 are yet available, early diagnosis and management are crucial for containing the outbreak. […] Thus, we have successfully fabricated a promising FET biosensor for SARS-CoV-2; our device is a highly sensitive immunological diagnostic method for COVID-19 that requires no sample pretreatment or labeling.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32293743&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coinfection with COVID-19 and Coronavirus HKU1 - the critical need for repeat testing if clinically indicated.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In general, respiratory viral co-infections are recognized more commonly today with the use of respiratory multiplex molecular diagnostic panels. […] A high degree of suspicion in this rapidly evolving outbreak is required in order to make the diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32294077&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32294077&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The goal of this column is to inform mental health care professionals about the evolving way the diagnosis of Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) is being made, with emphasis on tests to assist in making the diagnosis and to determine the presence of antibodies to the virus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32294796&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32294796&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This study was conducted to explore the clinical value of noninvasive assessment of bedside ultrasound in the diagnosis of lung lesions of Coronavirus Disease-19. […] The ultrasound scores to evaluate mild, moderate and severe lung lesions exhibited sensitivity of 68.8 % (11/16), 77.8 % (7/9), 100.0 % (2/2), specificity of 85.7 % (12/14), 76.2 % (16/21), 92.9 % (26/28), and diagnostic accuracy of 76.7 % (23/30), 76.7 % (23/30), 93.3 % (28/30), respectively. […] Though the diagnostic efficacy of bedside ultrasound is relatively low for mild to moderate patients, it is high for severe patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms to cluster Diagnsose Abstract</title>
      <link>/syntax_summary/diagnsosis/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/syntax_summary/diagnsosis/terms/</guid>
      <description> 

&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 2.&lt;/strong&gt; 16 terms used to create the Diagnosis Category and its counts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Term
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Count
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
All (sum)
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
360
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
diagnosis
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
270
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Techniques
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Clinical Diagnosis
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnostic Imaging
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
1
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Clinical Laboratory Techniques
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnosis of Health Situation
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnostic
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Diagnostic Techniques and Procedures
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Immunologic Tests
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Medicamentous Diagnosis
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Molecular Diagnostic Techniques
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Nursing Diagnosis
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Reagent Kits
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Serologic Tests
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Telediagnostics
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
