<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PlatCOVID</title>
    <link>/tissuepanel/placenta/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tissuepanel/placenta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>PlatCOVID</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>BioHub - UFPE</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu7e12209333f22d741aca7d462871821f_9877_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>PlatCOVID</title>
      <link>/tissuepanel/placenta/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>placenta</title>
      <link>/tissuepanel/placenta/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/tissuepanel/placenta/info/</guid>
      <description> 

&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;div id=&#34;tissue-sentence-context&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Tissue Sentence Context&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 1.&lt;/strong&gt; Analysis of context sentence of &lt;em&gt;spleen&lt;/em&gt; tissue in 18 abstracts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
PMID
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Senteces
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32172546&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32172546&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To investigate the pathological characteristics and the clinical significance of novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV)-infected pneumonia (termed by WHO as corona virus disease 2019, COVID-19). &lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; Minimally invasive autopsies from lung, heart, kidney, spleen, bone marrow, liver, pancreas, stomach, intestine, thyroid and skin were performed on three patients died of novel coronavirus pneumonia in Chongqing, China. […] Decreased numbers of lymphocyte, cell degeneration and necrosis were observed in spleen.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32215622&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32215622&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Maximal clinical signs of rapid breathing, weight loss, histopathological changes from the initial exudative phase of diffuse alveolar damage with extensive apoptosis to the later proliferative phase of tissue repair, airway and intestinal involvement with virus nucleocapsid protein expression, high lung viral load, and spleen and lymphoid atrophy associated with marked cytokine activation were observed within the first week of virus challenge.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281331&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32281331&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The location of the disease is lung, always involving spleen and stomach, and may further affect heart and kidney in severe cases.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32281332&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32281332&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Among them, the four properties were mainly concentrated in temperature, cold and level, the five tastes were mainly concentrated in bitter, hot and sweet, and the meridians were mainly concentrated in lung, stomach and spleen.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32292697&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32292697&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In China, a considerable number of convalescent SARS patients with steroid-associated ONFH had undergone conservative treatment by Traditional Chinese Medicine (TCM), and this study aims to evaluate the long-term results of a spleen-invigorating Huo-Gu Formula (HGF) therapy in these patients. and methods: A total of 33 convalescent SARS patients (nine males and 24 females) with bilateral steroid-associated ONFH (66 hips) were enrolled in this study.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32307268&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32307268&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Twelve disease pathways attributed to the Lung-Large Intestine meridians, with six and five attributed to the Kidney-Urinary Bladder and Stomach-Spleen meridians, respectively. […] RDS acts primarily in the Lung-Large Intestine, Kidney-Urinary Bladder and Stomach-Spleen meridians, with other Zang-fu viscera strategically covered by all nine ingredients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32308732&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32308732&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
According to the standard coefficients of regression, the factor affecting the length of stay for the most was CMs in category of invigorating spleen and removing dampness (ISRD), followed by administrating CMs, male, and cough.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32340089&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32340089&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To study the pathological changes of the spleen in patients with COVID-19 and to analyze the relationship between the weakened immune system and splenic lesions. &lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; Minimally invasive autopsies from the spleen were carried out on 10 patients who died from COVID-19 in Wuhan. […] The changes of lymphocytes were studied further with immunohistochemistry.RT-PCR was used to detect 2019-nCov RNA in the spleen. […] Histopathological examination showed that the cell composition of the spleen decreased, white pulp atrophied at different levels, meanwhile lymphoid follicles decreased or absent; in addition, the ratio of red pulp to white pulp increased with varying degrees. […] Meanwhile, necrosis and lymphocytic apoptosis were detected in 2 cases, small artery thrombosis and spleen infarction in 1 case, and fungal infection in 1 case. […] The results of immunohistochemistry showed that the T and B lymphocyte components of the spleen in all cases decreased in varying degrees. […] Spleen maybe one of the organs directly attacked by the virus in some patients who died from COVID-19. […] T and B lymphocyte in the spleen decrease in varying degrees, lymphoid follicles are atrophied, decreased or absent, and the number of NK cells do not change significantly. […] And the pathological changes of the spleen are not related to the use of low dose corticosteroid, which may be related to the direct attack of virus and the attack of immune system on its own tissues. &lt;b&gt;目的：&lt;/b&gt; 研究新型冠状病毒感染疾病（COVID-19）患者的脾脏病理改变，探讨患者免疫系统功能低下与脾脏病变之间的关系。
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32345362&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32345362&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
ACE2 expression levels were the highest in the small intestine, testis, kidneys, heart, thyroid, and adipose tissue, and were the lowest in the blood, spleen, bone marrow, brain, blood vessels, and muscle.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32380209&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32380209&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The isolate I0305/19 exhibited broader tropisms in different tissues, including tracheas, lungs, bursa of Fabricius, spleen, liver, kidneys, proventriculus, small intestines, large intestines, cecum, and cecal tonsils.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32402766&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32402766&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Concretely, this relates to (a) the inconsistent individual bioavailability of these drugs at the alveolar target cells, depending on intestinal resorption, hepatic first-pass metabolism and accumulation in liver, spleen and lung, and (b) the need for a relatively high concentration of 1-5 µM at the alveolar surface.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32422076&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32422076&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Additional frequent findings included renal proximal tubular injury, focal pancreatitis, adrenocortical hyperplasia, and lymphocyte depletion of spleen and lymph nodes.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32443177&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32443177&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We used MIA-US for tissue sampling of lungs, liver, heart, kidneys, spleen, brain, skin, skeletal muscle and testis for histology and RT-PCR to detect SARS-COV-2-RNA. […] Small thrombi were less frequently observed in glomeruli, spleen, heart, dermis, testis, and liver sinusoids.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32451533&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32451533&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Viral RNA was detected in lungs, bronchi, lymph nodes, and spleen in both cases using qRT-PCR method.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32489024&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32489024&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The potential herbs for treating pulmonary fibrosis mostly belong to lung(degree=14) and spleen(degree value=8), and the efficacy is focused on reinforcing deficiency(degree=9).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32495578&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32495578&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The main meridian of these TCM is lung, heart, spleen, liver, and stomach meridian.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32568186&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32568186&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In COVID-19 ICU patients massive aggression of lung with severe pulmonary failure, as well as kidney and liver injuries, heart, brain, bowel and spleen damages with lymph nodes necrosis and even cutaneous manifestations have been observed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32576343&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32576343&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Latent structure model was established based on 53 symptoms with frequency over 10, and 14 latent variables and 7 syndromes were concluded by comprehensive clustering, including syndrome of pathogenic heat invading lung, internal block and outward desertion, syndrome of dampness heat accumulating lung, syndrome of Qi and Yin deficiency, syndrome of epidemic virus closing lung, syndrome of cold dampness closing lung and syndrome of Qi deficiency of lung and spleen. […] The literatures included 25 syndromes, and the syndromes with constituent ratio over 5% were internal block and outward desertion (14.62%), syndrome of epidemic virus closing lung (13.68%), syndrome of dampness heat accumulating lung (12.74%), syndrome of Qi deficiency of lung (10.85%), spleen and syndrome of cold dampness closing lung (8.50%), syndrome of Qi and Yin deficiency (8.50%), syndrome of pathogenic heat invading lung (8.02%) and syndrome of dampness repressing defensive Qi of lung (5.66%). […] According to the results above, the common syndromes and their symptoms of COVID-19 were: (1) syndrome of pathogenic heat invading lung: fever, cough, throat-drying, headache, all of the body distressed and constipation, etc.; (2) syndrome of cold dampness closing lung: aversion to cold, all of the body distressed, nausea and vomiting, abdominal distention and loose stool, etc.; (3) syndrome of dampness heat accumulating lung: cough, sticky phlegm, anorexia, thirst without desire to drink and constipation, etc.; (4) syndrome of epidemic virus closing lung: fever, cough, yellow phlegm, wheezing, suffocation and purple lips, etc.; (5) internal block and outward desertion: coma, feel fidgety, suffocation, sweating and feel cold and purple lips, etc.; (6) syndrome of Qi and Yin deficiency: dry cough, sweating, fatigue, thirsty, feverish feeling in palms and soles and loose stool, etc.; (7) syndrome of Qi deficiency of lung and spleen: cough, wheezing, sweating, fatigue, nausea and vomiting, and loose stool, et al. […] The common syndromes of COVID-19 were syndrome of pathogenic heat invading lung, syndrome of cold dampness closing lung, syndrome of dampness heat accumulating lung, syndrome of epidemic virus closing lung, internal block and outward desertion, syndrome of Qi and Yin deficiency and syndrome of Qi deficiency of lung and spleen.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
