<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PlatCOVID</title>
    <link>/tissuepanel/testis/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tissuepanel/testis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>PlatCOVID</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>BioHub - UFPE</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu7e12209333f22d741aca7d462871821f_9877_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>PlatCOVID</title>
      <link>/tissuepanel/testis/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>testis</title>
      <link>/tissuepanel/testis/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/tissuepanel/testis/info/</guid>
      <description> 

&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;div id=&#34;tissue-sentence-context&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Tissue Sentence Context&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 1.&lt;/strong&gt; Analysis of context sentence of &lt;em&gt;placenta&lt;/em&gt; tissue in 18 abstracts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
PMID
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Senteces
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32114744&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32114744&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To investigate the clinical characteristics and placental pathology of 2019-nCoV infection in pregnancy, and to evaluate intrauterine vertical transmission potential of 2019-nCoV infection. &lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; The placentas delivered from pregnant women with confirmed 2019-nCoV infection which were received in the Department of Pathology, Union Hospital, Tongji Medical College, Huazhong University of Science and Technology collected by February 4th, 2020 and retrospectively studied. […] Their clinical material including placental tissue and lung CT, and laboratory results were collected, meanwhile, nucleic acid detection of 2019-nCoV of the placentas were performed by RT-PCR. &lt;b&gt;Results:&lt;/b&gt; Three placentas delivered from pregnant women with confirmed 2019-nCoV infection, who were all in their third trimester with emergency caesarean section. […] There were various degrees of fibrin deposition inside and around the villi with local syncytial nodule increases in all three placentas. […] One case of placenta showed the concomitant morphology of chorionic hemangioma and another one with massive placental infarction. […] All samples from three placentas were negative for the nucleic acid of 2019-nCoV. &lt;b&gt;Conclusions:&lt;/b&gt; The clinical characteristics of pregnant women with 2019-nCoV infection in late pregnancy are similar to those of non-pregnant patients, and no severe adverse pregnancy outcome is found in the 3 cases of our observation. […] Pathological study suggests that there are no morphological changes related to infection in the three placentas.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32298273&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32298273&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Our results revealed that ACE2 was highly expressed in maternal-fetal interface cells including stromal cells and perivascular cells of decidua, and cytotrophoblast and syncytiotrophoblast in placenta. […] And thus, both the vertical transmission and the placenta dysfunction/abortion caused by SARS-CoV-2 need to be further carefully investigated in clinical practice.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32305459&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32305459&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The nucleic acid test from the mother’s amniotic fluid, vaginal secretions, cord blood, placenta, serum, anal swab, and breast milk were also negative.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32365180&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32365180&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The available evidence suggests that ACE2 is widely expressed in the ovary, uterus, vagina and placenta.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32376317&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32376317&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Sars-cov-2 could be recovered by real-time (RT) PCR from nasal and throat swabs, sputum and feces of symptomatic patients including neonates but not from vaginal swabs, amniotic fluid, placenta, cord blood, neonatal blood or breast milk.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32379909&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32379909&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
However, mother-to-child SARS-CoV-2 transmission through the placenta probably does not occur, or likely occurs very rarely.&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt; All the studies conducted on COVID-19 pregnant women involved patients undergoing cesarean section, but the indications for such delivery modality were not clearly stated.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32385225&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32385225&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Questions arise concerning the continuation of pregnancy, how to terminate the pregnancy, the possibility of virus transmission through the placenta, isolation of the newborn after birth, and breastfeeding.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32391518&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32391518&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
One recent review reported that in a small number of cases, two PCR swabs of the placenta were sent in additional to neonatal and cord blood testing, and both placental PCR swabs were negative.&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; Other studies have demonstrated the finding of SARS-CoV2 IgM in neonates born to mothers diagnosed with COVID-19 during pregnancy,&lt;sup&gt;2,3&lt;/sup&gt; findings that may indicate vertical transmission of the virus in utero. […] We report our experience with placental/membrane SARS-CoV2 RNA PCR swab results after delivery to a series of symptomatic mothers with confirmed COVID-19 infection in pregnancy. […] Charts were reviewed for documentation of SARS-CoV-2 RNA RT-PCR testing sent from either the placenta or membranes within 30 minutes following delivery. […] Placental swabs were obtained from the amniotic surface after clearing the surface of maternal blood (placental PCR). […] Of 32 COVID-19 positive pregnant patients who gave birth in this timeframe, placental or membrane swabs were sent from 11 patients (Table). […] Of 11 placental or membrane swabs sent following delivery, 3 swabs were positive for SARS-CoV-2, all in women with moderate to severe COVID-19 illness at time of delivery. […] This is the first study to demonstrate the presence of SARS-CoV-2 RNA in placental or membrane samples. […] In summary, the presence of viral RNA by RT-PCR in placenta/membranes at the time of delivery suggests the need for further research into the possibility of vertical transmission.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32403141&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32403141&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
However, without positive RT-PCR tests of amniotic fluid, placenta, or cord blood, there is a lack of virologic evidence for intrauterine vertical transmission. […] Additional RT-PCR tests on amniotic fluid, placenta, and cord blood are needed to ascertain the possibility of intrauterine vertical transmission. […] · More RT-PCR tests on amniotic fluid, placenta, and cord blood are recommended..
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32441303&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32441303&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To describe histopathologic findings in the placentas of women with coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) during pregnancy. […] Placentas were examined and compared to historical controls and women with placental evaluation for a history of melanoma. […] Sixteen placentas from patients with severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) were examined (15 with live birth in the third trimester, 1 delivered in the second trimester after intrauterine fetal demise). […] Compared to controls, third trimester placentas were significantly more likely to show at least one feature of maternal vascular malperfusion (MVM), particularly abnormal or injured maternal vessels, and intervillous thrombi. […] Rates of acute and chronic inflammation were not increased.The placenta from the patient with intrauterine fetal demise showed villous edema and a retroplacental hematoma. […] Relative to controls, COVID-19 placentas show increased prevalence of decidual arteriopathy and other features of MVM, a pattern of placental injury reflecting abnormalities in oxygenation within the intervillous space associated with adverse perinatal outcomes. […] These changes may reflect a systemic inflammatory or hypercoagulable state influencing placental physiology.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32454807&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32454807&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Five studies using data on umbilical cord blood, placenta, and/or amniotic fluid reported no positive results. […] En cinco estudios se analizó la sangre del cordón umbilical, la placenta o el líquido amniótico y no se informaron resultados positivos. […] O sangue do cordão umbilical, a placenta ou o líquido amniótico foram analisados em cinco estudos, não tendo sido relatados resultados positivos.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32474140&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32474140&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Centers for Disease Control to affect fetal development similarly to other common respiratory coronaviruses through effects of the maternal inflammatory response on the fetus and placenta.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32529643&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32529643&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Despite reports of neonatal COVID-19, SARS-CoV-2 has not been consistently isolated in perinatal samples thus, definitive proof of transplacental infection is still lacking. […] To address these questions, we assessed investigative tools used to confirm maternal-fetal infection and known protective mechanisms of the placental barrier that prevent transplacental pathogen migration. […] Histological examination demonstrated sparse viral particles, vascular malperfusion and inflammation in the placenta from pregnant women with COVID-19. […] The paucity of placental co-expression of ACE-2 and TMPRSS2, two receptors involved in cytoplasmic entry of SARS-CoV-2, may explain its relative insensitivity to transplacental infection. […] Further spatial-temporal studies are needed to determine the true potential for transplacental migration.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32542883&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32542883&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In March 2020, the World health organization reported coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) as a pandemic.&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; Khan et al., 2020, in their systemic review about positive COVID-19 pregnant women, showed a rate of 29.1% preterm birth and 16.4% low birth weight among their babies.&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt; This increases the interest that hyper-inflammatory state in COVID-19 may be associated with hypoxic injury in the placenta and developing pre-eclamptic state.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32570959&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32570959&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
RT-PCR for SARS-CoV-2 yielded negative results on amniotic fluid, vaginal/cervical fluids, placenta tissue, and breast milk samples.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32573498&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32573498&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We present a case of second trimester pregnancy with symptomatic Covid-19 complicated by severe preeclampsia and placental abruption. […] We analyzed placenta for the presence of SARS-CoV-2 through molecular and immunohistochemical assays and by and electron microscopy, and we measured the maternal antibody response in blood to this infection. […] SARS-CoV-2 localized predominantly to syncytiotrophoblast cells at the maternal-fetal interface of the placenta. […] Histological examination of the placenta revealed a dense macrophage infiltrate, but no evidence for vasculopathy typically associated with preeclampsia. […] This case demonstrates SARS-CoV-2 invasion of the placenta, highlighting the potential for severe morbidity among pregnant women with Covid-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32574110&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32574110&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Reports of placental infection and vertical transmission are rare. […] Interestingly, despite lack of SARS-CoV-2 placenta productive infection there are several reports of significant abnormalities in placenta morphology.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32574285&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32574285&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The virus was not detected in the neonate nasopharyngeal swab samples at birth, in the placenta, in the umbilical cord, in the amniotic fluid, in the breast milk or in the maternal vaginal swab samples in any of these articles.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
