<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Epidemiology | PlatCOVID</title>
    <link>/syntax_summary/epidemiology/</link>
      <atom:link href="/syntax_summary/epidemiology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Epidemiology</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>BioHub - UFPE</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu7e12209333f22d741aca7d462871821f_9877_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Epidemiology</title>
      <link>/syntax_summary/epidemiology/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epidemiology Sentence Context</title>
      <link>/syntax_summary/epidemiology/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/syntax_summary/epidemiology/info/</guid>
      <description> 

&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 1.&lt;/strong&gt; Analysis of context sentence of 283 absracts clustered as Epidemiology.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Title
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Gene Context Sentence
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
ePubDate
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31986264&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical features of patients infected with 2019 novel coronavirus in Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Major gaps in our knowledge of the origin, epidemiology, duration of human transmission, and clinical spectrum of disease need fulfilment by future studies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31995857&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Early Transmission Dynamics in Wuhan, China, of Novel Coronavirus-Infected Pneumonia.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We analyzed data on the first 425 confirmed cases in Wuhan to determine the epidemiologic characteristics of NCIP. […] We described characteristics of the cases and estimated the key epidemiologic time-delay distributions.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32020915&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Novel Coronavirus: A Bird’s Eye View.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Herein, we present on an overview of the currently available information on the pathogenesis, epidemiology, clinical presentation, diagnosis, and treatment of this virus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32044814&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical characteristics of novel coronavirus cases in tertiary hospitals in Hubei Province.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This study aims to investigate its epidemiologic history, and analyze the clinical characteristics, treatment regimens, and prognosis of patients infected with 2019-nCoV during this outbreak.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32062875&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Retracted: Clinical and epidemiological characteristics of 34 children with 2019 novel coronavirus infection in Shenzhen].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To describe the characteristics of clinical manifestations and epidemiology of children with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. &lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; All 34 children with laboratory-confirmed 2019-nCoV infection by quantitative real-time reverse transcription-PCR through nasopharyngeal swab specimens were admitted to the Third People’s Hospital of Shenzhen from January 19 to Febuary 7, 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32065057&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Molecular and serological investigation of 2019-nCoV infected patients: implication of multiple shedding routes.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We also showed serology test can improve detection positive rate thus should be used in future epidemiology.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32072569&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;2019 Novel coronavirus: where we are and what we know.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This paper aggregates and consolidates the virology, epidemiology, clinical management strategies from both English and Chinese literature, official news channels, and other official government documents.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32078069&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;2019 novel coronavirus of pneumonia in Wuhan, China: emerging attack and management strategies.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
More comprehensive information is required to understand 2019-nCoV feature, the epidemiology of origin and spreading, and the clinical phenomina.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32080991&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Viral Load Kinetics of SARS-CoV-2 Infection in First Two Patients in Korea.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
With the numbers of confirmed cases are increasing, information on the epidemiologic investigation and clinical manifestation have been accumulated.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32083985&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19): A Perspective from China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This review focuses on the etiology, epidemiology, and clinical symptoms of COVID-19, while highlighting the role of chest CT in prevention and disease control. &lt;i&gt;A full translation of this article in Chinese is available.&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-21
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32084676&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Standardized diagnosis and treatment of colorectal cancer during the outbreak of novel coronavirus pneumonia in Renji hospital].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Referring to the “Diagnosis and Treatment Scheme for NCP (Trial Version 4 and 5)” and combining the actual practice situation in our hospital with the “Summary of New Coronavirus Files of Shanghai Renji Hospital”, we summarize how to carry out the clinical practice of colorectal surgery under the situation of the prevention and control of the NCP epidemiology, meanwhile under such situation aiming the procedure of diagnose and treatment for emergency patients with colorectal tumor, we share the experiences of the diagnosis of colorectal tumor, the management of patients with colorectal cancer who are scheduled to be admitted for surgery, the protection of wards, the perioperative management.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-02-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32092296&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus (COVID-19) Outbreak: What the Department of Radiology Should Know.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The purpose of the present review is to briefly discuss the known epidemiology and the imaging findings of coronavirus syndromes, with a focus on the reported imaging findings of NCIP.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32098422&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Systematic Comparison of Two Animal-to-Human Transmitted Human Coronaviruses: SARS-CoV-2 and SARS-CoV.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There are some similarities and differences in the epidemiology and clinical features between these two viruses and diseases that are caused by these viruses.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32105049&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Novel coronavirus COVID-19: an overview for emergency clinicians&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, the epidemiology, pathophysiology, and management of the recently discovered COVID-19 are reviewed, with a focus onbest practices and the public health implications.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32105680&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) and pregnancy: what obstetricians need to know.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Currently the primary epidemiologic risk factors for coronavirus disease 2019 include travel from mainland China (especially Hubei Province) or close contact with infected individuals within 14 days of symptom onset.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32113704&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The epidemiology and pathogenesis of coronavirus disease (COVID-19) outbreak.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we highlights the symptoms, epidemiology, transmission, pathogenesis, phylogenetic analysis and future directions to control the spread of this fatal disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32118389&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Clinical analysis of 31 cases of 2019 novel coronavirus infection in children from six provinces (autonomous region) of northern China].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Close contact history of epidemiology, nucleic acid detection and chest imaging are important bases for diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32125362&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiologic Features and Clinical Course of Patients Infected With SARS-CoV-2 in Singapore.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To report the initial experience in Singapore with the epidemiologic investigation of this outbreak, clinical features, and management.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32133832&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[WITHDRAWN: Potential false-positive rate among the ‘asymptomatic infected individuals’ in close contacts of COVID-19 patients].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Questions from the readers mainly focused on the article’s results and conclusions were depended on theoretical deduction, but not the field epidemiology data and further researches were needed to prove the current theory.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32133833&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[The differential diagnosis of pulmonary infiltrates in cancer patients during the outbreak of the 2019 novel coronavirus disease].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Information of clinical manifestations, history of epidemiology, lab tests and chest CT scan images of visiting patients from February 13 to February 28 were collected.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32138266&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Potential Factors Influencing Repeated SARS Outbreaks in China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
These natural and social factors influenced the general progression and trajectory of the SARS epidemiology.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32138488&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The 2019 Novel Coronavirus Outbreak - A Global Threat.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There are significant knowledge gaps in the epidemiology, transmission dynamics, investigation tools and management.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32141569&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 (Novel Coronavirus 2019) - recent trends.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 is similar to Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome coronavirus (SARS-CoV) virus in its pathogenicity, clinical spectrum, and epidemiology.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32145185&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Middle East respiratory syndrome.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This Seminar provides an update on the current knowledge and perspectives on MERS epidemiology, virology, mode of transmission, pathogenesis, diagnosis, clinical features, management, infection control, development of new therapeutics and vaccines, and highlights unanswered questions and priorities for research, improved management, and prevention.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32145718&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Healing the schism between public health and medicine, promoting the integration of prevention and treatment].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The &lt;i&gt;‘Healing the Schism: Epidemiology, Medicine, and the Public’s Health’&lt;/i&gt; by professor Kerr L.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32150748&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Incubation Period of Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) From Publicly Reported Confirmed Cases: Estimation and Application.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There is limited support for many of its key epidemiologic features, including the incubation period for clinical disease (coronavirus disease 2019 [COVID-19]), which has important implications for surveillance and control activities.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32161092&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The emergence of a novel coronavirus (SARS-CoV-2), their biology and therapeutic options.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this Review, we summarize current information about the emergence, origin, diversity, and epidemiology of three pathogenic coronaviruses with a specific focus on the current outbreak in Wuhan, China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-12
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32168465&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology of 2019 Novel Coronavirus Disease-19 in Gansu Province, China, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To determine the epidemiology of 2019 novel coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in a remote region of China, far from Wuhan, we analyzed the epidemiology of COVID-19 in Gansu Province.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32169119&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The origin, transmission and clinical therapies on coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) outbreak - an update on the status.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we summarized the latest research progress of the epidemiology, pathogenesis, and clinical characteristics of COVID-19, and discussed the current treatment and scientific advancements to combat the epidemic novel coronavirus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32170865&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus disease 2019: What we know?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The purpose of this review is primarily to review the pathogen, clinical features, diagnosis, and treatment of COVID-19, but also to comment briefly on the epidemiology and pathology based on the current evidence.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32171869&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical progression of patients with COVID-19 in Shanghai, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Studies on the 2019 novel coronavirus disease (COVID-19) have generally been limited to the description of the epidemiology and initial clinical characteristics.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32171952&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The SARS-CoV-2 outbreak: what we know.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This paper aggregates and consolidates the epidemiology, clinical manifestations, diagnosis, treatments and preventions of this new type of coronavirus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32172228&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Potential preanalytical and analytical vulnerabilities in the laboratory diagnosis of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Some practical indications can hence be identified for minimizing the risk of diagnostic errors, encompassing the improvement of diagnostic accuracy by combining clinical evidence with results of chest computed tomography (CT) and RT-PCR, interpretation of RT-PCR results according to epidemiologic, clinical and radiological factors, recollection and testing of upper (or lower) respiratory specimens in patients with negative RT-PCR test results and high suspicion or probability of infection, dissemination of clear instructions for specimen (especially swab) collection, management and storage, together with refinement of molecular target(s) and thorough compliance with analytical procedures, including quality assurance.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32174069&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Report on the Epidemiological Features of Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) Outbreak in the Republic of Korea from January 19 to March 2, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This report summarizes the epidemiologic features and the snapshots of the outbreak in the Republic of Korea from January 19 and March 2, 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32180175&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Safety and efficacy of different anesthetic regimens for parturients with COVID-19 undergoing Cesarean delivery: a case series of 17 patients.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Their epidemiologic history, chest computed tomography scans, laboratory measurements, and SARS-CoV-2 nucleic acid positivity were evaluated.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32181807&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiologic and Clinical Characteristics of 91 Hospitalized Patients with COVID-19 in Zhejiang, China: A retrospective, multi-centre case series.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Recent studies have focused initial clinical and Epidemiologic characteristics on the COVID-19, mainly revealing situation in Wuhan, Hubei. […] To reveal more data on the epidemiologic and clinical characteristics of COVID-19 patients outside of Wuhan, in Zhejiang, China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32183901&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology, causes, clinical manifestation and diagnosis, prevention and control of coronavirus disease (COVID-19) during the early outbreak period: a scoping review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this scoping review, 65 research articles published before 31 January 2020 were analyzed and discussed to better understand the epidemiology, causes, clinical diagnosis, prevention and control of this virus. […] During this early period, published research primarily explored the epidemiology, causes, clinical manifestation and diagnosis, as well as prevention and control of the novel coronavirus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32187007&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Identifying and Interrupting Superspreading Events-Implications for Control of Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Although we still have limited information on the epidemiology of this virus, there have been multiple reports of superspreading events (SSEs), which are associated with both explosive growth early in an outbreak and sustained transmission in later stages.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32190908&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A doubt of multiple introduction of SARS-CoV-2 in Italy: A preliminary overview.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Nevertheless, there is limited information about the genomic epidemiology of SARS-CoV-2 circulating in Italy from surveillance studies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32191623&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The critical role of laboratory medicine during coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) and other viral outbreaks.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
These include etiological diagnosis, patient monitoring, as well as epidemiologic surveillance.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32192296&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Standardized diagnosis and treatment of colorectal cancer during the outbreak of corona virus disease 2019 in Renji hospital].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Although colorectal surgery is not a front-line subject in the fight against the epidemic, but in this special situation, it is a difficult task to provide the highest quality medical services and ensure the orderly clinical work, on the premise of maximizing the protection for patients and their families, health of medical staff, and the safety of wards and hospitals, We summarize how to carry out the clinical practice of colorectal surgery under the situation of the prevention and control of the COVID-19 epidemiology, including the procedures of diagnose and treatment for emergency patients with colorectal tumor, and share the experiences of the diagnosis of colorectal tumor, the management of patients with colorectal cancer who are scheduled to be admitted for surgery, the protection of wards, the perioperative management.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32193905&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;First Pediatric Case of Coronavirus Disease 2019 in Korea.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Current epidemiologic knowledge suggests that relatively few cases are seen among children, which limits opportunities to address pediatric specific issues on infection control and the children’s contribution to viral spread in the community.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32194034&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;How Should the Rehabilitation Community Prepare for 2019-nCoV?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
With the novel coronavirus 2019 (2019-nCoV) pandemic spreading quickly in the United States and the world, it is urgent that the rehabilitation community quickly understands the epidemiology of the virus and what we can and must do to face this microbial adversary at the early stages of this likely long global pandemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32198834&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Case report of COVID-19 in a kidney transplant recipient: Does immunosuppression alter the clinical presentation?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 is novel infectious disease with an evolving understanding of its epidemiology and clinical manifestations.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32201353&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A review of the 2019 Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19) based on current evidence.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Based on the current published evidence, we systematically summarizes the epidemiology, clinical characteristics, diagnosis, treatment and prevention of knowledge surrounding COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32205349&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Updated approaches against SARS-CoV-2.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There is a growing understanding of SARS-CoV-2 in the virology, epidemiology and clinical management strategies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-24
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32207910&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Novel 2019 coronavirus SARS-CoV-2 (COVID-19): An updated overview for emergency clinicians&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This overview analyzes the best information from the early research, including epidemiologic and demographic features from SARS-CoV-1 and MERS-CoV viruses; lessons learned from the experience of an emergency physician in Northern Italy, where the outbreak has devastated the healthcare system; evidence on transmission and prevention through safe use of PPE; evidence and advice on SARS-CoV-2 testing and co-infection; management options; airway management options; steps for rapid sequence intubation in the ED and managing disaster ventilation; and information on managing pediatric and pregnant patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32214083&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 in a Long-Term Care Facility - King County, Washington, February 27-March 9, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Epidemiologic investigation of facility A identified 129 cases of COVID-19 associated with facility A, including 81 of the residents, 34 staff members, and 14 visitors; 23 persons died.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32217506&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Role of the Global Health Development/Eastern Mediterranean Public Health Network and the Eastern Mediterranean Field Epidemiology Training Programs in Preparedness for COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This viewpoint article aims to highlight the contribution of the Global Health Development (GHD)/Eastern Mediterranean Public Health Network (EMPHNET) and the EMR’s Field Epidemiology Training Program (FETPs) to prepare for and respond to the current COVID-19 threat.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32217947&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Perioperative COVID-19 Defense: An Evidence-Based Approach for Optimization of Infection Control and Operating Room Management.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
These 8 programmatic recommendations stand on a substantial body of empirical evidence characterizing the epidemiology of perioperative transmission and infection development made possible by support from the Anesthesia Patient Safety Foundation (APSF).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-03-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32220177&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Epidemiology, Treatment, and Epidemic Prevention and Control of the Coronavirus Disease 2019: a Review].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This review summarizes the ongoing researches regarding etiology, epidemiology, transmission dynamics, treatment, and prevention and control strategies of the coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) caused by severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2), with comparison to severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus (SARS-CoV), Middle East respiratory syndrome coronavirus (MERS-CoV) and pandemic H1N1 virus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32226288&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Traditional Chinese Medicine in the Treatment of Patients Infected with 2019-New Coronavirus (SARS-CoV-2): A Review and Perspective.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Due to the homology in epidemiology, genomics, and pathogenesis of the SARS-CoV-2 and SARS-CoV, and the widely use of TCM in the treatment of SARS-CoV, the clinical evidence showing the beneficial effect of TCM in the treatment of patients with SARS coronaviral infections are discussed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32226289&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Perspectives on therapeutic neutralizing antibodies against the Novel Coronavirus SARS-CoV-2.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Epidemiology, genomics, and pathogenesis of the SARS-CoV-2 show high homology with that of SARS-CoV.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32226295&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19: what has been learned and to be learned about the novel coronavirus disease.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We will cover the basics about the epidemiology, etiology, virology, diagnosis, treatment, prognosis, and prevention of the disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32228809&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Asymptomatic and Human-to-Human Transmission of SARS-CoV-2 in a 2-Family Cluster, Xuzhou, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We report epidemiologic, laboratory, and clinical findings for 7 patients with 2019 novel coronavirus disease in a 2-family cluster.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32229157&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Practical Strategies Against the Novel Coronavirus and COVID-19-the Imminent Global Threat.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Hopefully, cumulative data using whole-genome sequencing of the SARS-CoV-2 genome in parallel with mathematical modeling will help the molecular biologists to understand unknown features of the pathogenesis and epidemiology of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32230900&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Virology, Epidemiology, Pathogenesis, and Control of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Scientific advancements since the pandemic of severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS) in 2002~2003 and Middle East respiratory syndrome (MERS) in 2012 have accelerated our understanding of the epidemiology and pathogenesis of SARS-CoV-2 and the development of therapeutics to treat viral infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32232980&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 epidemic: Disease characteristics in children.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Although information regarding the epidemiology of COVID-19 in children has accumulated, relevant comprehensive reports are lacking.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32233876&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Role of Emergency Radiology in COVID-19: From Preparedness to Diagnosis.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We review the symptoms, epidemiology, and testing for this disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32234107&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiologic Features of 135 Patients With Coronavirus Disease (COVID-19) in Tianjin, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This study describes the epidemiologic features of an outbreak of the coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in Tianjin caused by a novel coronavirus and provides the scientific basis for prevention and control measures.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32234451&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19, SARS and MERS: are they closely related?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We provide a review of the differences in terms of pathogenesis, epidemiology and clinical features between COVID-19, SARS and MERS.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32234468&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The epidemiology, diagnosis and treatment of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This paper reviews the literature on all available information about the epidemiology, diagnosis, isolation and treatments of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32236624&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A new threat from an old enemy: Re‑emergence of coronavirus (Review).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In the present review, we address current knowledge on coronaviruses from a short history to epidemiology, pathogenesis, clinical manifestation of the disease, as well as treatment and prevention strategies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32238757&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Current Status of Epidemiology, Diagnosis, Therapeutics, and Vaccines for Novel Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here, we review the current status of epidemiology, diagnosis, treatment, and vaccine development for COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32239446&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Rapid Assessment and Early Warning Models for COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This would significantly improve global surveillance capacity, particularly in developing regions, and improve basic training in infectious diseases and molecular epidemiology.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32240973&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Peer-to-Peer Contact Tracing: Development of a Privacy-Preserving Smartphone App.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The novel coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) pandemic is an urgent public health crisis, with epidemiologic models predicting severe consequences, including high death rates, if the virus is permitted to run its course without any intervention or response.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32241316&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Case Report on Early Diagnosis of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Based on the analysis of the cases of 4 patients, this article finds that early diagnosis requires a combination of epidemiology, clinical manifestations, imaging, and etiology, with particular emphasis on epidemiology history and chest CT manifestations.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32247050&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Insight into 2019 novel coronavirus - an updated intrim review and lessons from SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Based on recently published literatures, official documents and selected up-to-date preprint studies, we reviewed the virology and origin, epidemiology, clinical manifestations, pathology and treatment of 2019-nCoV infection, in comparison with severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus (SARS-CoV) and middle east respiratory syndrome coronavirus (MERS-CoV) infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32247326&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Evolving epidemiology and transmission dynamics of coronavirus disease 2019 outside Hubei province, China: a descriptive and modelling study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Understanding the evolving epidemiology and transmission dynamics of the outbreak beyond Hubei would provide timely information to guide intervention policy.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32250957&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Tracking COVID-19 in Europe: An Infodemiology Study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Infodemiology, i.e. information epidemiology, uses Web-based data in order to inform public health and policy.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32252338&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Evidence that Vitamin D Supplementation Could Reduce Risk of Influenza and COVID-19 Infections and Deaths.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This article reviews the roles of vitamin D in reducing the risk of respiratory tract infections, knowledge about the epidemiology of influenza and COVID-19, and how vitamin D supplementation might be a useful measure to reduce risk.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32255761&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;High Contagiousness and Rapid Spread of Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We collected extensive individual case reports across China and estimated key epidemiologic parameters, including the incubation period.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32259119&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Daily Situation Report on Coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in Iran; March 14, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After detection of the first confirmed cases of COVID-19 in Iran, the National Committee on COVID-19 Epidemiology in Ministry of Health and Medical Education was established.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32259120&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Daily Situation Report on Coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in Iran; March 15, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After detection of the first confirmed cases of COVID-19 in Iran, the National Committee on COVID-19 Epidemiology in Ministry of Health and Medical Education was established.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32259121&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Daily Situation Report on Coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in Iran; March 16, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After detection of the first confirmed cases of COVID-19 in Iran, the National Committee on COVID-19 Epidemiology in Ministry of Health and Medical Education was established.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32259126&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Daily Situation Report on Coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in Iran; March 23, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After detection of the first confirmed cases of COVID-19 in Iran, the National Committee on COVID-19 Epidemiology in Ministry of Health and Medical Education was established.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32259127&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Daily Situation Report on Coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in Iran; March 25, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After detection of the first confirmed cases of COVID-19 in Iran, the National Committee on COVID-19 Epidemiology in Ministry of Health and Medical Education was established.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32259829&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Outbreak: An Overview.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we summarize the current knowledge about the epidemiology, phylogenesis, homology modeling, and molecular diagnostics of SARS-CoV-2.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32267220&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2-Specific Antibody Responses in Coronavirus Disease 2019 Patients.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Validated serologic assays are needed for contact tracing, identifying the viral reservoir, and epidemiologic studies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32268855&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19, Australia: Epidemiology Report 10 (Reporting week to 23:59 AEST 5 April 2020).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The epidemiology differs from country to country depending not only on the disease, but also on differences in case detection, testing and implemented public health measures.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32271460&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus disease 2019: a bibliometric analysis and review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
68 (37.2%) epidemiology, 49 (26.8%) virology and 26 (14.2%) clinical features.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32271601&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology and Clinical Characteristics of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we summarize the epidemiology and characteristics of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32271602&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Improved Early Recognition of Coronavirus Disease-2019 (COVID-19): Single-Center Data from a Shanghai Screening Hospital.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To clarify the early epidemiology and clinical characteristics about COVID-19. […] Epidemiology, demography, clinical, laboratory and chest CTs were collected and analyzed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32271722&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Presymptomatic Transmission of SARS-CoV-2 - Singapore, January 23-March 16, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Clinical and epidemiologic findings of all COVID-19 cases in Singapore through March 16 were reviewed to determine whether presymptomatic transmission might have occurred. […] Seven COVID-19 epidemiologic clusters in which presymptomatic transmission likely occurred were identified, and 10 such cases within these clusters accounted for 6.4% of the 157 locally acquired cases.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32271724&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Rapid Sentinel Surveillance for COVID-19 - Santa Clara County, California, March 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
At the time the investigation began, testing guidance recommended focusing on persons with clinical findings of lower respiratory illness and travel to an affected area or an epidemiologic link to a laboratory-confirmed COVID-19 case, or on persons hospitalized for severe respiratory disease and no alternative diagnosis (1). […] Sentinel surveillance in outpatient settings and emergency departments, implemented together with hospital-based surveillance, mortality surveillance, and serologic surveys, can provide a robust approach to monitor the epidemiology of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32272173&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus membrane fusion mechanism offers as a potential target for antiviral development.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We also provide a supplemental file containing background information on the biology, epidemiology, and clinical features of all human-infecting coronaviruses, along with a phylogenetic tree of these coronaviruses.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32272262&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;High-resolution Chest CT Features and Clinical Characteristics of Patients Infected with COVID-19 in Jiangsu, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Most patients (approximately 90%) were classified as common type and with epidemiologic history. […] Clinical performances of patients with COVID-19, mostly with epidemiologic history and typical symptoms, were critical valuable in the diagnosis of the COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-11
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32272857&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Role of Tissue Engineering in COVID-19 and Future Viral Outbreaks.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This work introduces the basics of virology and epidemiology for tissue engineers, and highlights important developments in the field of tissue engineering relevant to the current pandemic, including &lt;i&gt;in vitro&lt;/i&gt; model systems, vaccine technology, and small-molecule drug delivery.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32273156&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Disease 19 (COVID-19): Implications for Clinical Dental Care.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Thus, the aim of this article is to provide a brief overview of the epidemiology, symptoms, and routes of transmission of this novel infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32274617&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SARS-CoV-2 and COVID-19 in older adults: what we may expect regarding pathogenesis, immune responses, and outcomes.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here, we briefly review the virus, its structure and evolution, epidemiology and pathogenesis, immunogenicity and immune, and clinical response in older adults, using available knowledge on SARS-CoV-2 and its highly pathogenic relatives MERS-CoV and SARS-CoV-1.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-10
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32275259&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SARS-CoV-2, SARS-CoV, and MERS-COV: A comparative overview&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
So, this review aims at understanding the new scenario of SARS-CoV-2 outbreak and compares the epidemiology, clinical presentations, and the genetics of these coronaviruses.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32278065&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diarrhea during COVID-19 infection: pathogenesis, epidemiology, prevention and management.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here we investigate the epidemiology, clinical presentation, molecular mechanisms, management, and prevention of SARS-CoV-2 associated diarrhea.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32283894&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SARS-CoV-2 Epidemiology and Control, Different Scenarios for Turkey.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The epidemiology and control in different countries was compared and the differences discussed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32286766&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Novel 2019 coronavirus SARS-CoV-2 (COVID-19): an overview for emergency clinicians.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This review analyzes information from worldwide research and experience on the epidemiology, prevention, and treatment of COVID-19, and offers links to the most reliable and trustworthy resources to help equip healthcare professionals in managing this public health challenge.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32290293&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A Review of SARS-CoV-2 and the Ongoing Clinical Trials.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this article, we present a succinct overview of the epidemiology, clinical features, and molecular characteristics of SARS-CoV-2.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32290644&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical and epidemiologic profile of the initial COVID-19 patients at a tertiary care centre in India.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The objective of this work is to report the initial experience with epidemiologic and clinical features, as well as with the management of COVID-19 patients in India.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32292587&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Mutated COVID-19, May Foretells Mankind in a Great Risk in the Future.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Our study aimed to present an overview of the virus in terms of structure, epidemiology, symptoms, treatment, and prevention.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32292848&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 for the Cardiologist: A Current Review of the Virology, Clinical Epidemiology, Cardiac and Other Clinical Manifestations and Potential Therapeutic Strategies.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We discuss the basic virology, epidemiology, clinical manifestation, multi-organ consequences, and outcomes.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32292911&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;1,000,000 cases of COVID-19 outside of China: The date predicted by a simple heuristic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Prediction, forecast, pandemic, COVID-19, coronavirus, exponential growth curve parameter, heuristic, epidemiology, extrapolation, abductive reasoning, WHO situa- tion report.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32294816&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Bronchoalveolar lavage fluid was used to diagnose two cases of 2019-nCoV infection].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The case reports 2 cases of novel coronavirus pneumonia diagnosed by concurrent bronchoalveolar lavage in our hospital, 1 case had a history of epidemiology, clinical symptoms and high imaging suspicion, but repeated negative throat swabs.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32295188&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Diseases (COVID-19) Current Status and Future Perspectives: A Narrative Review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We performed a narrative review to describe existing literature with regard to Corona Virus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) epidemiology, pathophysiology, diagnosis, management and future perspective.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-21
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32295322&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Clinical analysis of 150 cases of 2019 novel coronavirus infection in Nanyang City, Henan Province].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To analyze the epidemiological characteristics and clinical features of the patients with 2019-nCoV infection in Nanyang City, so as to provide evidence for clinical diagnosis and treatment. &lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; The epidemiology, clinical symptoms, atory and radiologic data of 150 patients with 2019-nCoV infection admitted to the designated hospitals in Nanyang City from January 24,2020 to February 16, 2020 were retrospectively analyzed. &lt;b&gt;Results:&lt;/b&gt; The 150 patients with 2019 nCov infection consisted of 67 men and 83 women, and the median age was 45±16 years; 69 of them were the first generation case,60 of them were the second generation case, 6 of them were the third generation case,the median incubation period of the first generation case was 5.4±2.2 days, and the second generation case was 6.7±3.1 days, and the first-generation cases are the majority in severe patients (69%) .
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32296837&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology of seasonal coronaviruses: Establishing the context for COVID-19 emergence.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here we describe the epidemiology of seasonal coronaviruses (sCoVs) and other cocirculating viruses in the West of Scotland, UK.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32297868&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Global Preparedness Against COVID-19: We Must Leverage the Power of Digital Health.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We provide several use cases for infection control, home-based diagnosis and screening, empowerment through information, public health surveillance and epidemiology, and leveraging crowd-sourced data.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-21
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32298250&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Geographic Differences in COVID-19 Cases, Deaths, and Incidence - United States, February 12-April 7, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Geographic differences in numbers of COVID-19 cases and deaths, cumulative incidence, and changes in incidence likely reflect a combination of jurisdiction-specific epidemiologic and population-level factors, including 1) the timing of COVID-19 introductions; 2) population density; 3) age distribution and prevalence of underlying medical conditions among COVID-19 patients (1-3); 4) the timing and extent of community mitigation measures; 5) diagnostic testing capacity; and 6) public health reporting practices.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-17
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32298251&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hospitalization Rates and Characteristics of Patients Hospitalized with Laboratory-Confirmed Coronavirus Disease 2019 - COVID-NET, 14 States, March 1-30, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Ongoing monitoring of hospitalization rates, clinical characteristics, and outcomes of hospitalized patients will be important to better understand the evolving epidemiology of COVID-19 in the United States and the clinical spectrum of disease, and to help guide planning and prioritization of health care system resources.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32298803&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Are we facing a crashing wave of neuropsychiatric sequelae of COVID-19? Neuropsychiatric symptoms and potential immunologic mechanisms.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Therefore, prospective neuropsychiatric monitoring of individuals exposed to SARS-CoV-2 at various points in the life course, as well as their neuroimmune status, are needed to fully understand the long-term impact of COVID-19, and to establish a framework for integrating psychoneuroimmunology into epidemiologic studies of pandemics.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-24
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32299330&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19, Australia: Epidemiology Report 11 (Reporting week to 23:59 AEST 12 April 2020).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The epidemiology differs from country to country depending not only on the disease, but also on differences in case detection, testing and implemented public health measures.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-21
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32301600&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A review of initial data on pregnancy during the COVID-19 outbreak: implications for assisted reproductive treatments.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we summarize the latest research progress related to COVID-19 epidemiology and the reported data of pregnant women, and discuss the current evidence of COVID-19 infections during pregnancy and its potential consequences for assisted reproductive treatments.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32304371&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Public health literacy in the face of the Covid-19 pandemic emergency].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Some of these elements are: a) epidemiologic intelligence.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32305884&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology and clinical features of COVID-19: A review of current literature.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Studies are rapidly published to share information regarding epidemiology, clinical and diagnostic patterns, and prognosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32308494&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiologic and Clinical Characteristics of 26 Cases of COVID-19 Arising from Patient-to-Patient Transmission in Liaocheng, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Most studies to date on COVID-19 have focused on disease etiology and the genomics of 2019-nCoV, with few reports on the epidemiologic and clinical characteristics of infected patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32309679&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Clinical Trials: A Primer for the Cardiovascular and Cardio-Oncology Communities.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here we have provided a foundation for cardiovascular and cardio-oncology physicians who are on the frontline providing care to COVID-19 patients, so that they can better understand the emerging cardiovascular epidemiology of COVID-19, as well as the biological rationale for the clinical trials that are ongoing for the treatment of COVID-19 patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-31
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32309796&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Early epidemiological analysis of the coronavirus disease 2019 outbreak based on crowdsourced data: a population-level observational study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We assessed trends in the epidemiology of COVID-19 and studied the outbreak progression across China, assessing delays between symptom onset, seeking care at a hospital or clinic, and reporting, before and after Jan 18, 2020, as awareness of the outbreak increased.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32310621&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Infections in Children Including COVID-19: An Overview of the Epidemiology, Clinical Features, Diagnosis, Treatment and Prevention Options in Children.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we summarize epidemiologic, clinical and diagnostic findings, as well as treatment and prevention options for common circulating and novel CoVs infections in humans with a focus on infections in children.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-24
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32311448&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 and Thrombotic or Thromboembolic Disease: Implications for Prevention, Antithrombotic Therapy, and Follow-up.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Herein, we review the current understanding of the pathogenesis, epidemiology, management and outcomes of patients with COVID-19 who develop venous or arterial thrombosis, and of those with preexisting thrombotic disease who develop COVID-19, or those who need prevention or care for their thrombotic disease during the COVID-19 pandemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32311650&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical features and short-term outcomes of 221 patients with COVID-19 in Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We aimed to study the epidemiology, clinical features and short-term outcomes of patients with COVID-19 in Wuhan, China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32313804&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Tracing New Clinical Manifestations in Patients with COVID-19 in Chile and Its Potential Relationship with the SARS-CoV-2 Divergence.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we discuss the current implications of the changing genomic epidemiology of the Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2), etiological agent of the Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) and its potential relationship with the change of clinical manifestations in patients with confirmed infection. […] SARS-CoV-2/COVID-19 is changing not only its epidemiology, but also its genomic diversity and clinical manifestations, both aspects coupled, needs to be considered in the study of this ongoing pandemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32313824&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus as silent killer: recent advancement to pathogenesis, therapeutic strategy and future perspectives.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we are tried to explore the epidemiology, pathogenesis and current treatment of CoVs infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32313885&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Clinical Trials: A Primer for the Cardiovascular and Cardio-Oncology Communities.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here we have provided a foundation for cardiovascular and cardio-oncology physicians who are on the frontline providing care to COVID-19 patients, so that they can better understand the emerging cardiovascular epidemiology of COVID-19, as well as the biological rationale for the clinical trials that are ongoing for the treatment of COVID-19 patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32314081&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Pharmacologic Therapy for COVID-19 Infection.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The COVID-19 pandemic has focused attention on issues of epidemiology, public health, and vaccine design.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32314790&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;What’s New With the Old Coronaviruses?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we discuss what is known about the virology, epidemiology, and disease associated with pediatric infection with the common community-acquired human coronaviruses, including species 229E, OC43, NL63, and HKU1, and the coronaviruses responsible for past world-wide epidemics due to severe acute respiratory syndrome and Middle East respiratory syndrome coronavirus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32315723&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Current epidemiological and clinical features of COVID-19; a global perspective from China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Based on the published data, this review systematically discusses the etiology, epidemiology, clinical characteristics, and current intervention measures related to COVID-19 in the hope that it may provide a reference for future studies and aid in the prevention and control of the COVID-19 epidemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32320004&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) Infection in Children and Adolescents: A Systematic Review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The risk of bias for eligible observational studies was assessed according to the Strengthening the Reporting of Observational Studies in Epidemiology reporting guideline. […] The rapid spread of COVID-19 across the globe and the lack of European and US data on pediatric patients require further epidemiologic and clinical studies to identify possible preventive and therapeutic strategies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32321116&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Diagnostic and Management Protocol for Pediatric Patients.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This review aims to verify the main epidemiologic, clinical, laboratory-related, and therapeutic aspects of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) in critically ill pediatric patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32322400&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology, genome, and clinical features of the pandemic SARS-CoV-2: a recent view.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Various reports have suggested an &lt;i&gt;in vivo&lt;/i&gt; evolution of the virus, which may explain the rapid spread and changing epidemiology of SARS-CoV-2, but further evidence is needed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32322475&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Defending against the Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19) Outbreak: How Can the Internet of Things (IoT) help to save the World?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
•IoT within infectious disease epidemiology is an emerging field of research, however the ubiquitous availability of smart technologies, as well as increased risks of infectious disease spread through the globalization and interconnectedness of the world necessitates its use for predicting, preventing and controlling emerging infectious diseases•Considering the present situation in China, IoT based smart disease surveillance systems have the potential to be a major breakthrough in efforts to control the current pandemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32324209&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Association of Renin-Angiotensin System Inhibitors With Severity or Risk of Death in Patients With Hypertension Hospitalized for Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) Infection in Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 was confirmed by real-time reverse transcription-polymerase chain reaction and epidemiologic, clinical, radiologic, laboratory, and drug therapy data were analyzed in all patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32324359&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnostic consideration and bedside estimation of the prognosis in COVID-19 patients&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We also cite the current national epidemiologic regulations of testing for novel coronavirus. […] In addition to the epidemiologic interventions aiming the deceleration of the outbreak, the early identification and the correct hospital treatment remain key issues since these may influence mortality.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32324530&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Disease Outbreak in Call Center, South Korea.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We describe the epidemiology of a coronavirus disease (COVID-19) outbreak in a call center in South Korea. […] We obtained information on demographic characteristics by using standardized epidemiologic investigation forms.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32327901&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SBDiEM: A new Mathematical model of Infectious Disease Dynamics.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Hence, rigorous mathematical epidemiology models can be utilized to combat epidemic outbreaks.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32328595&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Dental care during the coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) outbreak: operatory considerations and clinical aspects.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The epidemiology, clinical signs and symptoms, and modes of transmission of COVID-19 are presented.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32329275&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[An analysis of global research on SARS-CoV-2].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
All articles were categorized into epidemiology, clinical diagnosis and treatment, basic research, pregnant women and children, mental health, epidemic prevention &amp;amp; control, and others.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32329877&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SARS-CoV-2 causing pneumonia-associated respiratory disorder (COVID-19): diagnostic and proposed therapeutic options.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Moreover, the review discusses different aspects of the COVID-19, including its epidemiology; incubation period; the general clinical features of patients; the clinical features of intensive care unit (ICU) patients; SARS-CoV-2 infection in the presence of co-morbid diseases and the clinical features of pediatric patients infected with the SARS-CoV-2.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32331509&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hospital preparedness for COVID-19 pandemic: experience from department of medicine at Veterans Affairs Connecticut Healthcare System.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
According to epidemiologic predictions, the peak of this pandemic has still not been reached, and hospitals everywhere need to ensure readiness to care for more patients than they usually do, and safety for healthcare workers who strive to save lives.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32335628&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Air Medical Evacuation of Nepalese Citizen During Epidemic of COVID-19 from Wuhan to Nepal.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
With the help of Health Emergency Organizing committee, Epidemiology and Disease Control Division, Nepal Army Hospital, Nepal Police Hospital, Waste Management team, Nepal Ambulance service, Tribhuwan Airport and Royal Airlines the government of Nepal planned, organized and successfully brought back all the 175 students on 15 the February, 2019 from Wuhan, China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32335749&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;How Could This Happen? : Narrowing Down the Contagion of COVID-19 and Preventing Acute Respiratory Distress Syndrome (ARDS).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this rapid commentary, a mini-review is given of the present state-of-knowledge regarding the etiology and epidemiology of the new coronavirus 2019-nCoV and the risks for developing Acute respiratory distress syndrome (ARDS).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32336802&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Fix the Supply Side! Demand Stimulus Will Not Cure What Ails].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The German Society for Epidemiology has warned that the number of cases could soon overshoot the capacity of the healthcare system.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32336927&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2): Emergence, History, Basic and Clinical Aspects.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This review article summarizes the developing situation surrounding the SARS-CoV-2 pandemic with respect to its epidemiology, unique genomic structure, possible origins, transmission, pathogenesis, comparison with other deadly species of Coronaviruses (CoV) and emerging treatment strategies built on informed literature.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32336957&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Combination of Biodata Mining and Computational Modelling in Identification and Characterization of ORF1ab Polyprotein of SARS-CoV-2 Isolated from Oronasopharynx of an Iranian Patient.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Iran is one of the top ranked countries in the tables of COVID-19-infected and -mortality cases that make the Iranian patients as the potential targets for diversity of studies including epidemiology, biomedical, biodata, and viral proteins computational modelling studies. […] The results revealed that nsp1 as a virulence factor and crucial agent in spreading of the COVID-19 among the society can be a potential target for the future epidemiology, drug, and vaccine studies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32336959&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SARS-CoV-2 (COVID-19) and intravascular volume management strategies in the critically ill.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
While knowledge regarding epidemiologic features and diagnostic tools of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) is rapidly evolving, uncertainties surrounding various aspects of its optimal management strategies persist.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32337131&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Focus on Mental Health During the Coronavirus (COVID-19) Pandemic: Applying Learnings from the Past Outbreaks.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
However, the unpreparedness of the nations, even with the advanced medical sciences and resources, has failed to address the mental health aspect amongst the public, as all efforts are focused on understanding the epidemiology, clinical features, transmission patterns, and management of COVID-19 pneumonia.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32339231&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiological characteristics and incubation period of 7,015 confirmed cases with Coronavirus Disease 2019 outside Hubei Province in China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We utilized confirmed cases outside Hubei Province to analyze epidemiologic characteristics and evaluate the effect of traffic restrictions implemented in Hubei beginning on January 23, 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32339662&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Addressing the Impact of the Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) Pandemic on Hematopoietic Cell Transplantation: Learning Networks as a Means for Sharing Best Practices.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This perspective paper reviews the following: current COVID-19 epidemiology, diagnosis, and potential therapies; care considerations unique to HCT recipients; and the concept of a learning network to assimilate emerging guidelines and best practices and to optimize patient outcomes through facilitating shared learning and experience across transplantation centers.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32340833&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19): A literature review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this literature review, the causative agent, pathogenesis and immune responses, epidemiology, diagnosis, treatment and management of the disease, control and preventions strategies are all reviewed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32343514&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Staffing with disease-based epidemiologic indices may reduce shortage of intensive care unit staff during the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In the light of lacking evidence for optimal staffing models in a pandemic, we hypothesized that staff shortage can be reduced when staff scheduling takes the epidemiology of a disease epidemic into account. […] Staffing along epidemiologic considerations may reduce HCW shortage by leveling the nadir from affected workforce.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32343939&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19, Australia: Epidemiology Report 12 (Reporting week to 23:59 AEST 19 April 2020).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Interpretation of international epidemiology should be conducted with caution as it differs from country to country depending not only on the disease dynamics, but also on differences in case detection, testing and implemented public health measures.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32345446&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Otolaryngology during COVID-19: Preventive care and precautionary measures.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Literatures on the epidemiology, clinical characteristics and infection control measures of COVID-19 were reviewed, practical knowledge from first-line otolaryngologists in China, the United States, and Brazil were reviewed and collated.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-03
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32347204&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Serological assays for severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2), March 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Heparinised plasma appeared to reduce the infectivity of the virus challenge dose and may confound interpretation of neutralisation test.ConclusionUsing IgG ELISA based on the RBD of the spike protein to screen sera for SARS-CoV-2 antibody, followed by confirmation using PRNT&lt;sub&gt;90&lt;/sub&gt;, is a valid approach for large-scale sero-epidemiology studies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32347685&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Neurosurgical activity during COVID-19 pandemic: an expert opinion from China, South Korea, Italy, United Stated of America, Colombia and United Kingdom.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The first part focused on the epidemiology until that date.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32347772&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;National Response to COVID-19 in the Republic of Korea and Lessons Learned for Other Countries.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Facilitators included existing hospital capacity, the epidemiology of the COVID-19 outbreak, and strong national leadership despite political changes and population sensitization due to the 2015 Middle East respiratory syndrome-related coronavirus (MERS-CoV) epidemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32348554&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Global reporting of cases of COVID-19 in psoriasis and atopic dermatitis: an opportunity to inform care during a pandemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We wish to bring your attention to the PsoPROTECT (Psoriasis Patient Registry for Outcomes, Therapy and Epidemiology of Covid-19 infecTion) and SECURE-AD (Surveillance Epidemiology of Coronavirus Under Research Exclusion-Atopic Dermatitis) registries; two urgent global initiatives that address an unmet need for delineating the determinants of COVID-19 outcomes in the common cutaneous immune-mediated inflammatory diseases (IMIDs) psoriasis and atopic dermatitis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32349517&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Becoming a Faithful Defender: Traditional Chinese Medicine against Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Therefore, on the basis of epidemiology and virology information, we reviewed relevant meta-analysis and clinical studies of anti-coronavirus therapeutics by TCM, in the aspect of mortality, symptom improvement, duration and dosage of corticosteroid, incidence of complications and the like.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-04-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32349772&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Novel Coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in newborns and infants: what we know so far.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This review provides an overview of the knowledge on SARS-CoV-2 epidemiology, transmission, the associated clinical presentation and outcomes in newborns and infants up to 6 months of life.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32350584&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiologic characteristics of traumatic fractures in elderly patients during the outbreak of coronavirus disease 2019 in China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This study aimed to describe the epidemiologic characteristics of fracture in the elderly during the COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32350632&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cardiovascular Risks in Patients with COVID-19: Potential Mechanisms and Areas of Uncertainty.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Robust epidemiologic and biologic studies are urgently needed to better understand the mechanism underlying these associations to develop better therapies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32350773&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Characterizing the Impact of COVID-19 on Men Who Have Sex with Men Across the United States in April, 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
While additional studies of COVID-19 epidemiology among MSM are needed, there is already evidence of emerging interruptions to HIV-related services.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32350796&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;It’s not over until it’s over: the chameleonic behavior of COVID-19 over a six-day period.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The current global outbreak of COVID-19 represents a major challenge in terms of epidemiology, contagiousness, treatment, as well as clinical and radiological behavior of this disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32353347&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology and transmission of COVID-19 in 391 cases and 1286 of their close contacts in Shenzhen, China: a retrospective cohort study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Our data on cases as well as their infected and uninfected close contacts provide key insights into the epidemiology of SARS-CoV-2.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32355547&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Trends and prediction in daily incidence of novel coronavirus infection in China, Hubei Province and Wuhan City: an application of Farr’s law.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Farr’s law is a classic epidemiology theory/practice for predicting epidemics.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32355904&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;To mask or not to mask: Modeling the potential for face mask use by the general public to curtail the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Moreover, mask use decreases the effective transmission rate in nearly linear proportion to the product of mask effectiveness (as a fraction of potentially infectious contacts blocked) and coverage rate (as a fraction of the general population), while the impact on epidemiologic outcomes (death, hospitalizations) is highly nonlinear, indicating masks could synergize with other non-pharmaceutical measures.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32357072&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CLINICAL CHARACTERISTICS OF 28 PATIENTS WITH DIABETES AND COVID-19 IN WUHAN, CHINA.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Epidemiologic, demographic, clinical, laboratory, treatment, and outcome data were analyzed. &lt;i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Results:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/i&gt; The average age of the 28 patients was 68.6 ± 9.0 years.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-01
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32357074&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Advanced Pulmonary and Cardiac Support of COVID-19 Patients: Emerging Recommendations From ASAIO&lt;i&gt;-&lt;/i&gt;a Living Working Document.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We review the rapidly changing epidemiology, pathophysiology, emerging therapy, and clinical outcomes of coronavirus disease 2019; and based on these data and previous experience with artificial cardiopulmonary support strategies, particularly in the setting of infectious diseases, provide consensus recommendations from American Society for Artificial Internal Organs.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32357503&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Deaths: Are We Sure It Is Pneumonia? Please, Autopsy, Autopsy, Autopsy!&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Defining the pathophysiology of death is not only limited to forensic considerations; it may also provide useful clinical and epidemiologic insights.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32358232&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Advanced Pulmonary and Cardiac Support of COVID-19 Patients: Emerging Recommendations From ASAIO-A “Living Working Document”.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We review the rapidly changing epidemiology, pathophysiology, emerging therapy, and clinical outcomes of COVID-19; and based on these data and previous experience with artificial cardiopulmonary support strategies, particularly in the setting of infectious diseases, provide consensus recommendations from ASAIO.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32359210&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical Course of COVID-19 in a Liver Transplant Recipient on Hemodialysis and Response to Tocilizumab Therapy: A Case Report.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There are limited published data on the epidemiology and outcomes of COVID-19 infection among organ transplant recipients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-02
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32359424&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Genomic Epidemiology of SARS-CoV-2 in Guangdong Province, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In order to understand the molecular epidemiology and genetic diversity of SARS-CoV-2 in China, we generated 53 genomes from infected individuals in Guangdong using a combination of metagenomic sequencing and tiling amplicon approaches.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32360053&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Characteristics of Endodontic Emergencies during Coronavirus Disease 2019 Outbreak in Wuhan.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Body temperature was measured and acquired for each patient, a coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) epidemiologic investigation questionnaire was given to each patient, an endodontic diagnosis was determined for the offending tooth, and a verbal numerical rating scale (VNRS) was used to record pain levels.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32361323&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical features of pediatric patients with coronavirus disease (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
All children had positive epidemiologic histories, 12 (12/16, 75 %) involving family units.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32362270&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19, Australia: Epidemiology Report 13 (Reporting week to 23:59 AEST 26 April 2020).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Interpretation of international epidemiology should be conducted with caution as it differs from country to country depending not only on the disease dynamics, but also on differences in case detection, testing and implemented public health measures.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32362392&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiologic and clinical characteristics of heart transplant recipients during the 2019 coronavirus outbreak in Wuhan, China: A descriptive survey report.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The epidemiologic and clinical characteristics of heart transplant (HTx) recipients during the severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) epidemic remains unclear.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32362424&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Intensive care during the 2019-coronavirus epidemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This narrative literature review aims to gather the main contributions in the area of intensive care to date in relation to the epidemiology, clinic, diagnosis and management of 2019-nCoViD.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32362969&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19, Modern Pandemic: A Systematic Review From Front-Line Health Care Providers’ Perspective.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The main aim of this systematic review is to provide a comprehensive clinical summary of all the available data from high-quality research articles relevant to the epidemiology, demographics, trends in hospitalization and outcomes, clinical signs and symptoms, diagnostic methods and treatment methods of COVID-19, thus increasing awareness in health care providers.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32363226&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A mild type of childhood Covid-19 - A case report.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This case is about a 9-year-old child diagnosed with COVID-19, with a history of epidemiology; SARS-CoV-2 nucleic acids testing was positive, while chest CT examination was negative.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32363228&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Art of prevention: Life in the time of coronavirus.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Early epidemiologic studies of viral spread support the hypothesis that COVID-19 can remain latent with an extended and infectious incubation period.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32363492&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Prevalence and socio-demographic correlates of psychological health problems in Chinese adolescents during the outbreak of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The epidemiology of emotional disorders is greatly influenced by stressful events.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32364890&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Evidence Supporting Transmission of Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2 While Presymptomatic or Asymptomatic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Recent epidemiologic, virologic, and modeling reports support the possibility of severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) transmission from persons who are presymptomatic (SARS-CoV-2 detected before symptom onset) or asymptomatic (SARS-CoV-2 detected but symptoms never develop).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-04
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32366488&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Nosocomial Outbreak of 2019 Novel Coronavirus Pneumonia in Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We collected and analysed data on exposure history, illness timelines, and epidemiologic characteristics of 25 laboratory-confirmed and two highly suspected HCWs as well as ten of their family members with COVID-19 from Jan 5 to Feb 12, 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32366746&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Guidance for the management of adult patients with coronavirus disease 2019.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This article summarized the understanding of the etiology, pathogenesis, epidemiology, clinical characteristics, diagnosis, treatment, rehabilitation, and prevention and control measures of COVID-19 based on the available data and anti-epidemic experience in China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-05
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32367739&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Outbreak dynamics of COVID-19 in Europe and the effect of travel restrictions.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here we combine a global network mobility model with a local epidemiology model to simulate and predict the outbreak dynamics and outbreak control of COVID-19 across Europe. […] We correlate our mobility model to passenger air travel statistics and calibrate our epidemiology model using the number of reported COVID-19 cases for each country. […] Ultimately, our network epidemiology model can inform political decision making and help identify exit strategies from current travel restrictions and total lockdown.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-31
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32367793&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiological characteristics of confirmed COVID-19 in Guizhou province, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To explore the epidemiological characteristics of COVID-19 associated with SARS-Cov-2 in Guizhou province, and to compare the differences in epidemiology with other provinces.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32368570&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Indian perspective of COVID-19 outbreak.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The present study review is on the general continent, virology, pathogenesis, global epidemiology, clinical presentation, diagnosis, treatment and control of COVID-19 with the reference to India.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32369865&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Considerations for pharmacoepidemiological analyses in the SARS-CoV-2 pandemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this paper, endorsed by the International Society for Pharmacoepidemiology, we provide methodological considerations for the conduct of pharmacoepidemiological studies in relation to the pandemic across eight domains: (1) timeliness of evidence, including the need to prioritise some questions over others in the acute phase of the pandemic; (2) the need to align observational and interventional research on efficacy; (3) the specific challenges related to “real-time epidemiology” during an ongoing pandemic; (4) what design to use to answer a specific question; (5) considerations on the definition of exposures; (6) what covariates to collect; (7) considerations on the definition of outcomes; and (8) the need for transparent reporting.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-21
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32371231&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Computational analysis of SARS-CoV-2/COVID-19 surveillance by wastewater-based epidemiology locally and globally: Feasibility, economy, opportunities and challenges.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
With the economic and practical limits of medical screening for SARS-CoV-2/COVID-19 coming sharply into focus worldwide, scientists are turning now to wastewater-based epidemiology (WBE) as a potential tool for assessing and managing the pandemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-31
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32371477&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Rapid implementation of mobile technology for real-time epidemiology of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We established the COronavirus Pandemic Epidemiology (COPE) consortium to bring together scientists with expertise in big data research and epidemiology to develop a COVID-19 Symptom Tracker mobile application that we launched in the UK on March 24, 2020 and the US on March 29, 2020 garnering more than 2.8 million users as of May 2, 2020. […] This initiative offers critical proof-of-concept for the repurposing of existing approaches to enable rapidly scalable epidemiologic data collection and analysis which is critical for a data-driven response to this public health challenge.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32371551&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The COronavirus Pandemic Epidemiology (COPE) Consortium: A Call to Action.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We established the COronavirus Pandemic Epidemiology (COPE) consortium to address this unprecedented crisis on behalf of the epidemiology research community. […] As a central component of this initiative, we have developed a COVID-19 Symptom Tracker mobile application as a common data collection tool for epidemiologic cohort studies with active study participants. […] The linkage of symptom data collected in the app with information and biospecimens already collected in epidemiology cohorts will position us to address key questions related to diet, lifestyle, environmental and socioeconomic factors on susceptibility to COVID-19, clinical outcomes related to infection, and long-term physical, mental health, and financial sequalae. […] We call upon additional epidemiology cohorts to join this collective effort to strengthen our impact on the current health crisis and generate a new model for a collaborative and nimble research infrastructure that will lead to more rapid translation of our work for the betterment of public health.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32373998&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The viral, epidemiologic, clinical characteristics and potential therapy options for COVID-19: a review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Meanwhile, we analyzed the epidemiologic and clinical characteristics of COVID-19, in order to provide recommendations for present clinical treatments and inspirations for potential therapy options.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32374000&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;An update on the status of COVID-19: a comprehensive review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we focus on our current understanding of epidemiology, pathogenesis, diagnostics and therapeutics of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32374544&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Venous thrombotic risk related to SARS-CoV-2 : prevalence, recommendations and perspectives].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this narrative review, we summarize available epidemiologic data on venous thromboembolism and recommendations on thromboprophylaxis in COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32374903&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SARS-CoV-2 viral spike G614 mutation exhibits higher case fatality rate.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The prevalence of this form of the virus should also be included in epidemiologic models predicting the COVID-19 health burden and fatality over time in specific regions.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-06
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32377559&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19: Review of Epidemiology and Potential Treatments Against 2019 Novel Coronavirus.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This manuscript reviews the epidemiology, etiology, mortality, COVID-19 clinical symptoms, and potential therapeutic drugs, while highlighting the seriousness and damage-induced by SARS-CoV-2.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32379077&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19: POSTMORTEM DIAGNOSTIC AND BIOSAFETY CONSIDERATIONS.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
While in some cases a history of fever and/or respiratory distress (e.g. cough or shortness of breath) may suggest the diagnosis, epidemiologic studies indicate that the majority of individuals infected with COVID-19 develop mild to no symptoms.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32379199&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A Typical Case of Critically Ill Infant of Coronavirus Disease 2019 With Persistent Reduction of T Lymphocytes.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Epidemiology, clinical characteristics, treatment, laboratory data and follow-up information and the treatment of critically ill infant were recorded.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32379502&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Estimating The Infection Fatality Rate Among Symptomatic COVID-19 Cases In The United States.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
When used with other estimating approaches, our model and our estimates can help disease and policy modelers to obtain more accurate predictions for the epidemiology of the disease and the impact of alternative policy levers to contain this pandemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-07
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32379727&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Improving Detection and Response to Respiratory Events - Kenya, April 2016-April 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
DaRRE initiatives support the four of 11 GHSA technical areas that CDC focuses on: surveillance, laboratory capacity, emergency operations, and workforce development.&lt;sup&gt;¶&lt;/sup&gt; In 2016, Kenya was selected to pilot DaRRE because of its existing respiratory disease surveillance and laboratory platforms and well-developed Field Epidemiology and Laboratory Training Program (FELTP) (2).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32382748&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Lessons from COVID-19 in children: Key hypotheses to guide preventative and therapeutic strategies.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Consistent epidemiologic evidence of reduced severity of infection in children across different populations and countries suggests there are underlying biologic differences between children and adults that mediate differential disease pathogenesis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32383254&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Evaluation of SARS-CoV-2 neutralizing antibodies using a CPE-based colorimetric live virus micro-neutralization assay in human serum samples.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The micro-neutralization assay is a fundamental test in virology, immunology, vaccine assessment, and epidemiology studies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32383432&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Structural Vulnerability in the United States Revealed in Three Waves of Novel Coronavirus Disease (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We describe three overlapping epidemiologic waves of spread of COVID-19 linked to three different kinds of structural vulnerabilities.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-08
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32385130&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical Characteristics of and Medical Interventions for COVID-19 in Hemodialysis Patients in Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We reviewed epidemiologic and clinical data of patients with laboratory-confirmed COVID-19 between January 1, 2020 and March 10, 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-09
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32385990&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Visualization analysis on treatment of coronavirus based on knowledge graph].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The main subject words were divided into three main categories, namely, CoVs epidemiology, basic research and drug development, in which basic research and drug development were strongly correlated.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-12
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32386027&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Unprecedented action has been taken to contain the epidemic of coronavirus disease 2019 in China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Significant improvement regarding the pathogenesis, epidemiology, and diagnosis and therapy for the COVID-19 has been achieved to stop the spread of the epidemics.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32387778&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;First confirmed detection of SARS-CoV-2 in untreated wastewater in Australia: A proof of concept for the wastewater surveillance of COVID-19 in the community.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Therefore, the quantification of SARS-CoV-2 in wastewater affords the ability to monitor the prevalence of infections among the population via wastewater-based epidemiology (WBE).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32388390&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The powerful immune system against powerful COVID-19: A hypothesis.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Epidemiology, risk factors, and clinical characteristics of patients with COVID-19 have been reported but the factors affecting the immune system against COVID-19 have not been well described.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32389849&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;From SARS to COVID-19: What we have learned about children infected with COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In the review, we draw upon the lessons learnt from SARS in the epidemiology, clinical characteristics and pathogenesis for further understand the features of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32390367&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical Features and Outcomes of 98 Patients Hospitalized with SARS-CoV-2 Infection in Daegu, South Korea: A Brief Descriptive Study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Although some information on the epidemiology of severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) and a few selected cases has been reported, data on the clinical characteristics and outcomes of patients hospitalized therewith in South Korea are lacking.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-12
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32391309&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Role of the Eye in Transmitting Human Coronavirus: What We Know and What We Do Not Know.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we describe the genomics and morphology of human CoVs, the epidemiology, systemic and ophthalmic manifestations, and mechanisms of human CoV infection, and recommendations for infection control procedures.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32391660&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Principles and suggestions on biosafety protection of biological specimen preservation during prevalence of COVID-19].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
According to the related national rules and the corresponding guidelines of Chinese Medical Association, this paper introduced the etiology about SARS-CoV-2, epidemiology about COVID-19, and the biosafety protection principles of individuals and biological specimen storage places in the process of personal protection, protection of collection, transport, handling, preservation, detection, post-detection disposal and emergencies of biological specimen.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-12
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32392337&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SARS-CoV-2 (COVID-19): What do we know about children? A systematic review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Few paediatric cases of COVID-19 have been reported and we know little about the epidemiology in children, though more is known about other coronaviruses.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32396550&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Virus detections among patients with severe acute respiratory illness, Northern Vietnam.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Initial screening for human respiratory viral pathogens was performed in Hanoi, Vietnam at the National Institute of Hygiene and Epidemiology (NIHE) or the Military Institute of Preventative Medicine (MIPM), and an aliquot was shipped to Duke-NUS Medical School in Singapore for validation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32397138&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A Systematic Review Analyzing the Prevalence and Circulation of Influenza Viruses in Swine Population Worldwide.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this context, the currently available scientific data hold a high significance to unravel influenza virus epidemiology and evolution.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-13
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32397688&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SARS-CoV-2/COVID-19: Viral Genomics, Epidemiology, Vaccines, and Therapeutic Interventions.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To address this global crisis, up-to-date information on viral genomics and transcriptomics is crucial for understanding the origins and global dispersion of the virus, providing insights into viral pathogenicity, transmission, and epidemiology, and enabling strategies for therapeutic interventions, drug discovery, and vaccine development. […] Therefore, this review provides a comprehensive overview of COVID-19 epidemiology, genomic etiology, findings from recent transcriptomic map analysis, viral-human protein interactions, molecular diagnostics, and the current status of vaccine and novel therapeutic intervention development.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32398569&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 in Children, Pregnancy and Neonates: A Review of Epidemiologic and Clinical Features.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this review, we summarize the epidemiologic and clinical features of children infected with SARS-CoV-2 reported in pediatric case series to date.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32398954&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Initial success in the identification and management of the coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) indicates human-to-human transmission in Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We summarized epidemiology, virological characteristics, clinical symptoms, diagnostic methods, clinical treatments, and prevention methods for COVID-19 to present a reference for the future wave of probable CoV outbreaks.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32401211&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Correlations of Online Search Engine Trends With Coronavirus Disease (COVID-19) Incidence: Infodemiology Study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The aim of this study is to apply digital epidemiology to the current COVID-19 pandemic to determine the utility of providing adjunctive epidemiologic information on outbreaks of this disease and evaluate this methodology in the case of future pandemics. […] An epidemiologic time series analysis of online search trends relating to the COVID-19 pandemic was performed from January 9, 2020, to April 6, 2020. […] This study demonstrates the utility of digital epidemiology in providing helpful surveillance data of disease outbreaks like COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32402329&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Novel human coronavirus (SARS-CoV-2): A lesson from animal coronaviruses.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The novel coronavirus (CoV) recognises, with high probability, a zoonotic origin but the role of animals in the SARS-CoV-2 epidemiology is still largely unknown.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32404473&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Towards effective diagnostic assays for COVID-19: a review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Accurate diagnoses of cases is key in managing the pandemic by identification, isolation and treatment of patients and defining the epidemiology of the virus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32405095&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Assessing changes in US public trust in science amid the Covid-19 pandemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The emergence of the Covid-19 and subsequent pandemic has led to the most substantive large-scale, open, and public social discussion of epidemiology and science in recent history. […] Continued examination of these trends is important for understanding public response to epidemiologic recommendations.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32405152&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Precautions and recommendations for orthodontic settings during the COVID-19 outbreak: A review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The objective of this review is to report to orthodontists on the emergence, epidemiology, risks, and precautions during disease crisis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32406852&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Awareness and preparedness of Field Epidemiology Training Program graduates in the Eastern Mediterranean Region to respond to COVID-19: A cross-section study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The Field Epidemiology Training Program (FETP) is a 2-year training program in applied epidemiology. […] The questionnaire comprised a series of questions pertaining to socio-demographic characteristics, knowledge of the epidemiology of COVID-19, and preparedness to respond to COVID-19. […] The FETP graduates in Jordan, Sudan, and Yemen were fully aware of the epidemiology COVID-19 and the safety measures and they are well positioned to investigate and respond to COVID-19 pandemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32407289&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 crisis in Jordan: Response, scenarios, strategies, and recommendations.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It is also recommended to increase and expand resources of intensive care units including respirators, increase the capacity and the number of trained health staff in the area of public health and epidemiology, ensure continued provision of essential public health programs and mobilize the resources of non-governmental sector and donors to provide services for refugees and vulnerable populations.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32407507&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Genomic epidemiology, evolution, and transmission dynamics of porcine deltacoronavirus.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here, we implemented and described an approach to analyze the epidemiology of PDCoV following its emergence in the pig population.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-14
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32408679&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Identifying Research Trends and Gaps in the Context of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In the research sector, there have been significant changes, and new research is coming very strongly in the related fields of virology and epidemiology. […] Significant progress is observed in the past research related to virology, epidemiology, infectious diseases among others.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32409547&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Complete Genome Sequences of SARS-CoV-2 Strains Detected in Malaysia.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Genome sequencing is important for understanding local epidemiology.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32410319&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus Disease 2019 and Viral Hepatitis coinfection: Provide guidelines for integrated screening and treatment.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We also call for guidelines for management and treatment as well as research to understand the epidemiology of coinfection This article is protected by copyright.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32410517&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Quarantine of the Covid-19 pandemic in suicide: A psychological autopsy.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The epidemiology of suicide has identified numerous psychiatric and occupational risk factors.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32412159&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;First experience of SARS-CoV-2 infections in solid organ transplant recipients in the Swiss Transplant Cohort Study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We performed a multicenter nationwide observational study within the Swiss Transplant Cohort Study (STCS) to describe the epidemiology, clinical presentation, treatment and outcomes of the first microbiologically documented SARS-CoV-2 infection among SOT recipients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-15
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32412422&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Complex Reporting of the COVID-19 Epidemic in the Czech Republic: Use of an Interactive Web-Based App in Practice.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Due to an urgent need for a tool that presents important reports based on valid data sources, a team of government experts and researchers focused on the design and development of a web app intended to provide a regularly updated overview of COVID-19 epidemiology in the Czech Republic to the general population.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32413616&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Mental Health Interventions during the COVID-19 Pandemic: A Conceptual Framework by Early Career Psychiatrists.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The emergence of mental health (MH) problems during a pandemic is extremely common, though difficult to address due to the complexities of pandemics and the scarcity of evidence about the epidemiology of pandemic-related MH problems and the potential interventions to tackle them. […] The CF was prepared based on the extant literature and the views discussed in this group; it illustrates the epidemiology of MH problems, preparedness plans, stage-specific plans or innovative solutions, opportunities to integrate those plans and possible outcomes at policy level.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32415727&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 knowledge prevents biologics discontinuation: Data from an Italian multicenter survey during RED-ZONE declaration.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
An ad hoc, validated questionnaire has 44 items investigating the following domains: knowledge of COVID-19 related to (a) epidemiology, (b) pathogenesis, (c) clinical symptoms, (d) preventive measures, and (e) attitudes. […] At the multivariate logistic regression, only the knowledge of epidemiology and preventive measures resulted independent predictors of continuation vs discontinuation and modification vs no modification, respectively.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32415915&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Perspectives on challenges and opportunities for birth defects surveillance programs during and after the COVID-19 era.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We discuss possible effects on clinical birth defect diagnoses, routine birth defects surveillance system activities, and epidemiologic considerations, as well as opportunities for mitigating the impact of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32416154&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Management of Gynecology Patients during COVID-19 Pandemic: Chinese Expert Consensus.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In our guidelines, we describe basic infection precaution principles, an epidemiologic screening tool, prioritization of surgical procedures, and operating room requirements.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32416629&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Management of primary cutaneous lymphoma patients during COVID-19 pandemic: EORTC CLTF guidelines Maarten Vermeer.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
During severe inflammatory coronavirus infectious disease (CoVID-19) pandemic and based on evidence on COVID-19 epidemiology, patients with primary cutaneous lymphomas (PCLs) have risk for developing complicated COVID-19 infections in consideration of their older age (majority above 60) and their potential underlying predisposing conditions (e.g. hypertension, diabetes).&lt;sup&gt;1,2,3&lt;/sup&gt; Moreover, PCL patients with aggressive biologic behavior should be carefully monitored according to guidelines for patients with neoplastic disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-16
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32417555&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Early SARS-CoV-2 outbreak detection by sewage-based epidemiology.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Sewage Epidemiology or Waste Based Epidemiology (WBE) approach has been successfully used to track and provide early warnings of outbreaks of pathogenic viruses such as Hepatitis A, Poliovirus and Norovirus.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32418508&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Erratum: COVID-19, Australia: Epidemiology Report 14 (Reporting week to 23:59 AEST 3 May 2020).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
An error in data processing resulted in the tabulation of incorrect crude case fatality rate values, for age groups of 50-59 and above, in Table 5 (Crude Case Fatality Rate of all cases and hospitalised cases, by age group) as originally published in the COVID-19 (Australia) epidemiology report 14.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32418549&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology of coronavirus disease 2019(COVID-19) caused by SARS-CoV-2.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Epidemiology characteristics of patients will be traced based on current information.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32419272&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Molecular Targets for the Testing of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Research priorities include infection control, epidemiology, clinical characterization and management, detection methods (including viral RNA detection, viral antigen detection, and serum antibody detection), therapeutics (neutralizing antibody and small molecule drugs), vaccines, and SARS-CoV-2 pathogenesis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32419771&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Epidemiological Aspects, Clinic And Control Mechanisms Of Sars-Cov-2pandemic: Situation In Spain].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In general, the epidemic control measures used so far have been based on adoption of interventions from the classical epidemiology, identifying and isolating the cases, following the contacts and establishing restrictions, including quarantine, closure of educational centers, avoiding events in which crowds of people occur, limiting mobility.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32420674&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Three months of COVID-19: A systematic review and meta-analysis.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This review analyses information on progression of the pandemic in the past 3 months and systematically discusses the characteristics of SARS-CoV-2019 virus including its epidemiologic, pathophysiologic, and clinical manifestations.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-18
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32420937&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Current laboratory diagnostics of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The availability of rapid tests for detecting either viral antigens or anti-SARS-CoV-2 antibodies are a potentially viable opportunity for purposes of epidemiologic surveillance, though more information is needed on accuracy and reliability of these portable immunoassays.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32420941&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Novel coronavirus infection and children.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We searched Pubmed, from January to April 2020, for the following search terms: “COVID-19”, “children”, “SARS-COV2”, “complications”, “epidemiology”, “clinical features”, focusing our attention mostly on epidemiology and symptoms of COVID-19 in children.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32422057&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Variation in False-Negative Rate of Reverse Transcriptase Polymerase Chain Reaction-Based SARS-CoV-2 Tests by Time Since Exposure.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
If clinical suspicion is high, infection should not be ruled out on the basis of RT-PCR alone, and the clinical and epidemiologic situation should be carefully considered.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32422983&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;No Autopsies on COVID-19 Deaths: A Missed Opportunity and the Lockdown of Science.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Autopsy should be considered mandatory to define the exact cause of death, thus providing useful clinical and epidemiologic information as well as pathophysiological insights to further provide therapeutic tools.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32423024&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Rationale for Potential Pharmacotherapy of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 is being increasingly investigated through virology, epidemiology, and clinical management strategies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32425000&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;An overview of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Meanwhile, recent research has revealed critical aspects of SARS-CoV-2 biology and disease pathogenesis; other studies have focused on epidemiology, clinical features, diagnosis, management, as well as drug and vaccine development.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-20
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32425234&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Corticosteroids, but not TNF Antagonists, are Associated with Adverse COVID-19 Outcomes in Patients With Inflammatory Bowel Diseases: Results from an International Registry.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Surveillance Epidemiology of Coronavirus Under Research Exclusion for Inflammatory Bowel Disease (SECURE-IBD) is a large, international registry created to monitor outcomes of IBD patients with confirmed COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32425279&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Swine enteric alphacoronavirus (swine acute diarrhea syndrome coronavirus): An update three years after its discovery.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This review summarizes the emergence of SeACoV and updates the research progress made from 2017 to early 2020, mainly focusing on the etiology, epidemiology, evolutionary perspective, potential for interspecies transmission, pathogenesis and diagnosis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32425491&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Pandemic COVID-19, the new health emergency of international concern: a review].&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The purpose of this review is to study the most relevant and current information on the pathogen, as well as epidemiology, pathology, clinical features, transmission, prevention, and treatment of the disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32425651&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Current Scenario of COVID-19 in Pediatric Age Group and Physiology of Immune and Thymus response.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Therefore, in this review, we outline the epidemiology, clinical symptoms, diagnosis, treatment, prevention, possible immune response and role of thymus in children to combat the COVID-19 outbreak.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32426529&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Impact of shelter-in-place order for COVID-19 on trauma activations: Santa Clara County, California, March 2020.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There were no other statistically significant changes to the epidemiology of trauma activations. […] Overall trauma activations decreased 4.8-fold after the shelter-in-place order went into effect in Santa Clara County on 16 March 2020, with no other effect on the epidemiology of persons presenting after traumatic injury.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32426754&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Viral Infection and Respiratory Illness Universal Study (VIRUS): An International Registry of Coronavirus 2019-Related Critical Illness.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Large areas of uncertainly regarding epidemiology, physiology, practice patterns, and resource demands for patients with coronavirus disease 2019 require rapid collection and dissemination of data.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32426877&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Metastatic melanoma treatment with check point inhibitors in the COVID-19 era: experience from an Italian Skin Cancer Unit.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Melanoma epidemiology has shown a constant increase in the last few decades even if mortality is low and only a small percentage of patients develop metastatic disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-19
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32427170&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A multi-hazards earth science perspective on the COVID-19 pandemic: the potential for concurrent and cascading crises.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 epidemiologic conditions at the time of a natural hazard event might also influence the characteristics of emergency and humanitarian responses (e.g. evacuation and sheltering procedures, resource availability, implementation modalities, and assistance types).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32429774&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Anti-Coagulant and Anti-Platelet Therapy in the COVID-19 Patient: A Best Practices Quality Initiative Across a Large Health System.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This disease and its worldwide impact have sparked tremendous interest in the epidemiology, pathogenesis, and clinical consequences of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-20
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32431961&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Global Ranking of COVID-19-Related Mortality by Country using a Novel Pandemic Efficiency Index (PEI).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
As the pandemic evolves, there is an urgent need to better understand its epidemiology, characterize its potential impact, and identify mitigatory strategies to avert pandemic-related mortality.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32433260&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Where Have All the Fractures Gone? The Epidemiology of Pediatric Fractures During the COVID-19 Pandemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A resulting change in pediatric fracture epidemiology is expected.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-20
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32434058&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A chronicle of SARS-CoV-2: Part-I - Epidemiology, diagnosis, prognosis, transmission and treatment.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The review explicitly covers the aspects like genome and pedigree of SARS-CoV-2; epidemiology, prognosis, pathogenesis, symptoms and diagnosis of COVID-19 in order to catalog the right information on transmission route, and influence of environmental factors on virus transmissions, for the robust understanding of right strategical steps for proper COVID-19 management.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32434211&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Viral and host factors related to the clinical outcome of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this ongoing pandemic, public health concerns and the urgent need for effective therapeutic measures require a deep understanding of its epidemiology, transmissibility and pathogenesis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-20
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32434402&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Psychological health during the coronavirus disease 2019 pandemic outbreak.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Currently all efforts are focused on the understanding of epidemiology, clinical features, mode of transmission, counteract the spread of the virus, and challenges of global health, while crucially significant mental health has been overlooked in this endeavor.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-21
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32438005&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Response to SARS-CoV-2 Pandemic in a Non-COVID-19 Designated Latin-American Neurosurgery Department.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Subsequently, a questionnaire with epidemiologic, radiologic, clinical, and serologic criteria will be applied to determine the risk of COVID-19 infection to define to which area they are going to be transferred according to the different risk zones in our facility.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32438622&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Dynamics of Population Immunity Due to the Herd Effect in the COVID-19 Pandemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In epidemiology, herd immunity is presented as an area that could also solve this new global threat. […] In this review, we present the basis of herd immunology, the dynamics of infection transmission that induces specific immunity, and how the application of immunoepidemiology and herd immunology could be used to control the actual COVID-19 pandemic, along with a discussion of its effectiveness, limitations, and applications.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32439651&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CT Scanning in Suspected Stroke or Head Trauma: Is it Worth to go the Extra Mile and Include the Chest to Screen for COVID-19 Infection?&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Correlation of chest CT results with epidemiologic history and clinical presentation, along with real-time reverse transcriptase polymerase chain reaction, is needed for confirmation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32440887&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The EPICENTRE (ESPNIC Covid pEdiatric Neonatal Registry) initiative: background and protocol for the international SARS-CoV-2 infections registry.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The European Society for Pediatric and Neonatal Intensive Care (ESPNIC) launched the EPICENTRE (ESPNIC Covid pEdiatric Neonatal Registry) international, multicenter, and multidisciplinary initiative to study the epidemiology, clinical course, and outcomes of pediatric and neonatal SARS-CoV-2 infections. […] EPICENTRE is open to centers all over the world, and this will allow to provide a pragmatic picture of the epidemic, with a particular attention to pediatric and neonatal critical care issues.Conclusions: EPICENTRE will allow researchers to clarify the epidemiology, clinical presentation, and outcomes of pediatric and neonatal SARS-CoV-2 infection, refining its clinical management and hopefully providing new insights for clinicians.What is Known:• COVID19 is the new disease caused by SARS-CoV-2 infection and is spreading around the globe. […] • EPICENTRE will allow to understand epidemiology and physiopathology of COVID19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-25
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32441548&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Unpredictable Fall of Severe Emergent Cardiovascular Diseases Hospital Admissions During the COVID-19 Pandemic: Experience of a Single Large Center in Northern Italy.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The aim of this study was to analyze the epidemiologic impact of Coronavirus Disease 2019 pandemic on hospital admission for severe emergent cardiovascular diseases (SECDs) in a single Northern Italy large tertiary referral center.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32441574&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A case series describing the epidemiology and clinical characteristics of COVID-19 infection in Jilin Province.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Since its outbreak in Wuhan, Hubei Province China, 2019-coronavirus infected disease (COVID-19) had been widely spread all over the world, the control of which calls for a better understanding of its epidemiology and clinical characteristics.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32442265&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Characterization of an asymptomatic cohort of SARS-COV-2 infected individuals outside of Wuhan, China.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here, we aimed to further clarify the epidemiologic and clinical characteristics of asymptomatic SARS-CoV-2 infections.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-22
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32442528&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Epidemiology, clinical course, and outcomes of critically ill adults with COVID-19 in New York City: a prospective cohort study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Data on the epidemiology, clinical course, and outcomes of critically ill patients with COVID-19 in this setting are needed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32444358&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Incidence, clinical outcomes, and transmission dynamics of severe coronavirus disease 2019 in California and Washington: prospective cohort study.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To understand the epidemiology and burden of severe coronavirus disease 2019 (covid-19) during the first epidemic wave on the west coast of the United States.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32446285&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A Guide to COVID-19: a global pandemic caused by the novel coronavirus SARS-CoV-2.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here, we provide an overview of SARS-CoV-2 by analyzing its virology, epidemiology, and modes of transmission while examining the current progress of testing procedures and possible treatments through drugs and vaccines.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-23
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32447059&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Use of Decision Modelling to Inform Timely Policy Decisions on Cardiac Resource Capacity during the COVID-19 Pandemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We provided predictions based on COVID-19 epidemiology available in real-time, in 3 phases. […] Second, with better local epidemiology data, we predicted that across five regions of Ontario, there may be insufficient resources to resume all elective outpatient cardiac procedures.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32447742&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Clinical Insights into the Gastrointestinal Manifestations of COVID-19.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Moreover, the epidemiology, clinical characteristics, diagnostic procedures, treatments and prevention of the gastrointestinal manifestations of COVID-19 remain to be elucidated.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32447820&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Coronavirus disease (COVID-19): An updated review based on current knowledge and existing literature for dermatologists.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Several studies, since then, have tried to study and explain the origin of SARS-CoV-2, its structure and pathogenicity, epidemiology, modes of transmission, spectrum of illness and causes of mortality and morbidity.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-24
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32448490&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Mysterious Virus: A Review on Behavior and Treatment Approaches of the Novel Coronavirus, 2019-nCoV.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In the present article, we made an attempt to review the behavior of the virus around the world, epidemiology, a pathway for influx into the host cells, clinical presentation, as well as the treatments currently in use and future approaches; nitazoxanide may be our dream drug.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32449614&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Gender differences in patients with COVID-19: a narrative review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The aim of this narrative review is to underline gender differences in epidemiology, etiopathogenesis, risk factors, clinical presentation, diagnosis, prognosis and mortality of patients infected with SARS-CoV-2.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32450727&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Chest CT-based differential diagnosis of 28 patients with suspected corona virus disease 2019 (COVID-19).&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There were no significant differences between the 12 confirmed COVID-19 (SARS-Cov-2-positive) patients and 16 SARS-CoV-2-negative patients in epidemiology and most of the clinical features or laboratory data.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32451162&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The management of surgical patients during the coronavirus dieases 2019 (COVID-19) pandemic.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Relevant publications reporting on the epidemiology of the pandemic, the diagnosis of the severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 infection, and the clinical management of cancer and surgical patients, as well as studies concerning health care workers’ safety, were included.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-29
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32452539&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 under spotlight: A close look at the origin, transmission, diagnosis, and treatment of the 2019-nCoV disease.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Herein, the COVID-19 structure, epidemiology, pathogenesis, etiology, diagnosis, and therapy have been reviewed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32452587&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Covid-19 diffusion and its impact on dental practice in distant countries with similar ethnic background.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Epidemiology of Covid-19 and diffusion patterns of the novel coronavirus (SARS - CoV - 2) are still poorly understood, as they differ substantially among countries and even in neighboring regions within the same country.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-26
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32455503&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Face coverings for the public: Laying straw men to rest.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
I set out some key findings from basic science, epidemiology, mathematical modelling, case studies, and natural experiments, and use this rich and diverse body of evidence as the backdrop for my rebuttal of their narrowly framed objections.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-28
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32458760&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;COVID-19 pandemic - An African perspective.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Therefore, in this review we collected and summarised the currently available literature on the epidemiology, etiology, vulnerability, preparedness and economic impact of COVID-19 in Africa, which could be useful and provide necessary information on ongoing COVID-19 pandemics in the continent.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32459192&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Molecular, serological, and biochemical diagnosis and monitoring of COVID-19: IFCC taskforce evaluation of the latest evidence.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The International Federation of Clinical Chemistry and Laboratory Medicine (IFCC) Task Force on COVID-19 has been established to synthesize up-to-date information on the epidemiology, pathogenesis, and laboratory diagnosis and monitoring of COVID-19, as well as to develop practical recommendations on the use of molecular, serological, and biochemical tests in disease diagnosis and management.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32459790&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Children in Critical Care Due to Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2 Infection: Experience in a Spanish Hospital.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Epidemiologic data, previous clinical characteristics, support therapy needed, imaging tests, laboratory observations on admission, and pharmacologic therapy.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32460302&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Need for Objective Assessment of Volume Status in Critically Ill Patients with COVID-19: The Tri-POCUS Approach.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
As the coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) continues to spread across the globe, the knowledge of its epidemiology, clinical features, and management is rapidly evolving.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-27
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32464333&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;First detection of SARS-CoV-2 in untreated wastewaters in Italy.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Several studies have demonstrated the advantages of environmental surveillance through the monitoring of sewage for the assessment of viruses circulating in a given community (wastewater-based epidemiology, WBE).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
2020-05-30
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms to cluster Epidemiology Abstract</title>
      <link>/syntax_summary/epidemiology/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/syntax_summary/epidemiology/terms/</guid>
      <description> 

&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 2.&lt;/strong&gt; 5 terms used to create the Epidemiology Category and its counts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Term
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Count
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
All (sum)
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
728
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Epidemiologic
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
541
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Epidemiology
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
226
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Pharmacoepidemiology
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
1
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Health Services Research
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
