<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PlatCOVID</title>
    <link>/drugpanel/turkey/</link>
      <atom:link href="/drugpanel/turkey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>PlatCOVID</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>BioHub - UFPE</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu7e12209333f22d741aca7d462871821f_9877_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>PlatCOVID</title>
      <link>/drugpanel/turkey/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>TURKEY</title>
      <link>/drugpanel/turkey/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/drugpanel/turkey/info/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p align=&#34;left&#34; style=&#34;font-size:16px&#34;&gt;
DrugBank ID: &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.drugbank.ca/drugs/db10575&#39; target=&#39;_blank&#39;&gt;db10575&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;
DrugCentral: &lt;a href=&#34;http://drugcentral.org/?q=turkey&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;turkey&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Synonymous : &lt;em&gt;None&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;drug-sentece-context&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Drug Sentece Context&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 1.&lt;/strong&gt; Analysis of context sentence of &lt;em&gt;turkey&lt;/em&gt; gene in 40 abstracts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
pmid
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
sentence
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32275463&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32275463&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This study aims to evaluate the knowledge of anesthesiology specialists and residents in Turkey about COVID-19 and their attitudes toward the strategies and application methods to be used for a suspected/confirmed COVID-19 case that needs to be operated on or followed up in an intensive care unit, as well as to raise awareness about this issue. &lt;b&gt; &lt;i&gt;Methods:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/b&gt; This descriptive study comprised anesthesiology specialists and residents working in various health institutions in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32283894&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32283894&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Coronavirus Infectious Disease 2019 (COVID-19) is now a pandemic spreading in most countries including Turkey. […] Turkey is early in the outbreak.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32293832&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32293832&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 was seen for the first cases in Turkey on March 10, 2020 and was number 47,029 cases and 1,006 deaths after 1 month.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32293834&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32293834&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The most frequently used agents both in Turkey and all over the world including chloroquine, hydroxychloroquine, lopinavir/ritonavir, favipiravir and remdesivir will be reviewed here .
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32299208&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32299208&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this process, the Scientific and Technological Research Council of Turkey (TÜBİTAK), which publishes academic journals including the Turkish Journal of Medical Sciences, has taken rapid action to mobilize the research community. […] This short communication aims to provide an introduction of the major initiatives that have been taken in the scientific landscape with a focus on Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32304192&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32304192&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Our first COVID-19 case in Turkey was a 44-year-old male who referred to the hospital on March 9, 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32334158&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32334158&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The present study examines the correlation between weather and coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) by considering nine cities in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32368875&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32368875&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To prevent the spread of COVID-19, Ministry of Health of Republic of Turkey and international institutions have published documents defining hygiene rules.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32374218&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32374218&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Apart from infectious bronchitis virus in chickens, the only avian species in which CoV has been definitively associated with disease are the turkey, pheasant and guinea fowl.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32391801&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32391801&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The United States, the United Kingdom, Turkey, China, and Russia saw a relatively fast spread of the disease. […] There was a high death rate ratio in Italy and the United Kingdom and a lower death rate ratio in Russia, Turkey, China, and the United States.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32392400&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32392400&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To evaluate the effect of the COVID-19 pandemic on female sexual behavior in women in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32395095&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32395095&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Data were collected by convenience sampling method, which allowed us to reach total 1304 participants, aged between 18 and 64 years, from 75 cities in Turkey. […] This scale will allow mental health professionals to do research on the psychological impacts of COVID-19 in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32401401&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32401401&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) emerged late in Turkey but it showed a rapid progression later. […] We aimed to investigate the changes in the number of patients who requested a dermatology outpatient clinic visit due to the increased social and medical burden caused by COVID-19 in Turkey during the first days of the pandemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32409210&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32409210&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
There were four stroke cases with simultaneously diagnosis of Covid-19 till the April 14, 2020 in the city of Sakarya, Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32413608&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32413608&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In total, 19 countries responded: Albania, Armenia, Belarus, Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bulgaria, Croatia, Czech Republic, Estonia, Georgia, Greece, Hungary, Lithuania, Macedonia, Poland, Republic of Moldova, Russia, Serbia, Turkey, and Ukraine.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32415519&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32415519&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We found that 86.7% of students regarded frequent hand washing as the most important means of protection against COVID-19, and 19.3% of students did not regard the COVID-19 pandemic as a severe public health problem for Turkey at that moment. […] In addition, 61.6% of students stated that a suppression strategy involving tight restrictions need to be applied to being the pandemic under control in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32427165&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32427165&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The sample comprised 1772 Turkish individuals (aged between 18 and 73 years) from 79 of 81 cities in Turkey, who completed measures of mental wellbeing, intolerance of uncertainty, rumination, and fear of COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32429517&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32429517&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
From February to March, the 4-12 ∘ C isotherm zone extended mostly from Central China toward Iran, Turkey, West-Mediterranean Europe (Italy, Spain and France) up to the United State of America, optimally coinciding with the geographic regions most affected by the pandemic from February to March.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32429780&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32429780&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Little is known about the psychological aspects, particularly for vulnerable populations including pregnant women.&lt;b&gt;Objectives:&lt;/b&gt; To understand the attitude, concerns, and knowledge of the non-infected pregnant women toward the COVID-19 outbreak in order to constitute base data for detailed counseling and to develop targeted messages.&lt;b&gt;Patients and methods:&lt;/b&gt; This cross-sectional survey research presented analysis of prospectively collected data yielded at a single tertiary “Coronavirus Pandemic Hospital” referral center for a ten days period following the first confirmed death due to the COVID-19 pandemic in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32434621&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32434621&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In Turkey, which has a strong health system, most hospitals have been turned into pandemic hospitals, elective procedures have been postponed and doctors have been re-assigned to treat COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32442684&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32442684&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The first case of Covid-19 in Turkey was detected on March 10, 2020.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32450712&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32450712&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This study aims to provide both a model by using cumulative cases and cumulative death toll for SARS-CoV-2 (severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2) outbreak in 4 countries, China, Italy, South Korea, and Turkey, starting from the first diagnosis and to compare associated indicators. […] The most successful estimation was obtained from the cubic model with natural logarithm for China, Italy, South Korea, and Turkey. […] On the other hand, the number of new cases was 24.6 per 1 million people on March 27, 2020, in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32452542&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32452542&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
On March 11, 2020, the first case of the novel coronavirus 2019 disease (COVID-19) was officially confirmed in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32478289&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32478289&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Turkey is one of the latest countries that COVID-19 disease was reported, with the first case on March 11, 2020, and since then, Istanbul became the epicenter of the pandemic in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32484930&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32484930&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The data of 12 adult COVID-19 pneumonia patients who were followed in the inpatient clinics of Biruni University Medical Faculty Hospital (Istanbul, Turkey) were retrospectively analyzed.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32490641&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32490641&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Novel coronavirus 19 infection (COVID-19) has become a global pandemic and Turkey had the first coronavirus patient tested positive in 10 March 2020. […] Turkey has avoided the disease for some time but as inevitable as it is, our country has been added to the countries which are infected.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32490887&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32490887&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The study population consisted of dentists in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32519618&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32519618&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Başkent University has 21 dialysis centers across Turkey, with 2420 patients on hemodialysis and 30 on peritoneal dialysis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32519953&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32519953&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It is imperative to act according to the standards set by health-care institutions and the Ministry of Health, Republic of Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32530587&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32530587&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The first confirmed cases were announced early in March, and since then, serious containment measures have taken place in Turkey. […] We expect that drastic changes in the course of the COVID-19 in Turkey will cause the model to suffer in predictive validity, and this can be used to monitor the epidemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32536762&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32536762&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this research, we are interested in predicting the epidemic peak outbreak of the Coronavirus in South Africa, Turkey, and Brazil. […] The investigated model allows us to predict the spread of COID-19 in South Africa, Turkey, and Brazil.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32538025&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32538025&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Turkey reported its first COVID-19 case on March 10, 2020. […] We present here the mitigation efforts Turkey has undertaken so far, and also review the lessons learned for future proactive strategies. […] At this phase, Turkey needs to adopt an evidence-based, proactive control system for an effective transition process to normalize the situation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32543353&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32543353&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This highlighted clade also included some strains isolated from patients who had a travel history to Turkey and Iran.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32551453&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32551453&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this case report, we aim to share our experience about the first organ donation during the COVID-19 pandemic in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32553714&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32553714&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A retrospective study was performed at a pandemic hospital in Istanbul, Turkey and 681 laboratory-confirmed patients with COVID-19 were included.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32563745&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32563745&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Studies from China, Italy, Turkey, Spain and Iran reported higher-than-pooled prevalence among healthcare workers and the general public.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32565625&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32565625&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this study, confirmed COVID-19 cases of Denmark, Belgium, Germany, France, United Kingdom, Finland, Switzerland and Turkey were modeled with Auto-Regressive Integrated Moving Average (ARIMA), Nonlinear Autoregression Neural Network (NARNN) and Long-Short Term Memory (LSTM) approaches.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32575957&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32575957&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
≤0.7) such as Indonesia, Pakistan, and Turkey should be on high alert and develop COVID- 19 response plans as soon as permitting.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32576329&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32576329&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The first COVID-19 case was diagnosed in Turkey on March 11, 2020 and the peak phase seemed to end by the end of April.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32578309&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32578309&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Retrospective, cohort study In this study we observed the dermatology consultations of the hospitalized patients over a period of 2 months, corresponding to the peak of COVID outbreak in a tertiary care hospital in Turkey.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
