<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PlatCOVID</title>
    <link>/drugpanel/dexamethasone/</link>
      <atom:link href="/drugpanel/dexamethasone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>PlatCOVID</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>BioHub - UFPE</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu7e12209333f22d741aca7d462871821f_9877_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>PlatCOVID</title>
      <link>/drugpanel/dexamethasone/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>DEXAMETHASONE</title>
      <link>/drugpanel/dexamethasone/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/drugpanel/dexamethasone/info/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p align=&#34;left&#34; style=&#34;font-size:16px&#34;&gt;
DrugBank ID: &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.drugbank.ca/drugs/db01234&#39; target=&#39;_blank&#39;&gt;db01234&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;
DrugCentral: &lt;a href=&#34;http://drugcentral.org/?q=dexamethasone&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;dexamethasone&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Synonymous :1-dehydro-16alpha-methyl-9alpha-fluorohydrocortisone | 1-dehydro-16α-methyl-9α-fluorohydrocortisone | 16alpha-methyl-9alpha-fluoro-1-dehydrocortisol | 16α-methyl-9α-fluoro-1-dehydrocortisol | 9alpha-fluoro-16alpha-methylprednisolone | 9α-fluoro-16α-methylprednisolone | dexametasona | dexaméthasone | dexamethasone | dexamethasonum
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;drug-sentece-context&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Drug Sentece Context&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 1.&lt;/strong&gt; Analysis of context sentence of &lt;em&gt;dexamethasone&lt;/em&gt; gene in 7 abstracts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
pmid
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
sentence
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32305989&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32305989&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
For standard-risk patients, we recommend the following: ixazomib, lenalidomide, and dexamethasone (IRd) (preferred), cyclophosphamide lenalidomide and dexamethasone (CRd), daratumumab lenalidomide and dexamethasone (DRd), lenalidomide, bortezomib, and dexamethasone (RVd), or cyclophosphamide, bortezomib, and dexamethasone (CyBorD). […] For high-risk patients we recommend carfilzomib, lenalidomide, and dexamethasone (KRd) (preferred) or RVd. […] Decreasing the dose of dexamethasone to 20 mg and giving bortezomib subcutaneously once a week is recommended.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32444866&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32444866&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Oral agent-based regimens should be considered, especially for the elderly and frail patients with standard risk disease, whereas de-intensified regimens for dexamethasone, bortezomib, carfilzomib and daratumumab should be used based on patient risk and response.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32507102&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32507102&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Dexamethasone, a widely prescribed antiemetic for acute and delayed nausea and vomiting from a variety of cancer drugs, causes B and T cell depletion, which may augment immunosuppression. […] Since it seems that lymphocytes are vital in the immune response to novel coronavirus, oncologists should reconsider the &lt;i&gt;routine&lt;/i&gt; use of prophylactic dexamethasone in uninfected patients, to avoid inducing lymphopenia, which may increase risk of infection or lead to inferior outcomes if a cancer patient subsequently becomes infected. […] Since many cancer drugs and malignant diseases inherently cause lymphopenia, further reduction of lymphocytes with dexamethasone should be avoided if possible and if safe and effective alternative antiemetics are available during the COVID-19 crisis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32519786&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32519786&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Hydroxychloroquine (600mg/day), Azithromycine, steroids (dexamethasone 20mg/day), vitamin C (3g/day), Zinc, diuretics and Enoxaparine were equally used for the two patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32551464&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32551464&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Recent announcements indicated, without sharing any distinct published set of results, that the corticosteroid dexamethasone may reduce mortality of severe COVID-19 patients only. […] Dexamethasone is a synthetic corticosteroid approved by the FDA 1958 as a broad-spectrum immunosuppressor and it is about 30 times as active and with longer duration of action (2-3 days) than cortisone. […] Dexamethasone would limit the production of and damaging effect of the cytokines, but will also inhibit the protective function of T cells and block B cells from making antibodies, potentially leading to increased plasma viral load that will persist after a patient survives SARS. […] Moreover, dexamethasone would block macrophages from clearing secondary, nosocomial, infections. […] Hence, dexamethasone may be useful for the short-term in severe, intubated, COVID-19 patients, but could be outright dangerous during recovery since the virus will not only persist, but the body will be prevented from generating protective antibodies. […] Instead, a pulse of intravenous dexamethasone may be followed by administration of nebulized triamcinolone (6 times as active as cortisone) to concentrate in the lungs only.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32560745&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32560745&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Therefore, we designed a trial to test our hypothesis that early administration of dexamethasone in combination with IV-IG and interferon-beta can reduce the effect of the cytokine storm in critically ill patients COVID-19. […] The age range of patients will be 18-70 years old. the need for intubation; allergy, intolerance, or contraindication to any study drug including dexamethasone, IV-IG, and interferon-beta; pregnancy or lactation; known HIV positive or active hepatitis B or C. […] Each patient in the Intervention Group 1 will receive the standard treatment for COVID-19 and dexamethasone, at the first 24 hours’ time of admission. […] The intervention begins with the administration of dexamethasone based on the SpO&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; levels. […] If the level of SpO&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; does not improve after 24 hours, IV-IG (400 mg/kg once daily for 5 days) and interferon-beta (7 doses every other day) will be prescribed along with dexamethasone administration. […] In Intervention Group 2, the administration of dexamethasone will be started within the first 24 hours’ time of admission and will be continued for 48-72 hours and then the SpO&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; level will be checked.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32570995&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32570995&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Dexamethasone, a synthetic glucocorticoid, has anti-inflammatory and immunosuppressive properties. […] We reviewed the charts of SARS-CoV-2 patients with pneumonia and moderate to severely elevated CRP and worsening hypoxemia who were treated with early, short-term dexamethasone. […] We describe a series of 21 patients who tested positive for SARS-CoV-2 and were admitted to The Miriam Hospital in Providence, RI, and were treated with a short course of dexamethasone, either alone or in addition to current investigative therapies. […] CRP levels decreased significantly following the start of dexamethasone from mean initial levels of 129.52 to 40.73 mg/L at time of discharge. 71% percent of the patients were discharged home with a mean length of stay of 7.8 days.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
