<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PlatCOVID</title>
    <link>/drugpanel/ruxolitinib/</link>
      <atom:link href="/drugpanel/ruxolitinib/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>PlatCOVID</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>BioHub - UFPE</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu7e12209333f22d741aca7d462871821f_9877_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>PlatCOVID</title>
      <link>/drugpanel/ruxolitinib/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUXOLITINIB</title>
      <link>/drugpanel/ruxolitinib/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/drugpanel/ruxolitinib/info/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p align=&#34;left&#34; style=&#34;font-size:16px&#34;&gt;
DrugBank ID: &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.drugbank.ca/drugs/db08877&#39; target=&#39;_blank&#39;&gt;db08877&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;
DrugCentral: &lt;a href=&#34;http://drugcentral.org/?q=ruxolitinib&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ruxolitinib&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Synonymous :ruxolitinib
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;drug-sentece-context&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Drug Sentece Context&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 1.&lt;/strong&gt; Analysis of context sentence of &lt;em&gt;ruxolitinib&lt;/em&gt; gene in 24 abstracts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
pmid
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
sentence
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32276453&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32276453&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Two of these senotherapeutics, azithromycin and ruxolitinib, are currently undergoing testing for their efficacy in treating COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32387301&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32387301&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The most promising drugs might be: Ruxolitinib, a JAK1/2 inhibitor, with a rapid and powerful anti-cytokine effect, tyrosine kinase inhibitors (TKIs), with their good anti-inflammatory properties, and perhaps the anti-Cd26 antibody Begelomab.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32421092&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32421092&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Other possible IL-6 pathway inhibitors such as Ruxolitinib and Baricinitib are then analyzed, underlying how they lack the benefit of targeting only the pro-inflammatory pathway.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32470486&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32470486&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This study evaluated the efficacy and safety of ruxolitinib, a Janus-associated kinase (JAK1/2) inhibitor, for COVID-19. […] Forty-three patients were randomly assigned (1:1) to receive ruxolitinib plus SoC treatment (22 patients) or placebo based on SoC treatment (21 patients). […] After exclusion of 2 patients (1 ineligible, 1 consent withdrawn) from the ruxolitinib group, 20 patients in intervention group and 21 patients in control group were included in the study. […] Treatment with ruxolitinib plus SoC was not associated with significantly accelerated clinical improvement in severe patients with COVID-19, although ruxolitinib recipients had a numerically faster clinical improvement. […] Eighteen (90%) patients from the ruxolitinib group showed CT improvement at D&lt;sub&gt;14&lt;/sub&gt; compared with 13 (61.9%) patients from the control group (P = 0.0495). […] Three patients in the control group died of respiratory failure, with 14.3% overall mortality at D&lt;sub&gt;28&lt;/sub&gt;; no patients died in the ruxolitinib group. […] Ruxolitinib was well tolerated with low toxicities and no new safety signals. […] Levels of 7 cytokines were significantly decreased in the ruxolitinib group in comparison to the control group. […] Although no statistical difference was observed, ruxolitinib recipients had a numerically faster clinical improvement. […] Significant chest CT improvement, a faster recovery from lymphopenia and favorable side-effect profile in ruxolitinib group were encouraging and informative to future trials to test efficacy of ruxolitinib in a larger population.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32518419&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32518419&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Using a newly developed COVID-19 Inflammation Score (CIS), patients were prospectively stratified for targeted inhibition of cytokine signalling by the Janus Kinase 1/2 inhibitor ruxolitinib (Rux).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32544802&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32544802&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The main drug interactions were found with tocilizumab, ruxolitinib and colchicine.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32581810&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32581810&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Based on the hypothesis that complement and coagulation cascades are activated by viral infection, and might trigger an acute respiratory distress syndrome (ARDS), we report clinical outcomes of 17 consecutive cases of SARS-CoV-2-related ARDS treated (N = 7) with the novel combination of ruxolitinib, a JAK1/2 inhibitor, 10 mg/twice daily for 14 days and eculizumab, an anti-C5a complement monoclonal antibody, 900 mg IV/weekly for a maximum of three weeks, or with the best available therapy (N = 10). […] Our results support the use of combined ruxolitinib and eculizumab for treatment of severe SARS-CoV-2-related ARDS by simultaneously turning off abnormal innate and adaptive immune responses.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32584421&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32584421&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
(5-7) Ruxolitinib (RXB), a JAK-STAT inhibitor, has also been shown to have proven efficacy in the treatment of sHLH.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32585295&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32585295&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
As many of the elevated cytokines signal through Janus kinase (JAK)1/JAK2, inhibition of these pathways with ruxolitinib has the potential to mitigate the COVID-19-associated cytokine storm and reduce mortality. […] This is supported by preclinical and clinical data from other diseases with hyperinflammatory states, where ruxolitinib has been shown to reduce cytokine levels and improve outcomes. […] The urgent need for treatments for patients with severe disease support expedited investigation of ruxolitinib for patients with COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32586380&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32586380&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Top hits included Vitamin E, ruxolitinib, and glutamine.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32587093&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32587093&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Moreover, ruxolitinib, an inhibitor of IFN-triggered Janus kinase (JAK)/signal transducer and activator of transcription (STAT) signaling, boosted SARS-CoV-2 replication in the IFN-competent Calu-3 cells.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32591667&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32591667&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Additionally, this study suggested oseltamivir, iopinavir, remdesivir, chloroquine, baricitinib, ruxolitinib, and fedratinib as possible drugs to help manage COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32593183&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32593183&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We present the case of a 53-year-old haematopoetic stem cell transplant recipient who developed a severe COVID-19 that was refractory to anti-IL6 therapy, but responded to Jak-Stat inhibition with ruxolitinib, demonstrating its safety and efficacy in this setting.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32593209&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32593209&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here, we report a compelling case of a 55-yo patient with proven COVID-19 pneumonia, who was taking the JAK1/2 inhibitor ruxolitinib in-label for co-existing primary myelofibrosis for 15 months prior to coronavirus infection. […] Since abrupt discontinuation of ruxolitinib may cause fatal cytokine storm and ARDS, ruxolitinib treatment was continued and was well tolerated, and the patient´s condition remained stable, without the need for mechanical ventilation or vasopressors. […] In conclusion, our report provides clinical evidence that ruxolitinib treatment is feasible and can be beneficial in patients with COVID-19 pneumonia, preventing cytokine storm and ARDS.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
