<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PlatCOVID</title>
    <link>/tissuepanel/skin/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tissuepanel/skin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>PlatCOVID</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>BioHub - UFPE</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu7e12209333f22d741aca7d462871821f_9877_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>PlatCOVID</title>
      <link>/tissuepanel/skin/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>skin</title>
      <link>/tissuepanel/skin/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/tissuepanel/skin/info/</guid>
      <description> 

&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;div id=&#34;tissue-sentence-context&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Tissue Sentence Context&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 1.&lt;/strong&gt; Analysis of context sentence of &lt;em&gt;skin&lt;/em&gt; tissue in 89 abstracts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
PMID
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Senteces
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32170800&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32170800&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Health professions preventing and controlling Coronavirus Disease 2019 are prone to skin and mucous membrane injury, which may cause acute and chronic dermatitis, secondary infection and aggravation of underlying skin diseases. […] Insufficient and excessive protection will have adverse effects on the skin and mucous membrane barrier.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32172546&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32172546&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To investigate the pathological characteristics and the clinical significance of novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV)-infected pneumonia (termed by WHO as corona virus disease 2019, COVID-19). &lt;b&gt;Methods:&lt;/b&gt; Minimally invasive autopsies from lung, heart, kidney, spleen, bone marrow, liver, pancreas, stomach, intestine, thyroid and skin were performed on three patients died of novel coronavirus pneumonia in Chongqing, China.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32201983&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32201983&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this paper we share our experiences in dealing with skin diseases in this special period and hope to provide some references for international colleagues in the epidemic situation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32219888&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32219888&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Since then numerous additional cases have been reported and the dissemination of the infection does not only pose a major health challenge for the entire population, medical care facilities and the economy, but also for the medical training of future doctors and outpatient care of patients with skin disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32220276&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32220276&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
All patients had acro-ischemia presentations including finger/toe cyanosis, skin bulla and dry gangrene.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32223004&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32223004&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Dermatoscope is a convenient diagnostic tool used by dermatologists in the diagnosis of skin, hair and nail disorders.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32255197&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32255197&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
During the outbreak of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19), healthcare workers (HCWs) caring for COVID-19 patient have to wear personal protective equipment (PPE) and are therefore susceptible to PPE-related adverse skin reactions. […] However, little is known about the prevalence and characteristics of these adverse skin reactions and their associated risk factors.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32255510&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32255510&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In patients with suspected or confirmed COVID-19 disease, all immunomodulators used for skin diseases should be immediately withheld, with the possible exception of systemic corticosteroid therapy, which needs to be weaned.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32268381&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32268381&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
· Parents should be engaged in shared decision-making with options for rooming in, skin-to-skin contact, and breastfeeding..
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32294259&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32294259&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A skin rash has been reported in 2 out of 1.099 patients presenting with Coronavirus disease 2019 in China [1], as in 14 of 48 patients with the same disease in Italia, but unfortunately without further description of its semiology [2]. […] We wish to report here the case of a woman who presented, coincidently with Covid-19, a skin rash that had an original picture.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32294264&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32294264&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We have read with great interest Dr Recalcati’s review about skin manifestations in COVID-19 as it is the first report on this subject&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; .
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32294265&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32294265&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Psoriasis is a major chronic inflammatory skin disease, affecting about 3% of the population in Italy, whose management require experienced specialists in order to guarantee high-quality standards of care.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32294273&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32294273&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
About skin manifestation, few cases of rashes on patients with laboratory-confirmed Covid-19 were described in two Chineses cohorts.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32298514&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32298514&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 presents many pressing challenges to the global dermatological community and our patients with ongoing skin needs, which must be considered by every dermatology provider.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32299776&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32299776&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We examined skin and lung tissues from 5 patients with severe COVID-19 characterized by respiratory failure (n= 5) and purpuric skin rash (n = 3). […] The purpuric skin lesions similarly showed a pauci-inflammatory thrombogenic vasculopathy, with deposition of C5b-9 and C4d in both grossly involved and normally-appearing skin.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32302444&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32302444&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
While most of the studies have focused on the skin reactions caused by gloves, other PPE such as gowns, respirator masks, face shields and goggles are also worn by HCWs for long hours during the current epidemic and skin irritations caused by these equipment may cause discouragement of health workers from using them [2].
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32304265&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32304265&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The working parties of TROG (head/neck/skin, genitourinary, breast and lung) were also sampled.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32305046&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32305046&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The patient underwent a cesarean delivery, and neonatal isolation was implemented immediately after birth, without delayed cord clamping or skin-to-skin contact.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32314460&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32314460&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 is a challenge for the treatment of dermatologic patients, either with severe inflammatory disorders or with skin cancer. […] COVID-19, although not a skin disease, by itself has an immense impact on dermatology.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32315079&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32315079&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It has been reported that the novel coronavirus disease (COVID-19) may be associated with a papulovesicular skin eruption predominantly involving the trunk.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32320091&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32320091&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
It is not known yet, if skin lesions and derangement of the skin barrier could make it easier for SARS-CoV-2 to transmit via indirect contact; it remains to be defined if specific mucosal or skin lesions are associated with SARS-CoV-2 infection, although some unpublished observations indicate the occurrence of a transient varicelliform exanthema during the early phase of the infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32320359&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32320359&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Objective:&lt;/b&gt; To investigate the prevalence, characteristics, and preventive status of skin injuries caused by personal protective equipment (PPE) in medical staff. &lt;b&gt;Approach:&lt;/b&gt; A cross-sectional survey was conducted online for understanding skin injuries among medical staff fighting COVID-19 in February 8-22, 2020. […] The questionnaire items included demographic data, grade of PPE and daily wearing time, skin injury types, anatomical sites, and preventive measures. […] Univariable analyses and logistic regression analyses were used to explore the risk factors associated with skin injuries. &lt;b&gt;Results:&lt;/b&gt; A total of 4,308 respondents were collected from 161 hospitals and 4,306 respondents were valid. […] The overall prevalence of skin injuries was 42.8% (95% confidence interval [CI] 41.30-44.30) with three types of device-related pressure injuries, moist-associated skin damage, and skin tear. […] Co-skin injuries and multiple location injuries were 27.4% and 76.8%, respectively. […] The logistic regression analysis indicated that sweating (95% CI for odds ratio [OR] 87.52-163.11), daily wearing time (95% CI for OR 1.61-3.21), male (95% CI for OR 1.11-2.13), and grade 3 PPE (95% CI for OR 1.08-2.01) were associated with skin injuries. […] Only 17.7% of respondents took prevention and 45.0% of skin injuries were treated. &lt;b&gt;Innovation:&lt;/b&gt; This is the first cross-sectional survey to understand skin injuries in medical staff caused by PPE, which is expected to be a benchmark. &lt;b&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/b&gt; The skin injuries among medical staff are serious, with insufficient prevention and treatment.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32329915&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32329915&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Here we report two cases of peculiar skin manifestation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32339344&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32339344&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Skin symptoms of COVID-19 have been poorly described but may include erythematous rash, urticaria and chicken pox like lesions (2-7).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32339362&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32339362&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Atopic dermatitis (AD) is a chronic inflammatory skin disease. […] Patients with AD have increased infection risk, including skin infections and systemic infections.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32345362&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32345362&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In the skin, digestive system, brain, and blood vessels, ACE2 expression levels were positively associated with immune signatures in both males and females.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32353170&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32353170&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Skin biopsy specimen showed slight spongiosis, basal cell vacuolation and mild perivascular lymphocytic infiltrate (c).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32356382&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32356382&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
According to the data reported by Lin et al &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; , based in the experience from healthcare workers in Wuhan, adverse skin reactions were reported in 74% of responders (n=376) to a general survey. […] The most commonly reported types of eruptions were skin dryness or desquamation (68.6%), papules or erythema (60.4%) and maceration (52,9%).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32358808&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32358808&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Since first reported in 2019, pneumonia associated with 2019 novel coronavirus disease (COVID-19) has rapidly developed into an outbreak across the world.&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; Number of the patients of all age groups has increased significantly.&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt; In order to curb the spread of the epidemic, thousands of health care workers (HCWs) have joined the front line of the fight against this highly contagious disease.&lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt; When taking care of patients with COVID-19 pneumonia, HCWs must first protect themselves by performing adequate hand hygiene and using protective equipment including medical mask, goggles/face shield, gown and gloves.&lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt; However, the wearing of these personal protective equipment (PPE) on a daily basis and the frequent use of hand disinfectants often cause skin problems which could reduce their enthusiasm for overloaded work and make them anxious at all stages of the pandemic.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32362062&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32362062&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Keeping the integrity of skin barrier is a critical method to prevent the spread of 2019-nCoV, since skin is the first line of defense of human body(4). […] It is of prime importance to ensure and maintain the skin clean, sterilized and protected of clinical health care staff during the fight against the epidemic. […] Self-protection of the medical staff is essential, however, utilizing protective equipment such as goggles, masks and protective clothing continuously impairs skin integrity and the skin damage caused by the respective protective measures must be taken seriously.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32365215&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32365215&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
These drugs are associated with some potential harms, including QTc-interval prolongation, hypoglycaemia, severe skin reactions and psychiatric effects.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32367558&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32367558&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The median age of these patients was 58 (minimum 18, maximum 80) years, and the most common dermatologic diseases before diagnosed COVID-19 were superficial fungal infections (5, 25%), psoriasis (4, 20%), and viral skin diseases (3, 15%).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32373409&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32373409&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Frequent hand washing implies a prolonged exposure to water and other chemical or physical agents and may induce several pathophysiologic changes, such as epidermal barrier disruption, impairment of keratinocytes, the subsequent release of proinflammatory cytokines, activation of the skin immune system, and delayed-type hypersensitivity reactions. […] Adverse dermatologic effects, such as excessive skin dryness or even contact dermatitis (particularly the irritant subtype and, to a lesser extent, the allergic subtype), can occur, especially in individuals with a history of atopic dermatitis. […] These skin conditions are perfectly manageable, and applying a moisturizer immediately after washing hands or after using a portable hand sanitizer is the cornerstone in preventing the development of eczematous changes in the hands.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32374033&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32374033&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We present four children investigated for suspected COVID-19 infection with who presented with acral skin findings and mild systemic symptoms.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32375776&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32375776&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
This would be sufficient to reduce R&lt;sub&gt;0&lt;/sub&gt; from 2.6 prior to lockdown to 0.62 (95% confidence interval [CI] 0.37-0.89) after the lockdown, based on all types of contact and 0.37 (95% CI = 0.22-0.53) for physical (skin to skin) contacts only.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32376531&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32376531&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Wearing the protective equipment (masks, goggles, and protective screens) with a poor breathability for a long time causes various skin problems, such as allergies, excessive skin hydration, local mechanical injuries, and even secondary infections. […] In addition, in a closed environment, compression and friction aggravate skin reactions, which may compromise duty performance of the medical staff. […] It is therefore essential to provide timely treatment opinions and prevention methods for common skin problems. […] We also give suggestions concerning the preparation of medical kit for skin protection in the epidemic area.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32381430&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32381430&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Skin lesion development occurred before the onset of respiratory symptoms or COVID-19 diagnosis in 12.5% (9/72) of the patients, and lesions spontaneously healed in all patients within 10 days. […] Majority of the studies reported no correlation between COVID-19 severity and skin lesions.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32383234&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32383234&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The searching strategy was (COVID* or coronavirus&lt;em&gt;) and (dermatol&lt;/em&gt; or skin* or cutaneous*). […] A total of 60 patients developed skin rashes, and the age ranged from 8 to 84. […] Skin lesions mainly appeared erythematous, urticarial, and vesicular (chicken pox-like or varicelliform). […] Newly reported eruptions like vascular lesions and peculiar (perniosis-like) skin lesions caused concern among dermatologists. […] This study reviewed the recently published COVID-19 studies with skin manifestations, which may pave the way for further research.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32384180&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32384180&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Vesicular skin rashes have been associated to the Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19), but there is little information about this cutaneous manifestation. […] Clinical characterization of skin findings was conducted by dermatologists. […] The median duration of the skin rash was of 10 days. […] Out of all, 19 patients (79.2%) presented the skin rash after the onset of COVID-19 symptoms. […] This monocentric study shows the clinical characteristics of vesicular skin rashes in COVID-19 patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32385858&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32385858&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
One patient developed the skin rash during hospitalization. […] These 3 patients returned to the Emergency department consulting for skin rashes 6, 7 and 4 days after discharge, respectively. […] Laboratory tests at the time of skin lesions showed worsening of one or more parameters, compared to those at the time of discharge (CRP, D-dimer and lymphocyte count). […] In all patients, skin lesions begun as erythematous papules in upper trunk, that progressively turned to erythemato-violaceous patches with a dusky center, and a pseudo-vesicle in the middle. […] All patients were treated with systemic corticosteroids with progressive resolution of the skin lesions within 2-3 weeks.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32385859&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32385859&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Novel coronavirus 2019 (SARS-CoV2) pandemic has particularly affected Italy, with a profound impact on the therapeutic strategy for complex disorder such as psoriasis, whose extensive skin damage might expose to an increased infective risk compared to the general population.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32385891&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32385891&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this quick review we have analyzed the mechanisms of action and related infective risk of drugs used for the treatment of immune-mediated and oncologic skin conditions during the daily clinical practice. […] The COVID19 emergency pandemic does not imply an under-treatment of existing skin conditions, which together with the SARS-Cov2 infection may jeopardize the patient’s life.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32386447&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32386447&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We have read with great attention the article by Van Damme et al. considering urticarial lesions as a coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) associated skin manifestation&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; .
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32386459&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32386459&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Since the beginning of the pandemic of Coronavirus disease (COVID-19) an increasing number of skin manifestations have been reported.&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt; Most reports concern adult patients and describe various patterns of skin eruptions, in most of cases with low specificity and no univocal temporal association with the onset of systemic symptoms of COVID-19.&lt;sup&gt;1-3&lt;/sup&gt;.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32386460&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32386460&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Different skin manifestations of COVID-19 are being reported. […] Pruritus and mild pain were the only skin symptoms elicited, and only 10 had mild respiratory and/or GI symptoms. […] Skin biopsies obtained in six patients were consistent with chilblains.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32387409&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32387409&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
A total of 2.3% of patients reported mild adverse events (gastrointestinal or skin symptoms, headache, insomnia and transient blurred vision).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32388643&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32388643&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The purposes of this report are to familiarize dermatologists with the hygiene practices recommended for COVID-19 prevention, to highlight adverse cutaneous reactions associated with repeated exposures to detergents and disinfectants, and to discuss strategies which patients can implement during the COVID-19 pandemic to minimize skin irritation white still performing hygiene practices effectively.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32396675&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32396675&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Several dermatoses have been reported due to PPE, such as pressure injury, contact dermatitis, pressure urticaria, and exacerbation of pre-existing skin diseases, including seborrheic dermatitis and acne.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32396999&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32396999&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Skin biopsies performed on each of the 6 patients demonstrated near identical histopathologic findings to those of idiopathic perniosis, with a lymphocytic inflammatory infiltrate without evidence of thromboembolism or immune complex vasculitis. […] We offer a clinical approach to evaluation of patients with this presentation and discuss the possibility that these skin findings represent a convalescent-phase cutaneous reaction to SARS-CoV-2 infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32400366&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32400366&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Ichthyosis – also called fish scale disease – is a group of skin diseases, which are characterised by xerosis and scaling.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32400852&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32400852&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Our results strongly suggest that while amounts of alcohol sufficient to cause a DER may be inhaled when hand sanitizers are used in confined spaces, absorption can be avoided by dispersal of the fumes, and absorption from the skin alone does not occur in pharmacologically significant quantities. […] Warnings about absorption of alcohol through the skin from hand sanitizers and products such as perfumes, deodorants and after-shave (whose use is often warned against when disulfiram is prescribed) should be modified accordingly.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32401228&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32401228&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The controversial procedures in the care of Covid-19-suspected or -positive asymptomatic women in labor were: mode of delivery, companion during birth and labor, skin-to-skin contact, breastfeeding, and visits during a hospital stay.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32401352&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32401352&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Though infection with the SARS-CoV2 virus predominantly manifests in the lung as an interstitial pneumonia (“ground glass opacities”), there is increasing evidence that the virus invades all compartments of the body, particularly the eyes, heart, skin, kidneys, and the central nervous system(CNS).&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; This article is protected by copyright.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32404482&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32404482&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
COVID-19 patients had a high proportion of organisms reflective of commensal skin microbiota, reducing the bacteremia rate to 1.6% when excluded.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32407551&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32407551&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Phototherapy is undoubtedly a long-established, relatively safe means of reducing the burden of inflammatory skin disease avoiding large doses of immunosuppression.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32407564&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32407564&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Many clinical manifestations of the virus are described, and new symptoms are emerging, only few cases of patients with skin manifestation were described since the pandemic was announced by the WHO on March.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32409976&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32409976&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
With the evolution of the pandemic, skin lesions were observed. […] Viral skin lesions are frequent causes of exanthema.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32416014&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32416014&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
New patient referrals from primary care into dermatology services usually enter via one of three routes: (i) 2 week wait for suspected serious skin malignancies, (ii) routine non-urgent cases and (iii) emergency referrals (via an on call service).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32418532&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32418532&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The main SARS-CoV-2-related COVID-19 symptoms/diseases reported hitherto are hypertension, atherosclerosis, thrombosis (coagulopathy), diarrhea, glaucoma, anosmia, ageusia, skin lesions (dermatitis), autoimmune inflammation of the central nervous system, and damages to various organs such as the lung, heart, kidney, and testicle [1, 2, 14].
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32421479&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32421479&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To help support patients and frontline health professionals, &lt;i&gt;JWC&lt;/i&gt; is republishing the consensus in a digital format, along with a new introductory article outlining the DRPU risks posed by PPE and other medical devices used by patients and health professionals during the pandemic, and how the skin damage can be avoided. […] The aim is to provide frontline staff with a clear, simple strategy on how to prevent the risk of personal skin damage and/or DRPU during the pandemic, as well as point them in the direction of more indepth guidance on long-term strategies for prevention, for both themselves and patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32421857&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32421857&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Since the outbreak of novel Coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19), reports concerning suspicious COVID-19 skin manifestations are progressively increasing.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32421877&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32421877&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Currently, several clinicians described an increasingly cases of coronavirus-positive patients reporting skin problems, either in early stage of infection or as late onset manifestation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32421878&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32421878&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Our previous research revealed that long-term wearing of N95 masks could lead to various facial skin lesions, which might affect their routine work and mental health. […] More importantly, severe skin lesions (e.g. ulcers) might put them in danger of being infected.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32422693&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32422693&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In France, COVID-19 wasn’t known to cause cutaneous manifestations before April 6&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; 2020, when an alert about possible associated skin symptoms was raised to the general public and the professional social network&lt;sup&gt;2-4&lt;/sup&gt; .
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32425356&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32425356&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
•COVID-19 is associated with specific skin manifestations and drug eruption.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32425360&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32425360&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Some of the mechanisms and conditions underlying endothelial dysfunction.A-human skin capillaries, visualized with high-resolution intravital color microscopy in the finger of a patient with obesity, metabolic syndrome and coronary artery disease.B- healthy control.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32436262&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32436262&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Nowadays hand hygiene practices with alcohol sanitizers are an unavoidable reality for many people which cause skin dryness and flaking.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32436617&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32436617&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
While it is unclear whether the patients on ISAs for skin conditions are more prone to develop COVID 19, and what impact the ISA may have on the clinical outcome if a patient does get infected, rationalizations based on the specific immune effects of each drug, and existing literature on incidence of various infections with each, are possible.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32437936&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32437936&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The differential diagnosis of drug-induced skin rash and hand-foot-mouth disease was ruled out based on the patient’s previous history and course of the disease.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32438942&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32438942&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Due to the shortage of Covid-19 testing devices, passengers were screened by measuring skin temperature.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32441360&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32441360&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
9 (37.5%) of these patients also had accompanying COVID-19 skin lesions (2 urticarial lesions, 2 livedo and necrosis, 2 maculopapular eruption, 2 vesicular rashes, 1 pseudo-chilblain).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32443177&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32443177&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We used MIA-US for tissue sampling of lungs, liver, heart, kidneys, spleen, brain, skin, skeletal muscle and testis for histology and RT-PCR to detect SARS-COV-2-RNA.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32445583&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32445583&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
During examination of cases of chilblains in children and adolescents, we identified four patients who also showed skin lesions similar to erythema multiforme (EM). […] Skin biopsies from two patients showed features not typical of EM, such as deep perivascular and perieccrine infiltrate and absence of necrosis of keratinocytes.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32446866&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32446866&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The virus may bind to corneal and conjunctival angiotensin converting enzyme 2 (ACE2) receptors and potentially to the lipophilic periocular skin and superficial tear film with downstream carriage into the nasopharynx and subsequent access to the lungs and gut.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32447801&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32447801&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Herpes Zoster is a viral skin disease caused by varicella zoster that remains dormant in the dorsal root ganglia of cutaneous nerves following a primary chicken pox infection.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32447934&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32447934&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
All patients had acro-ischemia presentations including finger/toe cyanosis, skin bulla and dry gangrene.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32449781&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32449781&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Subjects who reported sensitive skin and atopic predisposition, and those with facial dermatoses (acne, atopic dermatitis or seborrhoeic dermatitis) were at significantly higher risk of itch development.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32452036&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32452036&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The increase of hand sanitation during the COVID-19 pandemic impairs the skin of the hands across all HCWs, independent of direct intensive care of affected patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32452545&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32452545&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
To establish the real prevalence of COVID-19 in patients with acral skin lesions, we firstly evaluated all the cases of acral lesions presented in dermatology and paediatrics departments and family doctors’ offices in an eastern Spanish region over a three-week period. […] Our study suggests that acral skin lesions are not a specific marker of SARS-CoV-2 infection. […] Although larger prospective studies are needed, current evidence indicates that acral skin lesions should not be regarded as a sign of COVID-19 in otherwise asymptomatic patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32452563&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32452563&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In 2014, Woods et al. undertook a first-in-person study to assess the effect on skin of a 222 nm UVC emitting device (Sterilray disinfectant wand, Healthy Environment Innovations, Dover, NH, USA).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32453902&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32453902&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Colonna et al. reported four children with suspected COVID-19 cases with “[h]istology from one case showed signs of vasculitis with evident fibrin thrombus [1].” While various skin findings have been reported with COVID-19 infection, the chilblains lesions have been reported from Italy and Spain, and sporadically from China, the starting point of disease pandemic [2-5].
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32455499&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32455499&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
SARS-CoV-2 has been hypothesized as the aetiologic agent of CLL, on the basis of the temporal correlation between the “burst” of skin manifestations and the viral pandemic, even though we have scarce evidence of swab-confirmed infections.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32458530&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32458530&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We will focus on are skin disorders such as autoimmune connective tissue disorders, neutrophilic dermatoses and vasculitis.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32458536&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32458536&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Psoriasis and atopic dermatitis are common, chronic, inflammatory skin conditions, with immune dysregulation as a shared mechanism; therefore, mainstays of treatment include systemic immunomodulating therapies.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32458588&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32458588&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Because of the COVID-19 emergency, on March 9, 2020 Italy went in lock-down imposing the closure of non-urgent outpatient clinics devoted to care of chronic, severe, inflammatory skin diseases that require periodic follow-up. […] Remote monitoring was performed in 183 patients (126 moderate to severe psoriasis, 10 severe acne, 11 severe atopic dermatitis, 11 hidradenitis suppurativa, 9 blistering autoimmune diseases, 16 other autoimmune skin diseases). […] Our real-life experience shows that remote monitoring was effective in preventing unnecessary worsening of severe chronic skin diseases and poor outcomes due to withdrawal of current therapy.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32460421&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32460421&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The most frequent cancer worldwide is skin cancer, occurring at epidemic rates in countries exposed to high levels of chronic ultraviolet radiation such as Australia and New Zealand (ANZ). […] Australia has the highest incidence of non-melanoma skin cancer (NMSC) in the world.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32461409&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32461409&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The increased frequency of ABHR use and the aerosols generated pose a potential threat to the skin and exposed mucosal surfaces, especially that of the eye due to the proximity of use.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32468052&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32468052&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
CTSL was upregulated in lymphoid neoplasm diffuse large B‑cell lymphoma, oesophageal carcinoma, glioblastoma multiforme, head and neck squamous cell carcinoma, lower grade glioma, pancreatic adenocarcinoma, skin cutaneous melanoma, stomach adenocarcinoma, and thymoma.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/32468229&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;32468229&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Herein we propose an alternative model of skin cancer screening and the organization of screening campaigns in order to detect malignant lesions early during this emergency period.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
