<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>none | PlatCOVID</title>
    <link>/genepanel/1401/</link>
      <atom:link href="/genepanel/1401/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>none</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>BioHub - UFPE</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu7e12209333f22d741aca7d462871821f_9877_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>none</title>
      <link>/genepanel/1401/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRP</title>
      <link>/genepanel/1401/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/genepanel/1401/info/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;C-reactive protein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p align=&#34;left&#34; style=&#34;font-size:16px&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ENTREZID: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gene/1401&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;1401&lt;/a&gt; | Type: Protein Coding |
Map: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/genome/gdv/browser/gene/?id=1401&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt; 1q23.2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
OMIM: &lt;a href=&#39;https://omim.org/entry/123260&#39; target=&#39;_blank&#39;&gt;123260&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p align=&#34;justify&#34; style=&#34;font-size:16px&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Summary Entrez&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;The protein encoded by this gene belongs to the pentaxin family. It is involved in several host defense related functions based on its ability to recognize foreign pathogens and damaged cells of the host and to initiate their elimination by interacting with humoral and cellular effector systems in the blood. Consequently, the level of this protein in plasma increases greatly during acute phase response to tissue injury, infection, or other inflammatory stimuli. [provided by RefSeq, Sep 2009] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRP</title>
      <link>/genepanel/1401/gene_expression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/genepanel/1401/gene_expression/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;C-reactive protein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;gene-expression&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Gene Expression&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 1.&lt;/strong&gt; CRP expression overview from &lt;em&gt;human protein atlas database&lt;/em&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
ENSEMBL
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Tissue
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Protein
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
mRNA
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
ENSG00000132693
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
liver
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
High
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
532.1
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
ENSG00000132693
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
gallbladder
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Low
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
172.9
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
ENSG00000132693
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
soft tissue
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Low
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
ENSG00000132693
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
endometrium
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Not detected
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
5.2
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
ENSG00000132693
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
adipose tissue
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
NA
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
3.9
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRP</title>
      <link>/genepanel/1401/gene_context/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/genepanel/1401/gene_context/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/kePrint/kePrint.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;C-reactive protein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;gene-context-sentence&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Gene Context Sentence&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:12px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Table 2.&lt;/strong&gt; Analysis of context sentence of CRP gene in 25 abstracts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped&#34; style=&#34;width: auto !important; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
PMID
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center;position: sticky; top:0; background-color: #FFFFFF;&#34;&gt;
Gene Context Sentence
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32026671
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34; style=&#34;list-style-type: decimal&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The blood test of the patients showed normal or decreased white blood cell count (23/29), decreased lymphocyte count (20/29), increased hypersensitive C reactive protein (hs-CRP) (27/29), and normal procalcitonin. […] However, there were no statistically significant differences in serum levels of tumor necrosis factor-alpha (TNF-α), IL-1, IL-8, IL-10, hs-CRP, lymphocyte count and LDH among the three groups (P&amp;gt;0.05). &lt;b&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/b&gt; The clinical characteristics of 2019-nCoV pneumonia are similar to those of common viral pneumonia. […] 2）患者外周血一般表现为白细胞总数正常或减低（23/29），淋巴细胞计数减少（20/29），超敏C-反应蛋白（hs-CRP）增高（27/29），降钙素原正常。 […] 而3组研究对象血清中的肿瘤坏死因子-α（TNF-α）、IL-1β、IL-8、IL-10、hs-CRP、淋巴细胞计数、LDH表达水平差异均无统计学意义（&lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;&amp;gt;0.05）。
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32048163
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The most common laboratory abnormalities were hypoalbuminemia, lymphopenia, decreased percentage of lymphocytes (LYM) and neutrophils (NEU), elevated C-reactive protein (CRP) and lactate dehydrogenase (LDH), and decreased CD8 count. […] ALB, LYM, LYM (%), LDH, NEU (%), and CRP were highly correlated to the acute lung injury. […] Age, viral load, lung injury score, and blood biochemistry indexes, albumin (ALB), CRP, LDH, LYM (%), LYM, and NEU (%), may be predictors of disease severity.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32061066
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The median of CRP was 16.3 mg/L, including 5 patients with slightly elevated (5/9) , 4 patients with normal values (4/9) . the results of procalcitonin test were negative in5 patients. […] 5例患者外周血C反应蛋白（CRP）轻度升高，4例患者CRP正常，中位数为16.3 mg/L。
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32120458
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The observation indicators included total blood count, C-reactive protein (CRP), arterial blood gas analysis, myocardial injury markers, coagulation function, liver and kidney function, electrolyte, procalcitonin (PCT), B-type natriuretic peptide (BNP), blood lipid, pulmonary CT and pathogen detection. &lt;b&gt;Results:&lt;/b&gt; Compared with the general group, the lymphocyte count (0.74×10(9) (0.34×10(9), 0.94×10(9))/L vs. […] 0.99×10(9) (0.71×10(9), 1.29×10(9))/L, &lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;=0.03) was extremely lower in the critical group, CRP (106.98 (81.57, 135.76) mg/L vs. […] 观察指标包括全血细胞计数、C反应蛋白（CRP）、动脉血气分析、心肌损伤标志物、凝血功能、肝肾功能、电解质、降钙素原（PCT）、B型利钠肽（BNP）、血脂、肺部CT及病原学检测。 […] &lt;b&gt;结果：&lt;/b&gt; 与普通组比较，危重组患者淋巴细胞计数[0.74×10(9)（0.34×10(9)，0.94×10(9)）/L比0.99×10(9)（0.71×10(9)，1.29×10(9)）/L，&lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;=0.03]较低，CRP[106.98（81.57，135.76）mg/L比34.34（9.55，76.54）mg/L，&lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;&amp;lt;0.001]和PCT[0.20（0.15，0.48）μg/L比0.11（0.06，0.20）μg/L，&lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;&amp;lt;0.001]较高；危重组体重指数（BMI）明显高于普通组[25.5（23.0，27.5）kg/m(2)比22.0（20.0， 24.0）kg/m(2)，&lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;=0.003]。
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32141280
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Both univariate and multivariate logistic regression were used to analyze the correlation of past medical history including hypertension, diabetes and coronary heart disease (CHD) , as well as the levels of serum NT-proBNP and cTnI to the disease severity of COVID-19 patients. &lt;b&gt;Results:&lt;/b&gt; Age, hypersensitive C-reactive protein(hs-CRP) and serum creatinine levels of the patients were higher in critical care cases than in mild cases(all &lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;&amp;lt;0.05). […] Univariate logistic regression analysis showed that age, male, elevated NT-proBNP, elevated cTnI, elevated hs-CRP, elevated serum creatinine, hypertension, and CHD were significantly correlated with critical disease status(all &lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;&amp;lt;0.05). […] 收集入选患者住院期间实验室检查结果，包括血清N末端B型利钠肽原（NT-proBNP）、心肌肌钙蛋白I（cTnI）、超敏C反应蛋白（hs-CRP）和血肌酐的最高值，血红蛋白的最低值。 […] 危重型组患者的年龄、hs-CRP和血肌酐水平均高于非危重型组（&lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;均&amp;lt;0.05）。 […] 单因素logistic回归分析结果显示，年龄、男性、NT-proBNP升高、cTnI升高、hs-CRP升高、血肌酐升高、患有高血压、既往冠心病史是COVID-19危重型的相关因素（&lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt;均&amp;lt;0.05）。
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32166607
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Common laboratory findings include normal/ low white cell counts with elevated C-reactive protein (CRP).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32209890
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
C-reactive protein (CRP) levels were also significantly higher in the death group on admission (109.25 [35.00, 170.28] mg/L vs.3.22 [1.04, 21.80] mg/L, Z = 10.206, P &amp;lt; 0.001) showed no significant improvement after treatment (109.25 [35.0, 170.28] mg/L vs. […] Compared to the recovered group, more patients in the death group exhibited characteristics of advanced age, pre-existing comorbidities, dyspnea, oxygen saturation decrease, increased WBC count, decreased lymphocytes, and elevated CRP levels.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32233642
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Correlation analysis indicated total lymphocyte count was positively correlated with CD4+ T cell count, and no significant differences were found between the 2 groups in other laboratory measurements, including those of white blood cell (WBC) count, C-reactive protein (CRP), albumin, lactate dehydrogenase (LDH), and D-dimer.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32239591
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Males were more likely to have liver injury when infected with COVID-19 (P &amp;lt; .05); compared with patients without liver injury, patients with liver injury had increased levels of white blood cell counts, neutrophils, CRP and CT score (P &amp;lt; .05) and had a longer length of stay (P &amp;lt; .05).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32239796
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Most of the liver function indexes in COVID-19 patients were correlated with CRP and NLR, the markers of inflammation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32243911
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
We aimed to assess the usefulness of CRP levels in the early stage of COVID-19 and to correlate them with lung lesions and severe presentation. […] On admission CRP levels were collected, and the diameter of the largest lung lesion was measured in the most severe lung lesion by lung CT scan. […] Differences in the diameter and CRP levels were compared in the following groups of patients: mild group, moderate group, severe group, and critical group. […] CRP levels and the diameter of the largest lung lesion in the moderate group were higher than those in the mild group (Mann-Whitney test=-2.647, -2.171, P˂0.05), those in the severe group were higher than those in the moderate group (Mann-Whitney test=0.693, -2.177, P˂0.05), and those in the critical group were higher than those in the severe group (Mann-Whitney test=-0.068, -1.549, P˂0.05). […] CRP levels were positively correlated with the diameter of lung lesion and severe presentation (correlation coefficient=0.873, 0.734, P˂0.001). […] In the early stage of COVID-19 CRP levels were positively correlated with lung lesions and could reflect disease severity.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32249918
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Compared to the controls, COVID-19 pneumonia patients had lower counts of white blood cells (WBC), neutrophils, C-reactive protein (CRP), and alanine aminotransferase (ALT) on admission. […] Increased levels of WBC, neutrophils, eosinophils, and CRP were found in postpartum blood tests of pneumonia patients.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32251805
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The rising of neutrophils, SAA, PCT, CRP, cTnI, D-dimer, LDH and lactate levels can be used as indicators of disease progression, as well as the decline of lymphocytes counts.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32253759
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The demographic, treatment, laboratory parameters of C-reactive protein (CRP) and IL-6 before and after TCZ therapy and clinical outcome in the 15 COVID-19 patients were retrospectively assessed. […] Although TCZ treatment ameliorated the increased CRP in all patients rapidly, for the four critically ill patients who received an only single dose of TCZ, three of them (No. 1, 2, and 3) still dead and the CRP level in the rest one patient (No. 7) failed to return to normal range with a clinical outcome of disease aggravation.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32255437
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The most prevalent presenting symptoms were fever (64%) and cough (59%), and a mildly elevated mean (SD) C-reactive protein (CRP) level of 11.22(11.06) and erythrocyte sedimentation rate of 18.8 (15.17) were detected.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32259129
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
In this context, both &lt;i&gt;in vitro&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;in vivo&lt;/i&gt; studies have revealed that metronidazole could decrease the levels of several cytokines, which are known to increase during the COVID-19 infection, including interleukin (IL)8, IL6, IL1B, tumor necrosis factor (TNF)α, IL12, IL1α, and interferon (IFN)γ, as well as the levels of C-reactive protein (CRP) and neutrophil count.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32259132
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Patients with positive RT-PCR had significantly higher neutrophil (NEU) count (p = 0.0001), and C-reactive protein (CRP) (p = 0.04), lactate dehydrogenase (LDH) (p = 0.0001), aspartate aminotransferase (AST) (p = 0.001), alanine aminotransferase (ALT) (p = 0.0001), and Urea (p = 0.001) levels in serum. […] ALT (AUC = 0.879), CRP (AUC = 0.870), NEU (AUC = 0.858), LDH (AUC = 0.835), and Urea (AUC = 0.835) had very good accuracy in predicting cases with positive RT-PCR for COVID-19, respectively. […] Our findings suggest that level of LDH, CRP, ALT and NEU can be used to predict the result of COVID-19 test.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32271459
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
Compared with the non-severe group, the severe group showed statistical significance in older age, hypertension, bilateral lung plaque shadow, decrease in lymphocyte count, increase in C-reactive protein (CRP), aspartate aminotransferase (AST), lactate dehydrogenase, and creatine kinase.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32271602
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
No statistical difference was observed in plasma C-reactive protein (CRP) between the two groups (COVID-19 and non-COVID-19 ) of patients (P = 0.402), while the white blood cell count and lymphocyte count of the confirmed patients were slightly lower than those of the suspected patients (P &amp;lt; 0.05).
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32277967
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The dynamic changes of blood SAA, CRP, PCT, WBC, Lymphocyte (L), PLT, CT imaging, and disease progression were studied. […] COVID-19 patients had significantly increased SAA and CRP levels, while L count decreased, and PCT, WBC, and PLT were in the normal range. […] As disease progressed from mild to critically severe, SAA and CRP gradually increased, while L decreased, and PLT, WBC, and PCT had no significant changes; ROC curve analysis suggests that SAA/L, CRP, SAA, and L count are valuable in evaluating the severity of COVID-19 and distinguishing critically ill patients from mild ones; Patients with SAA consistently trending down during the course of disease have better prognosis, compared with the patients with SAA continuously rising; The initial SAA level is positively correlated with the dynamic changes of the serial CT scans.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32281668
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The levels of C-reactive protein (CRP) in the severe group at the initial and progression stages were higher than those in the mild group. […] Correlation analysis showed that CRP (R=0.62, P&amp;lt;0.01), erythrocyte sedimentation rate (R=0.55, P&amp;lt;0.01) and granulocyte/lymphocyte ratio (R=0.49, P&amp;lt;0.01) were positively associated with the CT severity scores. […] Receiver-operating characteristic analysis demonstrated that area under the curve of CRP on the first visit for predicting severe COVID-19 was 0.87 (95% CI 0.10-1.00) at 20.42 mg/L cut-off, with sensitivity and specificity 83% and 91%, respectively. […] CRP in severe COVID-19 patients increased significantly at the initial stage, prior to CT findings. […] Importantly, CRP, which was associated with disease development, predicted early severe COVID-19.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32282949
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
During the disease course, longitudinal evaluation of lymphocyte count dynamics and inflammatory indices, including LDH, CRP and IL-6 may help to identify cases with dismal prognosis and prompt intervention in order to improve outcomes.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32283217
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
The laboratory investigations showed leukopenia and lymphopenia as well as increased creatinine and CRP levels.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32294503
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
During the prenatal and postpartum period, there was no difference in the count of WBC, Neutrophils and Lymphocyte, the radio of Neutrophils and Lymphocyte and the level of CRP between the confirmed COVID-19 group and the control group(p&amp;lt;0.05). 20 babies (from confirmed mother and from normal mother) were subjected to SARS-CoV-2 examination by throat swab samples in 24 hours after birth and no case was tested positive.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
32294504
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
After short-term follow-up, 16 patients (27.6%) presented symptoms with lower lymphocyte count and higher CRP, mainly including fever, cough and fatigue.
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRP</title>
      <link>/genepanel/1401/clinvar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/genepanel/1401/clinvar/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;C-reactive protein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;clinvar-summary&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ClinVar Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:16px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
Under development
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRP</title>
      <link>/genepanel/1401/geo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/genepanel/1401/geo/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;C-reactive protein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;geo-dataset-summary&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;GEO dataset Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size:16px&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
Under development
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
